<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Berlinale - Berlin International Film Festival</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/programme/on-sale-from-today.html</link><description>Films in the Berlinale programme (on sale / in programme).</description><item><title>Nous sommes les fruits de la forêt by Rithy Panh</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202600987.html</link><description><![CDATA[The Indigenous Bunong cultivate Cambodia&rsquo;s forests and fields with the flick of a wrist. The rice grain embodies and brings together the ideas of preserving natural cycles, tradition, balanced economy and the worship of ancestors and gods; this equilibrium has been eaten up with the arrival of modernity and globalisation. The Bunong are losing the forest of whose ownership they have no conception. Pa Kreb belongs to the last generation of this culture of all-round skills, his voiceover analyses the clash of competing economic practices and the loss of a world in which exchange (instead of money) is imaginable. What looks like an ethnographic study (in the language of the Bunong) in the beginning, and fuses the real-life present with the past that flashes up in split-screen archive material, gradually becomes a lesson both bitter and valuable. Following films that catapulted his oeuvre into other realms over the last years &ndash; <em class="film-other">Irradi&eacute;s</em> (Berlinale<em class="program"> Competition</em> 2020), <em class="film-other">Everything Will Be Ok</em> (Berlinale<em class="program"> Competition</em> 2022) and <em class="film-other">Rendez-vous avec Pol Pot</em> (Cannes premiere 2024) &ndash; Rithy Panh now returns to a seemingly simpler form. Yet in modesty, there is wisdom and far-sightedness. Grand!<br/>
Cast: by Rithy Panh (Director), Rithy Panh (Screenplay) Cast: Pa Kreb, Mak Kreb, Yeay Kreb, Mak Lisa, Pouk Choeut, Mak Choeut, Pouk Noas, Mak Noas, Pouk Pritch, Mak Pritch<br/>
Durata: 87 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202600987_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sat Feb 14 21:00 - Delphi Filmpalast, Wed Feb 18 17:30 - Cinema Paris, Fri Feb 20 11:30 - Cubix 8, Sun Feb 22 12:00 - Cinema Betonhalle@Silent Green]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202600987.html</guid></item><item><title>Traces by Marysia Nikitiuk</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202601639.html</link><description><![CDATA[The film shines a light on Ukrainian women who, after surviving conflict-related sexual violence and torture during the Russian war of aggression, refuse to remain silent. Through the journey of Iryna Dovhan, a former captive turned activist who documents testimonies of affected women in the de-occupied territories of Ukraine, the film weaves a portrait of a collective trauma while opening space for hope. Iryna gathers other survivors into a circle of courage and care. Together, they transform their pain into a force for truth, justice and mutual support. More than a record of war crimes, <em class="film">Traces</em> is a testament to resilience and the solidarity of women standing side by side.<br/>
Cast: by Alisa Kovalenko (Screenplay) Cast: Iryna Dovhan, Tetiana Vasylenko, Liudmyla Mefodiivna, Galyna Tyshchenko, Olha Cherniak, Nina<br/>
Durata: 85 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202601639_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Mon Feb 16 17:30 - Haus der Berliner Festspiele, Tue Feb 17 15:30 - Urania, Wed Feb 18 10:00 - Cubix 7, Sat Feb 21 17:50 - Cubix 7, Sun Feb 22 22:30 - Cubix 5]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202601639.html</guid></item><item><title>Panda by Xinyang Zhang</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202601679.html</link><description><![CDATA[A decaying riverbank in wintry, ice-cold Nanjing. In a neighbourhood of crumbling houses lives a group of wraithlike figures. They do not fit into mainstream society and are each unique in their own particular way: an impoverished poet whose verses can heal; a young man attempting to end his life by leaping into the river; a vagabond searching for a dragon so he can return to the sky; and a traumatised young woman seeking comfort from an old friend who has since become a monk. Meanwhile, a severed fingertip has been eaten by a dog; improvised music drifts from a harmonica and the Chinese string instrument, the erhu; a mobile music wagon stands by the river. Surreal, real and hyperreal at once, a world unfolds like a painting in which documentary images and fiction dissolve into one another &ndash; as absurd as it is poetic, alive with humour and brimming with humanity. The inner logic of these characters forms the heart of a radically independent spirit, shaped by resilience and a quiet, stubborn defiance.<br/>
Cast: by Xinyang Zhang (Director), Xinyang Zhang (Screenplay) Cast: Xianmin Zhang, Elvis Yang, Han Chen, Jiahe Lyu, Ruyin Zhang<br/>
Durata: 146 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/media/filmstills/2026/plakate-2026/202601679_9_ORG.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Mon Feb 16 20:30 - Cinema Paris, Wed Feb 18 15:30 - CinemaxX 8, Thu Feb 19 10:00 - Cubix 8, Sat Feb 21 11:00 - Delphi Filmpalast]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202601679.html</guid></item><item><title>Doggerland by Kim Ekberg</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202602141.html</link><description><![CDATA[A Swedish indie shot on black-and-white 16mm with lively music: fleet-footed, mercurial, zany, improvised, atmospheric and full of sidesteps. Forty-year-old diabolo performer Alf still lives with his mum Monica and wanders, flaneur-like, through Norrk&ouml;ping, where the massive cultural cuts are happening to which director Kim Ekberg, inhabitant of the city and founder of anti-capitalist production company Post Post, is stepping up with <em class="film">Doggerland</em>. For him, culture is about daily life, reviving the social democratic &ldquo;we&rsquo;re all on board&rdquo;, about real locations, spaces and people who &ndash; like John and Anita Holm here &ndash; can become Alf and Monica while also being mother and son in real life. They like talking at cross purposes, too. She wants him to look for a real job and move out. When he finally goes on tour through Europe, she seems to regret it. Following <em class="film-other">XXL</em> (2024, co-directed by Sawandi Groskind), Ekberg keeps building worlds of everyday wonder with familiar characters, where the creative and the social intermingle and one can learn what (documentary) film is capable of in evening classes from Jan Lindqvist. Like measuring time with light and production design, now and across the arc of life.<br/>
Cast: by Kim Ekberg (Director), Kim Ekberg (Screenplay) Cast: John Holm, Anita Holm, Roger Carlsson, Kalle Thuleman, Astrid Drettner, Lotta Bäck-Vogel, Marcos Fuenzalida, Ilya Wikström, Hannah Wiker Wikström, Martin Grennberger, Stefan Ramstedt, Jan Lindqvist, Eva Eklund, Mam Häll<br/>
Durata: 76 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/media/filmstills/2026/plakate-2026/202602141_9_RWD_1920.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sat Feb 14 13:30 - ADK am Hanseatenweg, Mon Feb 16 14:30 - Cinema Paris, Wed Feb 18 15:00 - CinemaxX 7, Sat Feb 21 20:30 - Cinema Paris]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202602141.html</guid></item><item><title>El Tren Fluvial</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202602169.html</link><description><![CDATA[Nine-year-old Milo is growing up with the pressure to become a great Malambo dancer and the &ldquo;perfect&rdquo; son. He dreams of taking control of his life and escaping his responsibilities of washing dishes, cooking and practicing the Malambo at night. Milo wants another life. He fantasises about travelling by train and exploring the city of Buenos Aires, which he has seen so many times in the movies and on television. However, in order to break free from his family and the countryside, and make his big dreams come true, he must dare to take a new journey: a journey into solitude, and the unknown adventures and pleasures of the big city.<br/>
Cast: by Lorenzo Ferro (Screenplay) Cast: Milo Barria, Rita Pauls, Mariano Barria, Fabián Casas, Lucrecia Pazos, Pehuen Pedre, Mailén Barría, Diego Puente<br/>
Durata: 75 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/media/filmstills/2026/plakate-2026/202602169_9_RWD_1920.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Mon Feb 16 19:00 - Bluemax Theater, Tue Feb 17 16:00 - Cubix 9, Wed Feb 18 22:15 - Cubix 8, Fri Feb 20 13:00 - Colosseum 1, Sun Feb 22 14:30 - Cubix 9]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202602169.html</guid></item><item><title>A New Dawn by Yoshitoshi Shinomiya</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202602554.html</link><description><![CDATA[Once located in a forest of lush greenery, the Obinata firework factory is set for an administrative shutdown tomorrow and a major road is planned to be extended directly through the premises. For the past four years, Keitaro has locked himself inside the shuttered factory and has been making fireworks on his own. He is determined to unravel the mystery of the Shuhari, a mythical firework that represents the universe, and that was envisioned by his father before he disappeared without a trace. <em class="film">A New Dawn</em> is a story about the legacy of family, the bonds of childhood friendship, and the impact of climate change and urban sprawl on a picturesque village.<br/>
Cast: by Yoshitoshi Shinomiya (Director), Yoshitoshi Shinomiya (Screenplay) Cast: Riku Hagiwara, Kotone Furukawa, Miyu Irino<br/>
Durata: 76 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202602554_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Wed Feb 18 21:30 - Berlinale Palast, Thu Feb 19 16:00 - Uber Eats Music Hall, Fri Feb 20 12:30 - Urania, Fri Feb 20 20:00 - Haus der Berliner Festspiele, Sun Feb 22 11:00 - HKW 1 - Miriam Makeba Auditorium]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202602554.html</guid></item><item><title>Isabel by Gabe Klinger</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202602856.html</link><description><![CDATA[Isabel, a sommeli&egrave;re in S&atilde;o Paulo&rsquo;s fine-dining scene, dreams of escaping her controlling boss and opening her own wine bar where she decides what goes in the glass. When her plans fail to ferment as expected, Isabel must decide between playing it safe and taking her one bold chance to uncork her destiny on her own terms.<br/>
Cast: by Gabe Klinger (Director), Gabe Klinger (Screenplay) Cast: Marina Person, Caio Horowicz, John Ortiz<br/>
Durata: 85 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/media/filmstills/2026/plakate-2026/202602856_9_RWD_1920.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Mon Feb 16 21:30 - Urania, Tue Feb 17 10:00 - Cubix 9, Wed Feb 18 13:30 - ADK am Hanseatenweg, Thu Feb 19 13:15 - Cubix 6, Fri Feb 20 22:00 - Cubix 6]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202602856.html</guid></item><item><title>Truly Naked by Muriel d’Ansembourg</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202602884.html</link><description><![CDATA[Alec, a soft-spoken, introverted teenager, has always viewed life through the lens of his father&rsquo;s small-time pornography business where their home doubles as a set. Since his mother&rsquo;s death, Alec has been drawn deeper into the family business and he now films and edits the content that his rough and ready father, Dylan, produces and stars in. As an ageing performer, Dylan is struggling to keep things afloat and relies on girls such as Lizzie, a free-spirited adult entertainer who has become something like an older sister to Alec. As financial pressures mount, Dylan&rsquo;s swagger begins to unravel, exposing Alec to the growing chaos around him. When the father and son relocate from London to a sleepy seaside town, Alec hopes for a fresh start and tries to make new friends without revealing his unconventional life. Events take a turn when he meets classmate Nina, a fiercely independent and feminist young woman whose world view could not be further from the one that Alec grew up with. As their bond deepens, Nina invites Alec into a realm of intimacy and vulnerability that cannot be captured on camera and challenges him to explore what it means to be truly seen.<br/>
Cast: by Muriel d’Ansembourg (Director), Muriel d'Ansembourg (Screenplay) Cast: Caolán O'Gorman, Andrew Howard, Alessa Savage, Safiya Benaddi, Lyndsey Marshal<br/>
Durata: 102 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/media/filmstills/2026/plakate-2026/202602884_9_RWD_1920.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Mon Feb 16 21:30 - Bluemax Theater, Tue Feb 17 18:30 - Cubix 9, Wed Feb 18 13:00 - Cubix 9, Sat Feb 21 19:45 - Colosseum 1, Sun Feb 22 21:30 - Cubix 8]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202602884.html</guid></item><item><title>Ghost School by Seemab Gul</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202603120.html</link><description><![CDATA[Ten-year-old Rabia discovers that the only school in her village has closed. Rumour has it that the school is haunted and the teacher is possessed by a jinn. A fellow pupil brags that he is now going to a boys&rsquo; school in the neighbouring village. Jealous and confused, Rabia goes around asking the adults what is going on, but only receives vague responses. As the rumours about the haunted school take over the village, Rabia increasingly comes to doubt them. She dares the village kids to go into the school and exorcise the jinn. But this leads to devastating consequences. Ultimately, Rabia is left with the choice of either becoming a servant or doing something drastic to be able to go to school again. She decides to make a sacrifice, unleashing magical forces.<br/>
Cast: by Seemab Gul (Director), Seemab Gul (Screenplay) Cast: Nazualiya Arsalan, Samina Seher, Adnan Shah Tipu, Vajdaan Shah, Muhammad Zaman<br/>
Durata: 88 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/media/filmstills/2026/plakate-2026/202603120_9_RWD_1920.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sat Feb 14 15:00 - Cubix 6, Mon Feb 16 10:00 - HKW 1 - Miriam Makeba Auditorium, Tue Feb 17 13:00 - Zoo Palast 2, Wed Feb 18 16:15 - Cubix 6, Fri Feb 20 15:45 - Filmtheater am Friedrichshain, Sun Feb 22 10:00 - Zoo Palast 2]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202603120.html</guid></item><item><title>Siri Hustvedt – Dance Around the Self by Sabine Lidl</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202603166.html</link><description><![CDATA[Young, curious and full of drive, Siri Hustvedt leaves the wide, quiet landscapes of Minnesota and plunges into the pulsating life of New York City. In search of the protagonist for her first novel, she embarks on a journey that not only shapes her as a writer but leads her to become one of the most compelling voices in contemporary American literature. The film opens a perspective that reaches far beyond Siri Hustvedt herself, discovering women who courageously and independently realise their artistic visions. As Siri Hustvedt and her husband Paul Auster reflect on language, identity and the power of words, life intervenes: Paul Auster becomes seriously ill. In <em class="film">Siri Hustvedt &ndash; Dance Around the Self</em>, director Sabine Lidl portrays Siri Hustvedt&rsquo;s distinctive way of living and thinking, weaving her writing together with the major themes of life: love and farewell.<br/>
Cast: by Sabine Lidl (Director), Sabine Lidl (Screenplay) Cast: Siri Hustvedt, Paul Auster, Sophie Auster, Katerina Fotopoulou, Liv Hustvedt, Asti Hustvedt , Ingy Hustvedt , Spencer Ostrander, Wim Wenders , Jules* Elting<br/>
Durata: 110 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/media/filmstills/2026/plakate-2026/202603166_9_RWD_1920.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Fri Feb 13 17:30 - Haus der Berliner Festspiele, Sat Feb 14 15:15 - Urania, Sun Feb 15 10:00 - Cubix 7, Wed Feb 18 12:30 - CinemaxX 7, Sun Feb 22 09:45 - Haus der Berliner Festspiele]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202603166.html</guid></item><item><title>What Will I Become? by Lexie Bean</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202603286.html</link><description><![CDATA[According to the American Academy of Pediatrics, more than half of trans boys attempt suicide. Directors Lexie Bean and Logan Rozos explore the vulnerability of their transmasculine community. They delve into their own personal experiences, intertwining them with the stories of two young trans men who died by suicide. Homecoming king Blake Brockington and soft-spoken Kyler Prescott were poets, musicians and community advocates. The film traces their joys and challenges, their tragic deaths and resulting media attention, as well as the larger aftermath within their communities. The film also uplifts resources that affirm trans boys and the LGBTQIA2S+ community to provide an understanding of suicide-prevention practices. <em class="film">What Will I Become?</em> asks why people from the transmasculine community are particularly vulnerable to living briefly and dying quietly.<br/>
Cast: by Lexie Bean (Director), Logan Rozos (Director)<br/>
Durata: 86 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202603286_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Tue Feb 17 16:00 - HKW 1 - Miriam Makeba Auditorium, Wed Feb 18 10:15 - Zoo Palast 2, Thu Feb 19 15:45 - Filmtheater am Friedrichshain, Fri Feb 20 13:00 - Zoo Palast 2, Sun Feb 22 09:45 - Filmtheater am Friedrichshain]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202603286.html</guid></item><item><title>Mouse by Kelly O’Sullivan</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202603480.html</link><description><![CDATA[The summer of 2002, and the senior year of high school is on the horizon for best friends Minnie and Callie. As the golden child of their North Little Rock High School in Arkansas, Callie is the shining star of their school&rsquo;s drama class. Minnie is her reliable shadow who would much prefer to be prompter than on stage herself. Growing up in Callie&rsquo;s protective orbit means Minnie is a welcome guest at her friend&rsquo;s upper-class home where Callie&rsquo;s elegant mother, Helen, feeds them with delicious food and attention. This is in stark contrast to Minnie&rsquo;s hard-scrabble life outside school where she lives in a cramped, cluttered apartment with her mother, Barbara, a vet who is unable to resist hard-luck cases. When Callie and Minnie&rsquo;s friendship is suddenly upended, Minnie is left rudderless. Facing the challenge of establishing her own identity as the school year begins, she starts to pull away from Barbara and forms a complicated relationship with Helen.<br/>
Cast: by Kelly O'Sullivan (Screenplay) Cast: Sophie Okonedo, Katherine Mallen Kupferer, Chloe Coleman, Tara Mallen, Iman Vellani, David Hyde Pierce<br/>
Durata: 120 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202603480_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Fri Feb 13 18:15 - Zoo Palast 1, Sat Feb 14 10:45 - Haus der Berliner Festspiele, Sun Feb 15 21:30 - Cubix 7, Mon Feb 16 20:00 - Yorck Kino, Wed Feb 18 13:00 - Cubix 6, Sat Feb 21 22:00 - Urania]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202603480.html</guid></item><item><title>Shanghai Daughter by Agnis Shen Zhongmin</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202603531.html</link><description><![CDATA[Ming, a woman from Shanghai, travels alone to a rubber tree plantation in Xishuangbanna on China&rsquo;s southwestern border. Half a century ago, her late father was sent there during the Cultural Revolution&rsquo;s &ldquo;Down to the Countryside Movement&rdquo;. Now, she wants to find someone who once knew him. The old house of the former production team is on the verge of demolition, and a mining company and modern agricultural projects, which have replaced the rubber plantations of the past, are quietly transforming the land. A farm officer, a rural doctor, a Dai elder (from one of the ethnic minorities in southwest China), a rubber tapper, a young ecologist and a mysterious woman who has a special connection with Ming &ndash; they all drift into her journey one after another. Through their respective oral narratives and her own experience of getting lost and searching, something deep in the jungle pulls Ming into a web of layered truths.<br/>
Cast: by Agnis Shen Zhongmin (Director), Agnis Shen Zhongmin (Screenplay) Cast: Liang Cuishan<br/>
Durata: 94 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/media/filmstills/2026/plakate-2026/202603531_9_RWD_1920.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sat Feb 14 17:00 - Cubix 7, Wed Feb 18 19:00 - Zoo Palast 2, Thu Feb 19 21:30 - Cubix 5, Fri Feb 20 16:00 - Cubix 7, Sat Feb 21 16:00 - Deutsche Kinemathek – Halle]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202603531.html</guid></item><item><title>Enjoy Your Stay by Dominik Locher</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202603947.html</link><description><![CDATA[Luz is from the Philippines and has been working for several years without papers as a cleaner in Switzerland. At the start of winter, she is sent along with her friend Aileen and other Filipina women to the luxury ski resort of Verbier. There, she scrubs holiday chalets for Thibault, the manager of a cleaning company. Trapped between the risk of being discovered and deported by the police, and Thibault, who exploits their precarious situation, the women live in the shadows. Just before New Year&rsquo;s Eve, Luz&rsquo;s life is shaken by a Filipino reality TV show. Her ex-husband parades their six-year-old daughter Sofia in front of the cameras and demands full custody. To avoid losing her child after years abroad, Luz promises live on television to return home for Sofia&rsquo;s birthday in February. But one look at her savings makes it clear that she does not have enough money to pay off her debts and secure her daughter&rsquo;s future. Under enormous time pressure, Luz has no choice but to earn more, and quickly, even if that means betraying her community and crossing her own moral boundaries.<br/>
Cast: by Dominik Locher (Director), Dominik Locher (Screenplay) Cast: Mercedes Cabral, Alexis Manenti, Anna Luna, Hasmine Killip<br/>
Durata: 99 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202603947_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sat Feb 14 17:30 - Haus der Berliner Festspiele, Sun Feb 15 15:30 - Urania, Mon Feb 16 22:00 - Cubix 7, Wed Feb 18 10:45 - Colosseum 1, Fri Feb 20 15:30 - Zoo Palast 1, Sat Feb 21 10:00 - Urania]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202603947.html</guid></item><item><title>EIGHT BRIDGES by James Benning</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202603948.html</link><description><![CDATA[&ldquo;It seems to be the time to consider bridges.&rdquo; &ndash; James Benning<br/>
Cast: by James Benning (Director)<br/>
Durata: 82 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202603948_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Wed Feb 18 21:00 - Delphi Filmpalast, Fri Feb 20 10:00 - ADK am Hanseatenweg, Sat Feb 21 21:30 - Cinema Betonhalle@Silent Green]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202603948.html</guid></item><item><title>The Weight by Padraic McKinley</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202604113.html</link><description><![CDATA[Oregon, 1933. Samuel Murphy is torn from his daughter and sent to a brutal work camp. Warden Clancy tempts him with early release if he smuggles gold through the deadly wilderness. How far will Murphy go to see his child again?
 Padraic McKinley&rsquo;s tense, atmospheric Depression-era drama follows a group of desperate convicts on a journey through a physically and morally treacherous backcountry. Set against the stark beauty of the Oregon landscape, <em class="film">The Weight</em> draws on the introspective action cinema of the 1970s to depict a gritty survivalist scenario supported by brothers Latham and Shelby Gaines&rsquo; score and Matteo Cocco&rsquo;s cinematography. Ethan Hawke gives a muscular performance as the film&rsquo;s reluctant but resourceful hero, while Russell Crowe is quietly menacing as his foil. Julia Jones brings dignity and defiance to her role as Anna, the sole woman in the group.<br/>
Cast: by Padraic McKinley (Director), Matthew Booi (Screenplay) Cast: Ethan Hawke, Russell Crowe, Julia Jones, Austin Amelio, Avi Nash<br/>
Durata: 115 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202604113_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Tue Feb 17 21:30 - Zoo Palast 1, Wed Feb 18 22:00 - HKW 1 - Miriam Makeba Auditorium, Thu Feb 19 12:45 - Uber Eats Music Hall, Sat Feb 21 10:00 - ADK am Hanseatenweg]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202604113.html</guid></item><item><title>Douglas Gordon by Douglas Gordon by Finlay Pretsell</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202604430.html</link><description><![CDATA[Douglas Gordon grew up in Glasgow, Scotland during the economically and politically grim era of Margaret Thatcher and is among the most important and influential artists of his generation. He is best known for his large-scale video installations and films such as the Turner Prize winning <em class="film-other">24 Hour Psycho</em>, and <em class="film-other">Zidane: A 21st Century Portrait</em>, which premiered at Cannes. In this unsparingly honest and intimate portrait, which tests the boundaries between reality and performance, the artist bares his soul and innermost thoughts whilst making new work. In spontaneous acts and conversations, he reflects on his advancing years. As the filmmaker-subject relationship shifts from collaborative intimacy to a more complex dynamic, the question increasingly arises: Who actually is making this film? This multifaceted portrait bears witness to the fact that Douglas Gordon is ready to sacrifice everything for his art.<br/>
Cast: by Finlay Pretsell (Director) Cast: Douglas Gordon<br/>
Durata: 88 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/media/filmstills/2026/plakate-2026/202604430_9_RWD_1920.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Tue Feb 17 17:30 - Haus der Berliner Festspiele, Wed Feb 18 15:30 - Urania, Thu Feb 19 10:15 - Cubix 7, Fri Feb 20 10:45 - Colosseum 1, Sat Feb 21 20:15 - Cubix 7]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202604430.html</guid></item><item><title>Etwas ganz Besonderes by Eva Trobisch</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202604668.html</link><description><![CDATA[Lea is auditioning for a TV talent show. The producer asks her: &ldquo;Who are you and what defines you?&rdquo;. Lea has no answer. And thus begins a search for her identity. Meanwhile in her hometown, the museum is being lavishly renovated with EU money but her family&rsquo;s B&amp;B is struggling to stay afloat. Lea&rsquo;s parents Matze and Rieke are freshly separated because Rieke is expecting another man&rsquo;s child and they are still struggling to get used to the new family set up. Her grandparents are also beset by problems, both with each other and with their forest hotel which, in this region badly lacking in tourists, is eating up more money than it makes. Her aunt Kati is a role model of independence for Lea, but, as head of the museum, she is making few friends in this small provincial town. Lea&rsquo;s best friend Bonny is on a different planet since she fell in love with Lea&rsquo;s cousin, the activist Edgar. And therein lies the complexity of the question: Who is Lea and who does she want to be? What home story can be spun from her family&rsquo;s history?<br/>
Cast: by Eva Trobisch (Director), Eva Trobisch (Screenplay) Cast: Frida Hornemann, Max Riemelt, Eva Löbau, Gina Henkel, Rahel Ohm, Peter René Lüdecke, Florian Geißelmann, Yvon Sable Moltzen, Ida Fischer, Florian Lukas, Thomas Schubert, Kara Schröder, Anne Kulbatzki, Nairi Hadodo<br/>
Durata: 116 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202604668_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Wed Feb 18 18:15 - Berlinale Palast, Thu Feb 19 12:30 - Zoo Palast 1, Fri Feb 20 20:00 - Kino Casablanca, Fri Feb 20 21:45 - Uber Eats Music Hall, Sat Feb 21 15:00 - Haus der Berliner Festspiele]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202604668.html</guid></item><item><title>Roya by Mahnaz Mohammadi</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202604675.html</link><description><![CDATA[Roya, an Iranian teacher imprisoned in Tehran&rsquo;s Evin Prison for her political beliefs, is faced with a choice: make a forced televised confession or remain confined to her three-square-metre cell. As past and present slip out of sequence and exchange places, she moves between inner landscapes and lived experience. The film reveals how solitary confinement reshapes both perception and identity and makes the possibility of resistance increasingly fragile.<br/>
Cast: by Mahnaz Mohammadi (Director), Mahnaz Mohammadi (Screenplay) Cast: Melisa Sözen, Maryam Palizban, Hamidreza Djavdan, Mohammad Ali Hosseinalipour, Bacho Meburishvili, Gholamhassan Taseiri<br/>
Durata: 92 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202604675_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sat Feb 14 10:50 - Cubix 7, Wed Feb 18 21:30 - Urania, Thu Feb 19 10:00 - Cubix 9, Fri Feb 20 19:00 - Cubix 7, Sat Feb 21 10:15 - Colosseum 1, Sun Feb 22 10:00 - Cubix 9]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202604675.html</guid></item><item><title>Bucks Harbor by Pete Muller</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202604750.html</link><description><![CDATA[Downeast Maine is a narrow stretch of rugged coastline chiselled between the forest and the sea. Here, boys are shaped by the brutal winters, their harvesting of the ocean&rsquo;s bounty and the rigid codes of their fathers. <em class="film">Bucks Harbor</em> explores the inner lives of these fishermen, young and old, and the emotional complexity of growing up in a community where a man&rsquo;s worth is often defined by the strength of his back. The lobsters they hunt, deep on the ocean floor, serve as a metaphor for the adversity, survival and guarded vulnerability on land.<br/>
Cast: by Pete Muller (Director)<br/>
Durata: 98 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202604750_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sat Feb 14 13:00 - Bluemax Theater, Sun Feb 15 22:00 - Cubix 6, Tue Feb 17 17:00 - BALI KINO, Wed Feb 18 15:45 - Filmtheater am Friedrichshain, Fri Feb 20 10:00 - Cubix 9, Sun Feb 22 18:15 - Cubix 7]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202604750.html</guid></item><item><title>Where To? by Assaf Machnes</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202604888.html</link><description><![CDATA[In the endless Berlin nights, Hassan, a 55-year-old Palestinian Uber driver, shuttles night owls from one party to the next. Estranged from his eldest daughter, who is determined to marry her German boyfriend, Hassan often finds himself driving the streets without any sense of purpose. One night, Amir, a 25-year-old Israeli tourist who is exploring his sexual identity far away from home, stumbles into Hassan&rsquo;s cab. Months later, Amir makes a reappearance. He is now living in Berlin and suffering from heartbreak after the tortuous end of a love affair. As their rides together recur across two years, Hassan begins to recognise echoes of his own buried pain in Amir&rsquo;s struggles. Eventually, their late-night journeys help Hassan to confront his own past &ndash; including the events that led him to leaving his homeland 30 years ago.<br/>
Cast: by Assaf Machnes (Director), Assaf Machnes (Screenplay) Cast: Ehab Salami, Ido Tako, Milan Peschel, Rama Nasrallah, Raheeq Haj Yahia-Suleiman, Dov Navon, Sarit Vino Elad, Enzo Brumm<br/>
Durata: 95 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202604888_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Tue Feb 17 19:00 - Bluemax Theater, Wed Feb 18 16:00 - Cubix 9, Thu Feb 19 22:15 - Cubix 8, Sat Feb 21 12:45 - Colosseum 1, Sun Feb 22 12:15 - Cubix 9]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202604888.html</guid></item><item><title>Barbara Forever by Brydie O&apos;Connor</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202604921.html</link><description><![CDATA[Queer cinema pioneer Barbara Hammer (1939&ndash;2019) started making films at the age of 27, coming out as a lesbian in her early 30s: &ldquo;My life has been lived in film.&rdquo; The sheer wealth of film material of her life also forms the basis for <em class="film">Barbara Forever</em>, Brydie O&rsquo;Connor&rsquo;s debut feature which achieves the mammoth task of doing justice to her dazzling and charismatic personality: a pioneer of lesbian and queer self-representation &ldquo;in a world where we are invisible&rdquo;, a seductive lover &ndash; and a both experimental and daring filmmaker. Above all this: a lust for life. Through her films, which include <em class="film-other">Dyketactics</em> (1974), <em class="film-other">Audience</em> (1982) and <em class="film-other">Nitrate Kisses</em> (1992), hitherto unseen archive material, Barbara&rsquo;s narrative voice &ndash; and with her life partner Florrie Burke as another focal point &ndash; the temporality of life itself is queered: lots of sex and intimacy, the theory of the cinema of touch, the desire for artistic recognition, her relationship with her mother in an immigrant family and the mission to pass on and share what film does best, not least in view of her illness and dying. Fans, newcomers and returning viewers alike: allow yourselves to be touched by this Dyke Poetry!<br/>
Cast: by Brydie O'Connor (Director) Cast: Barbara Hammer<br/>
Durata: 102 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202604921_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sun Feb 15 17:30 - Cinema Paris, Wed Feb 18 14:00 - Xenon Kino, Thu Feb 19 14:30 - Delphi Filmpalast]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202604921.html</guid></item><item><title>Rumaragasa by Ryan Machado</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202604970.html</link><description><![CDATA[The lush but troubled landscape of mid-1990s Sibuyan Island in the Philippines. Eli is a reserved young man carrying the weight of a trauma that his community refuses to acknowledge. After surviving a sexual assault by a peer, an event dismissed by local authorities and friends as nothing more than rough play, he retreats into a world of silence and isolation. When he witnesses a mysterious plane crash in the island&rsquo;s densely forested mountains, his attempt to alert others is met with the same incredulity that greeted his earlier disclosure. In his solitude, Eli clings to fragments of sound and memory &ndash; often via the cassette tapes he carries with him &ndash; as he searches for some means of expression and truth. As the film unfolds, the personal and the communal collide: Eli&rsquo;s internal unravelling mirrors the larger spectre of the environmental exploitation that is threatening his hometown. What begins as a quiet examination of one individual&rsquo;s anguish evolves into a parable about how silence and denial can corrode both human lives and the natural world that sustains them.<br/>
Cast: by Ryan Machado (Director), Ryan Machado (Screenplay) Cast: Elijah Canlas, Ron Angeles, Reynald Raissel Santos, Glenn Sevilla Mas, Rodney Galicha, Nathan Sotto<br/>
Durata: 87 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/media/filmstills/2026/plakate-2026/202604970_9_ORG.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Tue Feb 17 15:30 - Zoo Palast 1, Wed Feb 18 21:30 - Cubix 9, Thu Feb 19 13:00 - Cubix 7, Fri Feb 20 21:45 - Filmtheater am Friedrichshain, Sat Feb 21 17:30 - Cubix 9]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202604970.html</guid></item><item><title>Hangar rojo by Juan Pablo Sallato</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202605144.html</link><description><![CDATA[Santiago, Chile, September 11, 1973. As the military coup unfolds across the country, Captain Jorge Silva &ndash; the former head of Air Force Intelligence &ndash; receives an order that will change his life forever: he is to transform the Air Force Academy where he currently trains young cadets into a centre for detention and torture. Convinced that the horror will be short lived, Silva tries to stay on the sidelines. But the arrival of Colonel Jahn &ndash; an old rival who is returning with unchecked power and unfinished business &ndash; forces Silva to confront not only his past but also his deepest beliefs. As trucks begin to fill the hangar with prisoners and the exercise of power grows increasingly ruthless, Silva finds himself trapped at an impossible crossroads: disobedience could cost him his life, but then so could obedience, too. Inspired by true events and shot in black and white, <em class="film">Hangar rojo</em> is the first Latin American thriller to explore the inner workings of the military during the dictatorships of the 1970s. A restrained, intimate and deeply political story about men ensnared in the machinery of power at the precise moment that history forces them to choose sides.<br/>
Cast: by Juan Pablo Sallato (Director), Luis Emilio Guzmán (Screenplay) Cast: Nicolás Zárate, Boris Quercia, Marcial Tagle, Catalina Stuardo, Aron Hernández, Francisco Carrasco, Juan Cano<br/>
Durata: 81 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/media/filmstills/2026/plakate-2026/202605144_9_RWD_1920.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Fri Feb 13 15:30 - Bluemax Theater, Sat Feb 14 13:00 - Cubix 9, Sun Feb 15 19:15 - Cubix 8, Mon Feb 16 16:00 - Colosseum 1, Wed Feb 18 17:00 - Xenon Kino]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202605144.html</guid></item><item><title>Forêt Ivre by Manon Coubia</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202605344.html</link><description><![CDATA[In the northern Alps, Anne, H&eacute;l&egrave;ne and Suzanne take turns looking after a mountain hut. Through the seasons, hikers come and go; stories bloom and fade, leaving each of them facing the silence.&nbsp;<em class="film">For&ecirc;t Ivre</em>&nbsp;tells the story of three women who have made the choice to withdraw from the world down in the valley. Each of them harbours a secret; and each of them is put to the test by their chosen solitude.<br/>
Cast: by Manon Coubia (Director), Manon Coubia (Screenplay) Cast: Salomé Richard, Aurélia Petit, Anne Coesens, Arthur Marbaix, Yoann Zimmer<br/>
Durata: 102 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202605344_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Mon Feb 16 16:00 - Bluemax Theater, Tue Feb 17 13:00 - Cubix 9, Wed Feb 18 19:30 - Cubix 8, Thu Feb 19 19:00 - Bluemax Theater, Fri Feb 20 16:00 - Colosseum 1]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202605344.html</guid></item><item><title>Árru by Elle Sofe Sara</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202605447.html</link><description><![CDATA[Amid the breathtaking landscapes of S&aacute;pmi, Sami reindeer herder Maia fights to protect her ancestral lands from a looming mining project. As protests increase, she turns to her uncle Lemme for help, but his presence reignites deep-buried familial traumas. Maia must choose: save the land at the cost of her family, or surrender it to break the silence.<br/>
Cast: by Elle Sofe Sara (Director), Johan Fasting (Screenplay) Cast: Sara Marielle Gaup Beaska, Simon Issát Marainen, Ayla Gáren Nutti, Mikkel Gaup<br/>
Durata: 95 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202605447_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Mon Feb 16 15:15 - Zoo Palast 1, Tue Feb 17 21:30 - Cubix 9, Wed Feb 18 13:00 - Cubix 7, Thu Feb 19 21:45 - Filmtheater am Friedrichshain, Fri Feb 20 12:15 - Cubix 9, Sun Feb 22 22:15 - Urania]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202605447.html</guid></item><item><title>Who Killed Alex Odeh? by Jason Osder</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202605733.html</link><description><![CDATA[In October 1985, Santa Ana, California was shaken by a brazen act of political violence: Palestinian American Alex Odeh, a beloved teacher and community leader, was killed by a tripwire bomb planted in his office. Despite having identified suspects, the police made no arrests and the case went cold. <em class="film">Who Killed Alex Odeh?</em> reopens the mystery, tracking the work of an Israeli journalist who, decades later, takes up the investigation. New leads emerge, long-buried records come to light and the forces behind a political assassination are finally uncovered. The case exposes a trail of unanswered questions that have international implications.<br/>
Cast: by Jason Osder (Director), William Lafi Youmans (Director)<br/>
Durata: 82 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202605733_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Tue Feb 17 14:00 - Haus der Berliner Festspiele, Wed Feb 18 16:30 - ADK am Hanseatenweg, Fri Feb 20 16:00 - ADK am Hanseatenweg, Sat Feb 21 22:00 - Colosseum 1]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202605733.html</guid></item><item><title>Panelstory, aneb jak se rodí sídliště by Věra Chytilová</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202605881.html</link><description><![CDATA[Life is a construction site for the tenants of the only partially finished prefab housing development in Prague. Between the buildings, young mothers struggle to push their prams through mounds of mud. And things are not any better inside. Here, a corpulent man is stuck because the door will not open; there, no water comes out of the taps, but a conversation in the neighbouring apartment can be heard clear as day through the pipes. And there is no way out of the boiler room because the door has no handle &hellip;
 Věra Chytilov&aacute;&rsquo;s film depicts one day in that construction chaos through the eyes of a handful of people of various ages who have to deal with the hodgepodge of permanently makeshift solutions in what was conceived as a &ldquo;garden city&rdquo;. In 2002, the director said: &ldquo;It&rsquo;s not a critical reaction to the regime; it&rsquo;s more actually a view of human behaviour.&rdquo; Nonetheless, her amusing social satire was held back by the authorities and not shown in Czechoslovakia until 1981.&nbsp;The digitisation was undertaken from the original picture negative and sound held at the N&aacute;rodn&iacute; filmov&yacute; archiv in Prague.<br/>
Cast: by Věra Chytilová (Director), Eva Kačírková (Screenplay) Cast: Lukáš Bech, Antonín Vaňha, Eva Kačírková, Oldřich Navrátil, Jiří Kodet, Bronislav Poloczek, Daniela Šrajerová, Milan Klásek, Ladislav Potměšil, Hana Hejduková<br/>
Durata: 100 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202605881_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Tue Feb 17 19:00 - ADK am Hanseatenweg, Wed Feb 18 11:15 - Cubix 5, Sun Feb 22 15:15 - Cubix 5]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202605881.html</guid></item><item><title>Wolfram by Warwick Thornton</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202606004.html</link><description><![CDATA[On the colonial frontier of 1930s Australia, two swaggering outlaws roll into a mining town and unleash a wave of cruelty, leading two siblings to break free from their white masters who have forced them to work as child labourers in the mines. The children escape and set off across the desert &ldquo;sweet country&rdquo; of central Australia, in search of safety and a way home. Set in the same universe as Thornton&rsquo;s multi award-winning film <em class="film-other">Sweet Country</em> from 2017, <em class="film">Wolfram</em> features standout performances from Deborah Mailman and its young actors, playing siblings who must rely on each other as they search for the truth about themselves and their family, escape a nightmare and make unexpected connections on their way to freedom. An outback Western but also a historical drama about survival, reckoning, resilience and love.<br/>
Cast: by Warwick Thornton (Director), Steven McGregor (Screenplay) Cast: Deborah Mailman, Erroll Shand, Joe Bird, Thomas M Wright, Ferdinand Hoang<br/>
Durata: 102 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202606004_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Tue Feb 17 15:15 - Berlinale Palast, Wed Feb 18 10:00 - Urania, Wed Feb 18 22:15 - Uber Eats Music Hall, Sat Feb 21 17:45 - Haus der Berliner Festspiele, Sun Feb 22 20:00 - Urania]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202606004.html</guid></item><item><title>Take Me Home by Liz Sargent</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202606137.html</link><description><![CDATA[Anna, a 38-year-old Korean woman with a cognitive disability, cares for her ageing adoptive parents in a fragile balance of meeting each other&rsquo;s needs. When a Florida heatwave shatters both the family&rsquo;s and Anna&rsquo;s routines, her future looks uncertain &ndash; until she manages to create a world in which she can thrive.
 ​Liz Sargent&rsquo;s intimate debut drama examines the shifting demands placed on a uniquely vulnerable family in a Florida suburb. The film exposes the indignities of the American healthcare system and the structural challenges faced by disabled people and their families. It also gently and imaginatively traces Anna&rsquo;s path to finding independence and a connection to a community of chosen family. By turns quietly devastating and bracingly optimistic,&nbsp;<em class="film">Take Me Home</em>&nbsp;confronts us with an impossible situation, while holding out hope for Anna&rsquo;s future.<br/>
Cast: by Liz Sargent (Director), Liz Sargent (Screenplay) Cast: Anna Sargent, Victor Slezak, Ali Ahn, Marceline Hugot, Shane Harper<br/>
Durata: 91 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/media/filmstills/2026/plakate-2026/202606137_9_RWD_1920.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Tue Feb 17 16:00 - Bluemax Theater, Wed Feb 18 18:45 - Cubix 9, Thu Feb 19 19:30 - Cubix 8, Sat Feb 21 15:00 - Colosseum 1, Sun Feb 22 22:00 - Colosseum 1]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202606137.html</guid></item><item><title>Piedras preciosas by Simón Vélez</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202606145.html</link><description><![CDATA[Young Colombian immigrant Machado has a job harvesting grapes in the French countryside. He also seems to have a criminal past, as a female gangster boss hires him to steal a valuable emerald &ndash; dressed up as a priest &ndash; from a famous church close to Medell&iacute;n. Yet this supposedly watertight plan quickly goes awry ... Images and moments, woven together with fine threads: amusingly and with considerable lightness of touch, director Sim&oacute;n V&eacute;lez gets to grips with and reconfigures the gangster film genre. The plot is characterised by original dramatic paths rather than a classical linear narration: pared down in terms of action and dialogue, unfolding at unique locations that do not just frame the plot but enter into a congenial unity with the characters. The striking camerawork carries out expeditions through Colombia&rsquo;s multifaceted flora &ndash; at once shimmering and shining, just like the object of desire. Imposing colour compositions, energetic dances, cool costume design: <em class="film">Piedras preciosas</em> is a feature debut that elegantly eschews Colombian stereotypes, relates to colonial history and cultivates a timeless pop aesthetic.<br/>
Cast: by Simón Vélez (Director), Paulo Carneiro (Screenplay) Cast: Juan Lugo, Laura Taurines, Sofía Jaramillo, Yira Plaza, Daniel Cortés, Chiara Spolaor<br/>
Durata: 70 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202606145_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Tue Feb 17 21:00 - Cinema Paris, Wed Feb 18 14:00 - Cubix 8, Fri Feb 20 16:00 - Bluemax Theater, Sat Feb 21 20:00 - Zoo Palast 2]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202606145.html</guid></item><item><title>Ravalear by Isaki Lacuesta</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202606276.html</link><description><![CDATA[&ldquo;Can Mosques&rdquo;&nbsp;is a hundred-year-old family-run restaurant in Barcelona&rsquo;s El Raval district, adored and respected by everyone. But, after falling into the hands of an investment fund whose aim is to empty the building and accelerate the transformation of the neighbourhood, it is now facing eviction. The news plunges the family into deep despair. When they decide to stand up for themselves with the help of their neighbours, the fight quickly spirals out of control and becomes increasingly dangerous. In order to save Can Mosques, they will have to cross lines they never thought themselves capable of crossing and ask themselves just how far they are prepared to go to secure the restaurant&rsquo;s survival.<br/>
Cast: by Isabel Campo (Screenplay) Cast: Enric Auquer Sardà, María Rodríguez Soto, Sergi López, Quim Ávila, Francesc Orella<br/>
Durata: 95 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202606276_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Tue Feb 17 19:00 - Zoo Palast 2, Wed Feb 18 10:00 - Bluemax Theater, Fri Feb 20 19:15 - Cubix 8, Sun Feb 22 12:00 - ADK am Hanseatenweg]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202606276.html</guid></item><item><title>Nina Roza by Geneviève Dulude-de Celles</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202606549.html</link><description><![CDATA[Mihail left Bulgaria in the 1990s after the death of his wife and raised his young daughter, Roza, alone in Montreal. Far from his homeland, he established himself as a specialist in French and contemporary art. Now, he is commissioned by a collector to authenticate the work of an eight-year-old girl, Nina, who is living in a Bulgarian village and whose paintings have gone viral online. Mihail hesitates but eventually agrees to undertake the journey. Meeting Nina shakes him deeply. The disarmingly mature child reminds him of Roza at the same age. During his stay in Bulgaria, he gradually makes his peace with the ghosts of his past while trying to unravel the mystery behind Nina: is she truly the author of her work? Has someone helped her? What gives him the right to disrupt her happy life? Somewhere between the past and the present, the tangible and the symbolic, Mihail&rsquo;s journey becomes a cathartic one which highlights the intricate relationships between life, art and human beings. Sometimes, the journey matters more than the destination.<br/>
Cast: by Geneviève Dulude-de Celles (Director), Geneviève Dulude-de Celles (Screenplay) Cast: Galin Stoev, Ekaterina Stanina, Sofia Stanina, Chiara Caselli, Michelle Tzontchev, Christian Bégin, Nikolay Mutafchiev<br/>
Durata: 103 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202606549_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Mon Feb 16 21:45 - Berlinale Palast, Tue Feb 17 13:00 - Uber Eats Music Hall, Wed Feb 18 18:45 - Haus der Berliner Festspiele, Fri Feb 20 10:00 - HKW 1 - Miriam Makeba Auditorium, Sun Feb 22 16:00 - Berlinale Palast]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202606549.html</guid></item><item><title>Papaya by Priscilla Kellen</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202606578.html</link><description><![CDATA[Passionate about the idea of flying, Papaya is a tiny seed in a world governed by laws of nature with sprinkles of fantasy. She struggles to conform to expectations because her curiosity and an uncontrollable desire for freedom make her different from other seeds. When she realises that her destiny is to become a tree, she rebels. Fighting against her own nature, Papaya tries to stay in constant motion to avoid rooting. On her journey away from the mother tree, she learns a great deal about the creatures of the forest. But even Papaya must eventually take root &ndash; on the median strip of a highway, of all places. There she discovers the power within her, triggers a revolution and transforms her environment. Papaya&rsquo;s emotional development is accompanied by a moving soundtrack as she learns that the world is shaped by ancestral wisdom. As her dream comes true, albeit in an unexpected way, the film imaginatively tells a story of resistance and of coming to terms with change.<br/>
Cast: by Priscilla Kellen (Director), Priscilla Kellen (Screenplay)<br/>
Durata: 74 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202606578_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sun Feb 15 09:30 - Zoo Palast 1, Mon Feb 16 16:00 - Filmtheater am Friedrichshain, Tue Feb 17 13:15 - Cubix 6, Wed Feb 18 09:45 - Filmtheater am Friedrichshain, Fri Feb 20 14:00 - Kino Casablanca, Sun Feb 22 16:00 - HKW 1 - Miriam Makeba Auditorium]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202606578.html</guid></item><item><title>Two Mountains Weighing Down My Chest by Viv Li</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202606587.html</link><description><![CDATA[Viv, a Chinese wannabe artist, found herself stuck in Berlin after the pandemic and accidentally ventured into the city&rsquo;s vibrant alternative culture scene. Drifting between new environments and traditional expectations, Viv is constantly adapting to shifting opinions about herself, the world and, of course, China, only to feel more lost than ever. <em class="film">Two Mountains Weighing Down My Chest</em> follows Viv&rsquo;s eclectic encounters and the nuanced culture clashes that shape them. Told in a deeply personal and humorous voice, the film takes a witty yet sharp look at the quest for a sense of belonging in a globalised world and how different societies define our lives. ' A story of the perpetual search for oneself, identity and acceptance, woven into a spiral of surreal yet tangible moments.<br/>
Cast: by Viv Li (Director), Viv Li (Screenplay) Cast: Viv Li<br/>
Durata: 85 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/media/filmstills/2026/plakate-2026/202606587_9_RWD_1920.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Fri Feb 13 21:30 - Zoo Palast 2, Sat Feb 14 22:00 - Cubix 7, Sun Feb 15 13:15 - Cubix 7, Tue Feb 17 16:00 - Cubix 7, Wed Feb 18 22:00 - Cubix 6, Sat Feb 21 18:00 - Zoo Palast 2]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202606587.html</guid></item><item><title>Joy Boy: A Tribute to Julius Eastman by Mawena Yehouessi</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202606712.html</link><description><![CDATA[An homage to Julius Eastman (1940&ndash;1980), African American pianist, composer, homosexual &ndash; legendary for his voice and his stage presence, who died in poverty. In 1979, he wrote &ldquo;Evil Nigger&rdquo; and &ldquo;Gay Guerrilla&rdquo; for piano quartet. <em class="film">Joy Boy</em> is a concert performance alternating between his music and archival recordings &ndash; visualised by a trans-national, six-headed collective in four chapters. Music and images autonomous. The compositions show his skill, the texts his attitude. Inflamed by colonial and life history, raw, radical and crystal clear, he downright hurls the words out (including the N-word &ndash; beyond all possible, necessary trigger warnings), spews them out, becomes thoughtful, quiet. Coming from a wide spectrum of theoretical and artistic practices &ndash; film, performance, dance; textile, archive, research &ndash; the directors partake in a complex collaboration, independent and collective, in solidarity with Eastman and each other. A film that packs a political punch and is beautiful to boot, especially the contact of bodies, colours and rhythms, and the choreography of the Gay Guerrilla along the highway, taking up space, threatening, vulnerable, strong.<br/>
Cast: by Mawena Yehouessi (Director), Fallon Mayanja (Director), Rob Jacobs (Director), Victoire Karera Kampire (Director), Paul Shemisi (Director), Anne Reijniers (Director)<br/>
Durata: 64 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/media/filmstills/2026/plakate-2026/202606712_9_ORG.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sat Feb 14 14:30 - Cinema Paris, Sun Feb 15 13:30 - Cubix 8, Tue Feb 17 22:00 - Bluemax Theater, Wed Feb 18 15:00 - CinemaxX 6]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202606712.html</guid></item><item><title>Members of the Problematic Family by R Gowtham</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202606749.html</link><description><![CDATA[Prabha, a troubled and troublesome young man, has died under mysterious circumstances. Stunned and emotionally numb, Prabha&rsquo;s mother Santhi, paternal uncle Sellam, cousins Dinesh and Mugil, and other members of the extended family go through the motions, preparing for a 16-day-long funeral that culminates in a feast. Who was Prabha? What does his loss mean to his community? Raw, unflinching and throbbing with abrasive energy, Gowtham&rsquo;s bracing fictional debut weaves through a dozen characters who embody different ways of grappling with a violent breach in the social fabric. Their frenetic activity, hot-headed exchanges and delayed reflections together paint an expansive, at times absurd portrait of human nature. With an anthropologist&rsquo;s eye, the filmmaker traces the complexities of bereavement, examining the ways in which grief manifests in the most unexpected moments and objects. Embracing men and women as they are, with their mad outpourings, sordid habits, abusive love, misplaced pride and casual cruelty, <em class="film">Members of the Problematic Family</em> is a work of deep and uncompromising humanism.<br/>
Cast: by R Gowtham (Director), R Gowtham (Screenplay) Cast: Karuththadayan, A.ra. Ajith Kumar, Uvesri, Kanchana Senthil, Saravana Siddharth, TPS aka T Panneerselvam, Aswine, Hari Krishnan, Thaen Iniyan, Thiyagu Kallu, Vijay Sooran<br/>
Durata: 105 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/media/filmstills/2026/plakate-2026/202606749_9_RWD_1920.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Wed Feb 18 20:00 - Cinema Paris, Fri Feb 20 15:00 - Delphi Filmpalast, Sun Feb 22 14:30 - Cinema Betonhalle@Silent Green]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202606749.html</guid></item><item><title>River Dreams by Kristina Mikhailova</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202607108.html</link><description><![CDATA[A &ldquo;Heimatfilm&rdquo; with a difference: Kristina Mikhailova asks women and girls to imagine themselves as a river. Village girls, young female city dwellers, LGBT and gender positivity activists, a headmistress singing the praises of gender-conformist education, women in prison, students with dreams of emigrating, as well as recurring conversations of toxic masculinity, sexual assault and, finally, the trial of a former economics minister widely reported on in Kazakhstan who brutally murdered his wife, Saltanat Nukenova. But on the banks of the unassuming river Aksay, the &ldquo;river girls&rdquo; also talk of their desires, dreams and utopias. A brave act, since the interviews take place against the backdrop of a gender-conservativism that is often hard to imagine. The thus emerging panorama of female life plans, including the opportunities to realise these in Kazakhstan, combines into poetry through the guiding metaphor of the river. With radical tenderness and almost sociological rigour, feminist demos and the art of active listening give rise to political scenes marked by sisterhood and solidarity.<br/>
Cast: by Kristina Mikhailova (Director), Kristina Mikhailova (Screenplay) Cast: Alexandra Cherezova, Dana Ageleuova, Mira Ungarova, Aiya Kuzenbayeva, Juliya Jenis, Kristina Mikhailova, Dariya Temirhan, Tamara Yelantseva, Yakha Alieva, Akzel Beisembay, Inzhu Abeu, Gulnaz Moldakhmet, Sandugash Manapova<br/>
Durata: 98 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/media/filmstills/2026/plakate-2026/202607108_9_ORG.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Wed Feb 18 13:00 - Zoo Palast 2, Thu Feb 19 21:00 - Delphi Filmpalast]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202607108.html</guid></item><item><title>Ich verstehe Ihren Unmut by Kilian Armando Friedrich</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202607173.html</link><description><![CDATA[Heike (59) works as a customer service manager at a cleaning company, mediating daily between clients, company management and cleaning staff. Her firm is having problems with an important subcontractor because Heike tried to poach one of his unofficial workers, contrary to regulations. The subcontractor is now threatening to stop his support unless Heike secures more hours and revenue for him. To meet his demands, she must dismiss one of her own employees&nbsp;&ndash; a colleague who is highly valued by her friend, Taja. Heike finds herself increasingly caught between her responsibility for her own employees and the conditions of the low-wage sector.<br/>
Cast: by Kilian Armando Friedrich (Director), Kilian Armando Friedrich (Screenplay) Cast: Sabine Thalau, Nada Kosturin, Werner Posselt, Sadibou Diabang, Nigyar Velagic<br/>
Durata: 93 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/media/filmstills/2026/plakate-2026/202607173_9_RWD_1920.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Fri Feb 13 16:15 - Zoo Palast 2, Sat Feb 14 19:15 - Cubix 7, Mon Feb 16 15:30 - Urania, Tue Feb 17 10:45 - Colosseum 1, Wed Feb 18 12:45 - CinemaxX 5, Wed Feb 18 12:45 - CinemaxX 6, Fri Feb 20 09:45 - Haus der Berliner Festspiele]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202607173.html</guid></item><item><title>En Route To by Yoo Jaein</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202607204.html</link><description><![CDATA[A seemingly typical day unfolds at an all-girls&rsquo; boarding school in the countryside. When form teacher Jong-sung fails to turn up for class, most of the pupils remain indifferent &ndash; only the pregnant Yun-ji, a quiet outsider, is increasingly filled with unease. The situation escalates when Jong-sung&rsquo;s angry wife storms into the classroom. Driven to desperation, Yun-ji leaves the school premises to buy illegal abortion pills. In order to pay for them, she has plundered the savings of her sharp and outgoing roommate, Kyung-sun, who has been putting the money aside from her underground liquid vape business to finance a year abroad in Australia. When Kyung-sun discovers the theft, she embarks on a search for Yun-ji which leads her to uncover a shocking truth. A story about the abuse of power and the right over one&rsquo;s own body, about love and responsibility, society and community.<br/>
Cast: by Yoo Jaein (Director), Yoo Jaein (Screenplay) Cast: Sim Subin, Lee Jiwon, Jang Sun<br/>
Durata: 106 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/media/filmstills/2026/plakate-2026/202607204_9_RWD_1920.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Wed Feb 18 19:00 - HKW 1 - Miriam Makeba Auditorium, Thu Feb 19 12:30 - HKW 1 - Miriam Makeba Auditorium, Fri Feb 20 10:15 - Cubix 6, Sat Feb 21 12:45 - Filmtheater am Friedrichshain, Sun Feb 22 19:00 - Cubix 6]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202607204.html</guid></item><item><title>Lady by Olive Nwosu</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202607364.html</link><description><![CDATA[In the restless night of Lagos, one of the city&rsquo;s few female cab drivers, Lady, survives by staying tough and focused. She dreams of escape, saving her earnings for a new life far from the chaos of this Nigerian metropolis. But when her long-lost childhood friend, Pinky &ndash; now a sex worker &ndash; returns with a burst of colour and trouble, Lady is pulled reluctantly into her orbit. Soon, she is driving a crew of glamorous, reckless, fun-loving women through the underbelly of Lagos nightlife. What begins as judgement develops into unexpected sisterhood: wild, tender and disarming. As Lady becomes entangled in their world, the nights grow more dangerous, and the city presses harder against old wounds that she has never confronted. Forced to face the trauma she has long outrun, Lady cracks open &ndash; learning to feel, to belong, to see herself through new eyes. When everything reaches breaking point, Lady must make a choice that will change her life&rsquo;s direction forever. In that choice lies a new kind of freedom: one rooted not in escape, but in transformation.<br/>
Cast: by Olive Nwosu (Director), Olive Nwosu (Screenplay) Cast: Jessica Gabriel's Ujah, Amanda Oruh, Tinuade Jemisey, Agu Ghineye Esthyraph, Precious Agu Eke, Fadesaye Olateru-Olabegi, Eva Ibiam, Seun Kuti, Bucci Franklin<br/>
Durata: 93 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202607364_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sat Feb 14 12:50 - Cubix 7, Wed Feb 18 15:30 - Zoo Palast 1, Thu Feb 19 21:30 - Cubix 9, Fri Feb 20 13:15 - Cubix 7, Sat Feb 21 21:45 - Filmtheater am Friedrichshain]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202607364.html</guid></item><item><title>Kryshtalevyi Palats by Hryhori Hrycher</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202607486.html</link><description><![CDATA[In a totalitarian state, pacifist artist Martin Bruno is commissioned to sculpt a statue of Christ for the city&rsquo;s cathedral. When it is unveiled, a scandal erupts. An indignant official destroys the sculpture and accuses Bruno of communist provocation. When the artist goes to explain himself, he discovers the dead body of the official in his office. Bruno is arrested. He is threatened with the death penalty.
 As one of the first Ukrainian sound films, <em class="film">Crystal Palace</em> was influenced by German expressionist film and the avant-garde movement at home. Shortly after its premiere, the film was withdrawn from circulation.&nbsp;The restoration was undertaken from a digital scan of the film held by Amherst College and concentrated on removing scratches and dirt, as well as frame stabilisation and jitter correction. Small imperfections common to old 35mm films were digitally corrected. The original grain and texture of the film were preserved in order to lend the restoration authenticity.<br/>
Cast: by Hryhori Hrycher (Director), Leo Mur (Screenplay) Cast: Irina Volodko, Stepan Shahaida, Gavriil Terekhov, Pavlo Kyiansky, Terenti Yura, M. Hermanovych, Yakiv Vurmansky, Yevhen Kokhanenko, Hryhori Hrycher, Semen Hrabin<br/>
Durata: 89 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202607486_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sat Feb 14 11:00 - ADK am Hanseatenweg, Sun Feb 15 13:00 - Cubix 5, Wed Feb 18 21:30 - Cubix 5]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202607486.html</guid></item><item><title>Im Umkreis des Paradieses by Yulia Lokshina</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202608231.html</link><description><![CDATA[In one of the poorest regions of Paraguay lies Caazap&aacute;, the &ldquo;city of magic and legends&rdquo;. Here, two young Paraguayan students are searching for happiness, gold and a magic bird. Behind the fences of a gated community, European dropouts are seeking freedom, healing and salvation from Armageddon &ndash; for themselves and their savings. Separating them are 12 kilometres of red-earth road which transforms into a quagmire every rainy season. Around them hovers the humid heat and choruses of cicadas. Step by step, the film explores the new community of settlers and the local population; the camera drifts through construction sites, schools, treatment rooms and shooting ranges, gazes up at the sky and into the internet. While the newcomers experience turf wars and loss, the locals follow their own myths which hark back to the country&rsquo;s missionary and colonial history. They all have a version of paradise.<br/>
Cast: by Yulia Lokshina (Director), Yulia Lokshina (Screenplay)<br/>
Durata: 121 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/media/filmstills/2026/plakate-2026/202608231_9_RWD_1920.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sat Feb 14 14:40 - Cubix 7, Wed Feb 18 13:00 - Haus der Berliner Festspiele, Thu Feb 19 15:00 - Urania, Fri Feb 20 10:00 - Cubix 7, Sun Feb 22 20:30 - Cubix 7]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202608231.html</guid></item><item><title>The Other Side of the Sun by Tawfik Sabouni</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202608798.html</link><description><![CDATA[Years ago, filmmaker Tawfik Sabouni was released from Saidnaya, the infamous Syrian prison also known as &ldquo;the other side of the sun&rdquo;. In the immediate aftermath of the fall of Assad&rsquo;s regime in December 2024, the filmmaker returns to the site of his detention. He does not intend to reopen wounds but instead to restore what systematic violence tried to erase: voices, stories and humanity. Sabouni invites four fellow survivors of Saidnaya to join him. Together, they return to the physical spaces where they were tortured and dehumanised for years, and engage in a carefully constructed re-enactment of their confinement: daily rituals, gestures and moments of survival. Filmed inside the former prison, these re-enactments become a means to express what language alone cannot contain. With restraint, the film confronts the viewer with the enduring marks of imprisonment and gives a voice not only to these five men but also to those thousands who did not survive the Assad regime and whose families are still searching for answers.<br/>
Cast: by Tawfik Sabouni (Director), Tawfik Sabouni (Screenplay) Cast: Tawfik Sabouni, Mahmoud Alqadah, Abdelkafi Alhaj, Mohammad Hamki, Abdelhamid Jadoue<br/>
Durata: 90 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/media/filmstills/2026/plakate-2026/202608798_9_RWD_1920.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sun Feb 15 17:30 - Haus der Berliner Festspiele, Mon Feb 16 22:00 - Cubix 6, Tue Feb 17 10:00 - Cubix 7, Wed Feb 18 10:00 - CinemaxX 7, Sat Feb 21 15:45 - Cubix 7, Sun Feb 22 20:30 - Zoo Palast 2]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202608798.html</guid></item><item><title>Jaripeo</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202608887.html</link><description><![CDATA[Every Christmas in Penjamillo, a town in Michoac&aacute;n, the annual &ldquo;jaripeo&rdquo; &ndash; central Mexican rodeo &ndash; draws locals and returning US migrants alike for a nostalgic celebration of the masculine ideals of this rural Mexican state. But beneath the spectacle, another story emerges: fleeting touches, coded glances and secret hookups in the woods behind the arena reveal a hidden queer subculture shaped by this environment. Filmmaker Efra&iacute;n, who grew up partly in Penjamillo, partly in Riverside, California, guides us through this world, blending personal memory, Super 8 images, stylised scenes and raw verit&eacute; to question the very machismo which the jaripeo upholds. At the Christmas rodeo, they meet two other protagonists: No&eacute;, a handsome and macho cowboy who is out to some of his family but who still lives largely in secrecy; and Joseph, a flamboyant diva and devoted jaripeo superfan who is cherished by his community. Through their interactions with them, Efra&iacute;n embarks on a journey of self-recognition, creating layered, intimate portraits of three lives shaped by tradition, desire and identity.<br/>
Cast: by Efraín Mojica (Screenplay)<br/>
Durata: 70 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202608887_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Wed Feb 18 13:00 - Bluemax Theater, Thu Feb 19 16:00 - Cubix 7, Fri Feb 20 13:00 - ADK am Hanseatenweg, Sat Feb 21 22:30 - Cubix 7, Sun Feb 22 22:00 - Cubix 6]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202608887.html</guid></item><item><title>La Face cachée de la Terre by Arnaud Alain</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202608889.html</link><description><![CDATA[Dimitri loves to photograph the people around him. But for years, images have been slipping away from his sight. He knows that, one day, he will no longer see. He is unable to take photos as he used to. So, night and day, hidden behind his camera, he gathers light and bodies. The film accompanies Dimitri through the streets of Paris, New York and elsewhere; as he captures his objects, the film camera captures him. Along the way, the director and his protagonist encounter friends including Pierre, who lost his eyesight twenty years ago, but also lovers and strangers, met by chance or during a photo shoot. Imaginations and gazes overlay. Dimitri&rsquo;s photographs converse with the filmmaker&rsquo;s reveries. Dimitri invites him and the audience to discover the hidden face of the Earth.<br/>
Cast: by Arnaud Alain (Director), Arnaud Alain (Screenplay) Cast: Dimitri Jean, Pierre Marragou<br/>
Durata: 68 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/media/filmstills/2026/plakate-2026/202608889_9_RWD_1920.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Tue Feb 17 21:30 - Urania, Wed Feb 18 10:00 - Cubix 9, Thu Feb 19 19:00 - Cubix 7, Sat Feb 21 14:00 - Cubix 7, Sun Feb 22 13:00 - Bluemax Theater]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202608889.html</guid></item><item><title>Liebhaberinnen by Koxi</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202609496.html</link><description><![CDATA[A sleeping bag on the floor in front of the fitness studio lockers, a coaching seminar and the morning shift briefing (to practise the salesperson smile): these are the tough situations Brigitte (Johanna Wokalek) finds herself in. She is the protagonist of this Elfriede Jelinek adaptation, in which debut filmmaker Koxi takes stock of the successful early novel by the later Nobel Prize winner by catapulting it from the 1970s into contemporary late capitalism. Female market value today? While scrolling, middle-aged trade fair hostess Brigitte comes across schoolgirl Paula (Hannah Schiller), who is doing all she can to get Internet fame. While one seems full of youthful ambitions and aspirations, the other starts comparing herself to her, increasingly obsessively. Brigitte must change her life to reach her goals with proper calculation &ndash; but are they really hers? Paula goes to drastic measures to break out of her dreary home, but there is no escape. <em class="film">Liebhaberinnen</em> is a dark tragicomedy about the impossibility of female fulfilment and the less empowering brand of mother-daughter relationships. &ldquo;Use the patriarchy&rdquo; cum self-marketing optimisation. All in all, little has changed.<br/>
Cast: by Koxi (Director), Antonio de Luca (Screenplay) Cast: Johanna Wokalek, Hannah Schiller, Ben Münchow, Victoria Trauttmansdorff, Jasmin Artosha Mokhtare, Susanne Bredehöft<br/>
Durata: 98 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/media/filmstills/2026/plakate-2026/202609496_9_ORG.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sun Feb 15 18:00 - Delphi Filmpalast, Wed Feb 18 14:30 - Cinema Paris, Thu Feb 19 21:30 - Bluemax Theater, Sun Feb 22 11:00 - Delphi Filmpalast]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202609496.html</guid></item><item><title>Forest up in the Mountain by Sofía Bordenave</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202609839.html</link><description><![CDATA[In 2017, young Mapuche Rafael Nahuel was killed by Argentina&rsquo;s Naval Prefecture police in the Andean forest of Villa Mascardi, Patagonia. Drawing on court records, official documents and forensic archives, <em class="film">Forest up in the Mountain</em> situates this crime within a long history of systematic state violence against the Mapuche people. The film links this case to violence rooted in territorial colonisation following the so-called &ldquo;Conquest of the Desert&rdquo; in the late 19<sup>th</sup> century. By exposing the fractures of a judicial system that reproduces disproportionate power relations between the state and Indigenous peoples &ndash; and treats their territories as sites of industrial exploitation &ndash; this porous documentation brings to light processes of dislocation and identity rupture enacted through material and symbolic violence. Through a historical examination of territorial disputes, Sof&iacute;a Bordenave&rsquo;s film presents the forest as both witness and space of resistance, an echoing archive whose testimony extends beyond the courtroom and challenges official narratives.<br/>
Cast: by Sofía Bordenave (Director), Sofía Bordenave (Screenplay) Cast: Mirta Ñancunao, Lorena Cañuqueo, Joaquin Rapoport<br/>
Durata: 91 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/media/filmstills/2026/plakate-2026/202609839_9_RWD_1920.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sat Feb 14 17:00 - Cinema Paris, Mon Feb 16 13:00 - Zoo Palast 2, Wed Feb 18 15:00 - CinemaxX 5]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202609839.html</guid></item><item><title>Matapanki by Diego &quot;Mapache&quot; Fuentes</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202609924.html</link><description><![CDATA[Ricardo is a punk who spends his days drinking cheap alcohol, going to gigs and wandering the streets of the outskirts with his two best friends, Mella and Claudia. Beneath his tough exterior lies a fragile tenderness: he lives with and cares for his grandmother, Mar&iacute;a Luisa, the only emotional anchor in his chaotic life. One night, during a reckless drinking session, Ricardo tries a strange, clandestinely brewed alcoholic drink known as Matapanki. From that moment on, he gains alcohol-fuelled superpowers that activate every time he drinks the potion. This places Ricardo in a dilemma: he is unsure whether to become a superhero and embrace the responsibility of changing society. But when alcohol and rage take over, Ricardo recklessly springs into action and commits a brutal, irreversible mistake that ignites an international conflict.<br/>
Cast: by Diego "Mapache" Fuentes (Director), Diego "Mapache" Fuentes (Screenplay) Cast: Ramón Gávez, Diego Bravo, Antonia McCarthy, Rosa Peñaloza, Rodrigo Lisboa<br/>
Durata: 71 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/media/filmstills/2026/plakate-2026/202609924_9_ORG.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Tue Feb 17 19:00 - HKW 1 - Miriam Makeba Auditorium, Wed Feb 18 12:30 - Zoo Palast 1, Thu Feb 19 10:15 - Cubix 6, Sat Feb 21 16:15 - Cubix 6, Sun Feb 22 18:45 - Filmtheater am Friedrichshain]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202609924.html</guid></item><item><title>Moscas by Fernando Eimbcke</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202610010.html</link><description><![CDATA[Olga lives a strictly regulated life without any friends or relationships in a vast block of flats. When, out of financial necessity, she is forced to rent out a room, a man moves in who also sneaks his nine-year-old son into the flat. To her own surprise, Olga begins to form an unlikely bond with the child. Her carefully controlled world begins to shift and, entirely against Olga&rsquo;s will, these three lives start to become intertwined.<br/>
Cast: by Fernando Eimbcke (Director), Vanesa Garnica (Screenplay) Cast: Teresita Sánchez, Bastian Escobar, Hugo Ramírez<br/>
Durata: 99 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202610010_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Wed Feb 18 15:00 - Berlinale Palast, Thu Feb 19 12:30 - Urania, Thu Feb 19 18:30 - Uber Eats Music Hall, Fri Feb 20 17:30 - Haus der Berliner Festspiele, Sun Feb 22 21:30 - HKW 1 - Miriam Makeba Auditorium]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202610010.html</guid></item><item><title>Not a Hero by Rima Das</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202610128.html</link><description><![CDATA[Eleven-year-old Mivan has been raised in the city. Now, he is sent to his family&rsquo;s ancestral village to stay with his young aunt, Pahi. Used to the rhythms and comforts of urban life, Mivan finds the village slow, unfamiliar and unwelcoming. His relationship with Pahi is also distant, shaped by unspoken tensions and unresolved feelings from the past. As he is drawn into village routines, goes to school and develops new friendships, he begins to experience a world where time moves differently and nothing comes easily. Through everyday encounters with people, animals and nature, Mivan slowly opens himself up to empathy, patience and a sense of belonging. Due to his quiet presence, buried emotions within the household begin to surface. Without recourse to grand gestures, the film observes the gentle transformation of a child &ndash; and of adults who rediscover what they have long left behind.<br/>
Cast: by Rima Das (Director), Rima Das (Screenplay) Cast: Bhuman Bhargav Das, Sukanya Boruah, Mrinmoy Das<br/>
Durata: 97 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202610128_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sat Feb 14 10:30 - HKW 1 - Miriam Makeba Auditorium, Sun Feb 15 16:00 - Zoo Palast 2, Mon Feb 16 09:45 - Filmtheater am Friedrichshain, Wed Feb 18 15:45 - HKW 1 - Miriam Makeba Auditorium, Sun Feb 22 10:15 - Cubix 6]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202610128.html</guid></item><item><title>Se eu fosse vivo... vivia by André Novais Oliveira</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202610152.html</link><description><![CDATA[Brazil, the 1970s. Contagem is still a growing town and the home of a young couple in love. Gilberto asks for Jacira&rsquo;s forgiveness just before an unexpected encounter changes the course of their lives. Fifty years later, Gilberto and Jacira are still together. A charismatic and gentle couple in their mid-seventies, they lead a happy life despite the health problems that come with age, sharing almost all of their daily activities side by side. When Jacira is suddenly hospitalised, Gilberto begins to experience disturbing events &ndash; in a spiral through time and space &ndash; that lead him towards the unknown.<br/>
Cast: by André Novais Oliveira (Director), André Novais Oliveira (Screenplay) Cast: Conceição Evaristo, Norberto Novais Oliveira, Jean Paulo Campos, Tainá Evaristo<br/>
Durata: 101 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202610152_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sun Feb 15 15:15 - Zoo Palast 1, Mon Feb 16 21:45 - Cubix 9, Tue Feb 17 13:00 - Cubix 7, Wed Feb 18 21:45 - Filmtheater am Friedrichshain, Fri Feb 20 18:30 - Zoo Palast 1, Sat Feb 21 15:30 - Urania]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202610152.html</guid></item><item><title>Animol by Ashley Walters</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202610496.html</link><description><![CDATA[Behind the walls of a young offender institution, Troy (Tut Nyuot) is thrust into a brutal world of gangs, loyalty and violence. From the moment he arrives, he is tested. Paired with a volatile cellmate, Troy is forced to deal with daily threats and power struggles. An unspoken bond with a fellow inmate offers solace in the oppressive environment, but their growing connection becomes a dangerous vulnerability. As Troy&rsquo;s welfare officer Claypole tries to reconnect him with his estranged mother, Troy is increasingly caught up in the institution&rsquo;s brutal hierarchy and is eventually forced to make impossible choices. And when violence erupts, Troy finds himself isolated and confronting his deepest fears. In this unforgiving world, where survival means betrayal and trust can be weaponised, Troy must navigate a path between the person he once was and the one he is in danger of becoming.<br/>
Cast: by Ashley Walters (Director), Nick Love (Screenplay) Cast: Tut Nyuot, Vladyslav Baliuk, Sekou Diaby, Stephen Graham, Sharon Duncan-Brewster, Ryan Dean<br/>
Durata: 90 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202610496_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sat Feb 14 19:15 - Bluemax Theater, Sun Feb 15 16:00 - Cubix 9, Mon Feb 16 22:15 - Cubix 8, Wed Feb 18 13:15 - Colosseum 1, Fri Feb 20 16:30 - Cubix 9]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202610496.html</guid></item><item><title>Flying Tigers by Madhusree Dutta</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202610591.html</link><description><![CDATA[Spurred by her Alzheimer&rsquo;s-afflicted mother&rsquo;s strange evocation of home-invading tigers, filmmaker Madhusree Dutta travels to Assam, India. Here, she learns about the Flying Tigers: US aircraft that transferred military supplies during WWII across the perilous Himalayas, from Assam to Kunming in China. So begins a globetrotting, decades-spanning docufiction essay on the human-scale experience of monumental logistical phenomena, featuring small histories that unfold in the quiet shadows of History writ large. Teaming up with Kunming-born media theorist Mi You and Assam-based researcher Purav Goswami, Dutta contrasts the smooth international flow of goods today with increasing restrictions on people&rsquo;s movement across borders. Her film reveals how lived realities of frontier populations have always been fluid and malleable, refusing the homogeneity demanded by cartographic political imagination. Appropriately, Dutta adopts a heterogeneous, genre-defying form, mixing interviews, archival material, performances, animation and musical numbers to craft a personal, wide-ranging work at once intimate and colossal.<br/>
Cast: by Madhusree Dutta (Director), Madhusree Dutta (Screenplay) Cast: Madhusree Dutta, Mi You, Purav Goswami, Devika Hazarika<br/>
Durata: 105 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/media/filmstills/2026/plakate-2026/202610591_9_ORG.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Mon Feb 16 15:00 - Cinema Betonhalle@Silent Green, Tue Feb 17 14:00 - Cinema Paris, Wed Feb 18 20:00 - CinemaxX 5, Sat Feb 21 17:30 - Cinema Paris]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202610591.html</guid></item><item><title>Geunyeoga doraon nal by Hong Sangsoo</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202611058.html</link><description><![CDATA[After getting married, she gave up acting. Then, after getting divorced, she took it up again and starred in an independent film. Now, the film is about to be released and she is giving interviews to support it. Having reached middle age, she is presenting her face to the world as an actor for the first time in a long while. She does three interviews at 30-minute intervals, and tries to answer each question as best as she can. Later that day, her acting coach asks her to re-enact the interviews she did earlier. But every time she reaches the crucial parts, for some reason she is unable to remember a thing. She is tired and wants to go home. Her daughter is waiting.<br/>
Cast: by Hong Sangsoo (Director), Hong Sangsoo (Screenplay) Cast: Song Sunmi, Cho Yunhee, Park Miso<br/>
Durata: 84 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/media/filmstills/2026/plakate-2026/202611058_9_ORG.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Wed Feb 18 18:30 - Zoo Palast 1, Thu Feb 19 10:45 - Haus der Berliner Festspiele, Fri Feb 20 22:00 - Cubix 7, Sat Feb 21 20:00 - Urania, Sun Feb 22 16:15 - Cubix 7]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202611058.html</guid></item><item><title>Johanna d’Arc of Mongolia by Ulrike Ottinger</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202611171.html</link><description><![CDATA[Four women travelling solo on the Trans-Siberian railway strike up a friendship &ndash; a French-speaking private tutor based in London, a German university lecturer, a Broadway singer, and a young backpacker. After transferring to the Trans-Mongolian railway, the four are kidnapped by a Mongolian princess and her mounted army.
 In 1988, Ulrike Ottinger was the first western director to get permission to film in Inner Mongolia. Equally based on anthropological accounts and feminist fantasy, she created a beguiling mixture of far eastern fable and ethnographic documentation. With a musical tapestry by the Georgian trio Kalinka Sisters, traditional celebrations and shamanic rituals lead to a boisterous rendezvous of cultures. Talking about the film in 1989, Ottinger said &ldquo;my film is not trying to create an exotic image, but to explore the issue of cultural transfer. If that results in exoticism, it is never identified with &lsquo;the foreign&rsquo;, but rather with an unsuccessful encounter with it. I don&rsquo;t mean that in an entirely negative way, because it can certainly produce something exciting&rdquo;.<br/>
Cast: by Ulrike Ottinger (Director), Ulrike Ottinger (Screenplay) Cast: Delphine Seyrig, Irm Hermann, Gillian Scalici, Inés Sastre, Re Huar Xu, Peter Kern, Nougzar Sharia, Christoph Eichhorn<br/>
Durata: 166 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202611171_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sat Feb 14 21:00 - Deutsche Kinemathek – Halle, Wed Feb 18 13:30 - Cubix 5]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202611171.html</guid></item><item><title>Juice by Ernest R. Dickerson</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202611173.html</link><description><![CDATA[A story of four Black teens hanging out in Harlem. They skip school, chill at the arcade, lock horns with a Puerto Rican gang, and steal hip-hop LPs. But cracks begin to appear in the tight-knit group. Bishop thinks the only way for him to get &ldquo;juice&rdquo; (respect and street cred) is with violence. His biggest role model is James Cagney in Raoul Walsh&rsquo;s iconic gangster movie <em class="film-other">White Heat</em> (1949). Quincy (&ldquo;Q&rdquo;) wants to be a star DJ and enters a competition. Meanwhile, Bishop and Raheem are trying to set up an alibi for a convenience store robbery. But the plan goes pear-shaped when Bishop starts shooting.
 In this directorial debut of Spike Lee cinematographer Ernest R. Dickerson, the quartet of young men are united by a love of rap and hip-hop. The music was also a big draw for the target audience. Not only did the cast include hip-hop superstars Tupac Shakur and Queen Latifah, the pre-release of the soundtrack brought in audiences, weaving New Black Cinema together with the music charts. In an analogy to gangsta rap and its often-violent music videos, <em class="film">Juice</em> combined the traditional teen subgenre of juvenile delinquents with elements of high-octane action movies.<br/>
Cast: by Ernest R. Dickerson (Director), Gerard Brown (Screenplay) Cast: Omar Epps, Jermaine Hopkins, Tupac Shakur, Khalil Kain, Cindy Herron, Queen Latifah, Samuel L. Jackson, Vincent Laresca, George O. Gore, Grace Garland<br/>
Durata: 95 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202611173_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Mon Feb 16 19:15 - Cubix 5, Wed Feb 18 21:30 - Deutsche Kinemathek – Halle, Sat Feb 21 17:45 - Cubix 5]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202611173.html</guid></item><item><title>No Salgas by Victoria Linares Villegas</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202611243.html</link><description><![CDATA[Liz, a closeted gay college student pretending to be straight, is still haunted by the gruesome death of her girlfriend, Wendy. Desparate for escape, she joins her friends on a weekend trip away. But as Liz grows close to a mysterious young woman on the trip, unresolved sorrow and long-buried desires stir something unnatural within her. An unseen force that twists suspicion into violence spreads through the group, threatening to consume it. In a society where being seen can be dangerous, Liz must confront not only her grief, but also the brutal cost of being herself.<br/>
Cast: by Victoria Linares Villegas (Director), Victoria Linares Villegas (Screenplay) Cast: Cecile van Welie, Gabriela Cortés, Camila Issa, Camila Santana, Mariela Guerrero, Jonathan López, Johnny Morales, José Beato<br/>
Durata: 105 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/media/filmstills/2026/plakate-2026/202611243_9_RWD_1920.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sat Feb 14 16:50 - Cubix 6, Mon Feb 16 19:00 - HKW 1 - Miriam Makeba Auditorium, Tue Feb 17 15:45 - Filmtheater am Friedrichshain, Wed Feb 18 20:00 - Xenon Kino, Thu Feb 19 18:45 - Filmtheater am Friedrichshain, Fri Feb 20 10:00 - Zoo Palast 2, Sat Feb 21 19:00 - Cubix 6]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202611243.html</guid></item><item><title>Assarab by Ahmed Bouanani</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202611447.html</link><description><![CDATA[Set in colonial-era Morocco, where a poor villager finds a bundle of banknotes in a bag of flour. He convinces his wife to give up her position as a maid in a French household and move to the city with him. He wants to exchange the currency, but is afraid of going to a bank. He wanders around Sal&eacute; looking for a money changer, meeting many other people who are also looking for a better life. They include the clown-like singer and actor Ali ben Ali and the hungry visitors to a soup kitchen. His wife also does her best to find happiness &ndash; she wants to have a goat sacrificed to get the help of the Genie.
 Poet and screenwriter Ahmed Bouanani (1938&ndash;2011) was one of the founders of Morocco&rsquo;s modern cinema tradition. He said he made films &ldquo;the way he wrote poems&rdquo;.&nbsp;The 4K restoration of his only narrative feature used original 35mm elements and took four months. It focused on retaining the film&rsquo;s unique visual and audio identity, faithfully recreating the analogue aesthetic at the heart of Ahmed Bouanani&rsquo;s work.<br/>
Cast: by Ahmed Bouanani (Director), Ahmed Bouanani (Screenplay) Cast: Mohamed el-Habachi, Mohamed Saïd Afifi, Fatima Regragui, Mostafa Mounir, Mohamed Razine, Mohamed Idrissi, Abdellah Amrani, Jilali Bel Haj<br/>
Durata: 100 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202611447_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Wed Feb 18 19:00 - ADK am Hanseatenweg, Thu Feb 19 11:30 - Cubix 5, Sun Feb 22 11:00 - Cubix 5]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202611447.html</guid></item><item><title>Un hijo propio by Maite Alberdi</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202611871.html</link><description><![CDATA[The profound desire to become a mother and the constant pressure from her surroundings drive Alejandra to fake a pregnancy. In this feature-length documentary, Maite Alberdi (<em class="film-other">The Mole Agent</em>) captures how what begins as a simple lie turns into a complex charade that Alejandra must sustain for months before her hopeful husband and family. Trapped in a pretence that consumes her, Alejandra is pushed to cross an irreversible line, unleashing a media scandal that makes it impossible for her to continue the deception.<br/>
Cast: by Maite Alberdi (Director), Julián Loyola (Screenplay) Cast: Ana Celeste, Armando Espitia, Ángeles Cruz, Mayra Sérbulo Cortés, Luisa Guzmán<br/>
Durata: 96 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/media/filmstills/2026/plakate-2026/202611871_9_ORG.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sat Feb 14 14:00 - Haus der Berliner Festspiele, Sun Feb 15 16:15 - ADK am Hanseatenweg, Wed Feb 18 22:00 - Colosseum 1, Sun Feb 22 19:45 - Colosseum 1]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202611871.html</guid></item><item><title>Monster Pabrik Rambut by Edwin</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202613096.html</link><description><![CDATA[Factory owner Maryati exploits her employees with excessively long shifts, luring them with incentives to make them prioritise productivity and greed over sleep. Putri is convinced that, because of this, her mother, who worked in the factory, committed suicide. Her sister Ida, however, believes that their mother died from being possessed. She thinks that whenever the workers grow weak from exhaustion, a dark and evil figure emerges and takes possession of their bodies. To prove her theory, Ida decides to work day and night in the factory so that she, too, will become possessed and can see for herself the being that she believes seized their mother&rsquo;s body. The sisters have a younger brother, Bona, who was born with a special gift that enables his wounds to heal quickly whenever he is injured. As the sisters investigate their mother&rsquo;s death, a ghostly figure searching for an ideal body seeks to take advantage of Bona&rsquo;s gift, putting him in danger. The three siblings now must bravely confront their own weaknesses and find strength in their faith in each other to overcome the terror that threatens their family.<br/>
Cast: by Edwin (Director), Eka Kurniawan (Screenplay) Cast: Rachel Amanda, Lutesha, Iqbaal Ramadhan, Didik Nini Thowok, Sal Priadi, Luqman 'Kev' Hakim<br/>
Durata: 96 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202613096_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sat Feb 14 18:15 - Uber Eats Music Hall, Sun Feb 15 20:30 - Haus der Berliner Festspiele, Wed Feb 18 20:30 - CinemaxX 6, Fri Feb 20 21:30 - Zoo Palast 1, Sun Feb 22 15:15 - Colosseum 1]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202613096.html</guid></item><item><title>Sunny Point by Wolf Vogel</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202613947.html</link><description><![CDATA[West Berlin in the autumn of 1989. Victor is a film producer. For adverts &ndash; but with the demeanour of a Hollywood tycoon! In reality, things do not look good for his company, Sunny Point. His credit line is overstretched, a big job has fallen through. All he has are a few cinema ads that are paying peanuts. The company is held together by his secretary (still in her probation period) and an ambitious employee. The big secret is that Victor is a refugee from East Germany, where he was a plastics engineer. In order to collect a second round of start-up aid from West Germany, he decides to feign a new escape and jumps into the River Spree &ndash; on November 9, of all days.
 This satire about a self-made man who knows all the capitalist tricks to deploy for his criminal business plan was made with no state subsidies, instead relying on improvisational talent and creative input. In addition to film quotes and images of the Berlin Wall coming down, snippets of video games and local movie adverts, director Wolf Vogel brought his industry knowledge and his experiences in East Germany to his narrative debut. Shot with a West-East crew and cast, <em class="film">Sunny Point</em> avoids the popular clich&eacute; of the needy &ldquo;brothers and sisters in the East&rdquo;.<br/>
Cast: by Wolf Vogel (Director), Wolf Vogel (Screenplay) Cast: André M. Hennicke, Jenny Schily, Christian Kuchenbuch, Petra Kleinert, Claudine Wilde, Günter Zschäckel, Jockel Tschiersch, Horst Günter Marx, Santiago Ziesmer, Hendrick Arnst<br/>
Durata: 97 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202613947_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sun Feb 15 18:30 - Deutsche Kinemathek – Halle, Wed Feb 18 19:00 - Cubix 5, Sat Feb 21 19:00 - Deutsche Kinemathek – Halle]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202613947.html</guid></item><item><title>Narciso by Marcelo Martinessi</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202614171.html</link><description><![CDATA[Paraguay, 1959. Asunci&oacute;n vibrates for the first time with a foreign rhythm. Rock &rsquo;n&rsquo; roll has found its way onto the radio carrying heat, speed and the faint illusion that the times might suddenly move forward. The city feels younger, looser &ndash; briefly out of sync with itself. At the same time, another rhythm settles in. Slower. Heavier. A disciplined pulse that orders gestures, silences voices and redraws the limits of what can be seen or desired. Words like virtue, decency, tradition begin to circulate with unusual force, shaping a shared fear. In this charged atmosphere, the charismatic musician Narciso becomes a symbol of freedom. His youth, his body, his way of inhabiting the night resonate with the music and with the threat it carries. Desire becomes visible. And visibility, dangerous. What once passed unnoticed now attracts attention, suspicion, judgment. As the regime consolidates its power, morality determines the situation &ndash; both intimate and oppressive. The future does not disappear all at once; it tightens. It learns to watch itself. Between dance and discipline, a new order takes shape, and an entire generation feels it closing in.<br/>
Cast: by Marcelo Martinessi (Director), Marcello Martinessi (Screenplay) Cast: Diro Romero, Manuel Cuenca, Arturo Fleitas, Margarita Irun, Mona Martinez, Nahuel Perez Biscayart<br/>
Durata: 101 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202614171_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Tue Feb 17 18:30 - Zoo Palast 1, Wed Feb 18 10:00 - Haus der Berliner Festspiele, Thu Feb 19 21:30 - Cubix 7, Sat Feb 21 22:00 - Cubix 6, Sun Feb 22 21:30 - Cubix 9]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202614171.html</guid></item><item><title>Shibire by Takuya Uchiyama</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202614502.html</link><description><![CDATA[In the snowy coastal city of Niigata, which is blanketed in grey skies and the roar of winter waves, Daichi, a boy who lost his voice under the tyranny of his father in early childhood, lives in a prefab room on the rooftop of an old multi-tenant building with his mother, Aki. She works in the nightlife trade, pours her earnings into men and is rarely home. The days of the two are defined by their extreme poverty and deep separation from society. The shy and withdrawn Daichi is searching for small traces of solace and love, yet finds no place to belong. Aki, now suffering from severe liver cirrhosis caused by years of alcoholism, moves with Daichi into the home of her sister, a devout follower of a new religious sect. There, Aki endures oppressive demands from her controlling lover, but clings to him even as she is harmed, while Daichi can do nothing but watch. Then, a faint light shines into his life: he experiences a sudden, breathtaking love and his fate, buffeted by forces far beyond his grasp, begins to shift.<br/>
Cast: by Takuya Uchiyama (Director), Takuya Uchiyama (Screenplay) Cast: Takumi Kitamura, Rie Miyazawa, Tsukasa Enomoto, Anji Kato, Masatoshi Nagase<br/>
Durata: 118 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/media/filmstills/2026/plakate-2026/202614502_9_RWD_1920.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sun Feb 15 21:30 - Urania, Mon Feb 16 10:00 - Cubix 9, Tue Feb 17 18:30 - Cubix 7, Wed Feb 18 10:15 - CinemaxX 5, Wed Feb 18 10:15 - CinemaxX 6, Fri Feb 20 21:30 - Cubix 5, Sat Feb 21 15:30 - Zoo Palast 1]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202614502.html</guid></item><item><title>Dust by Anke Blondé</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202614604.html</link><description><![CDATA[In the spring of 1999, Belgian entrepreneurs Luc and Geert learn that their network of shell companies is about to be exposed in the international press. An emergency board meeting is called. Evidence must be destroyed; and discretion enforced. By tomorrow morning, the police will be at the door. After this final meeting, the two men go their separate ways, entering their last day as free, rich and powerful men. Luc, the technical genius, retreats to his villa, where he gets the impression that his wife Alma has known all along what has been going on. Repeatedly unable to reach Geert, his trusted partner, Luc grows increasingly uneasy. Meanwhile Geert, the charismatic salesman, seeks refuge in the arms of his driver and lover inside his bunker-like villa. Having insider knowledge, Geert is tempted to act &ndash; but doing so would mean betraying those closest to him. Luc heads back to the company HQ but, in the middle of a violent storm, his car gets stuck in the mud. When Geert discovers the abandoned vehicle, panic sets in. Slowly, they realise that they are not actually on the run but on a journey towards something they can no longer avoid: responsibility. And each other.<br/>
Cast: by Anke Blondé (Director), Angelo Tijssens (Screenplay) Cast: Arieh Worthalter, Jan Hammenecker, Thibaud Dooms, Anthony Welsh<br/>
Durata: 115 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202614604_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sun Feb 15 21:30 - Berlinale Palast, Mon Feb 16 18:45 - Uber Eats Music Hall, Wed Feb 18 10:00 - HKW 1 - Miriam Makeba Auditorium, Thu Feb 19 16:15 - Haus der Berliner Festspiele, Sun Feb 22 22:00 - Haus der Berliner Festspiele]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202614604.html</guid></item><item><title>AnyMart by Yusuke Iwasaki</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202615330.html</link><description><![CDATA[Sakai is the assistant manager at a convenience store, his working days determined by routine. Without any hint of emotion, he deflects the annoying customers and follows the rigid rules which the store owner imposes on the staff. When the ambitious Ogawa is employed part time, Sakai increasingly begins to question his role in the system. The monotonous world of the AnyMart gradually unravels until the boundary between life and death eventually becomes dissolved by the ghosts called forth by consumerism. Carried by current young Nippon stars, this feature debut by commercial filmmaker Yusuke Iwasaki, himself a son of a long-term store owner, uses a crazy mix of off-beat horror, socially critical drama and absurd comedy to home in on fears about work as well as the feelings of powerlessness towards society, with which the younger generations increasingly see themselves confronted. In the midst of a sea of power lines and grey apartment complexes, the convenience store becomes a heterotopia. Is there still hope in the cold world of late capitalism or must we eternally haunt the sterile aisles of the AnyMart, like chickens packed in plastic?<br/>
Cast: by Yusuke Iwasaki (Director), Yusuke Iwasaki (Screenplay) Cast: Shota Sometani, Erika Karata, Masahiko Nishimura<br/>
Durata: 88 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/media/filmstills/2026/plakate-2026/202615330_9_RWD_1920.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Fri Feb 13 17:30 - Cinema Paris, Sat Feb 14 09:30 - Cubix 8, Wed Feb 18 22:00 - Bluemax Theater, Sun Feb 22 20:30 - Delphi Filmpalast]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202615330.html</guid></item><item><title>17 by Kosara Mitic</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202615475.html</link><description><![CDATA[Seventeen-year-old Sara is hiding a secret during a school trip. When the trip spirals out of control and she witnesses her friend Lina being sexually assaulted, the two girls try to break the cycle of casual violence. This seals an everlasting bond between them.<br/>
Cast: by Kosara Mitic (Director), Kosara Mitic (Screenplay) Cast: Eva Kostic, Martina Danilovska, Dame Joveski, Eva Stojchevska, Petar Manic<br/>
Durata: 105 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202615475_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Wed Feb 18 19:00 - Bluemax Theater, Thu Feb 19 15:45 - Cubix 9, Fri Feb 20 21:45 - Cubix 8, Sat Feb 21 19:00 - Bluemax Theater, Sun Feb 22 17:30 - Colosseum 1]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202615475.html</guid></item><item><title>Un hiver russe by Patric Chiha</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202615476.html</link><description><![CDATA[Following the full-scale invasion of Ukraine in 2022, many people in Russia face a weighty choice: military service, prison or exile. Margarita, Yuri and their friends refuse to comply with the regime and leave the country in search of a new home. They no longer have a place to which they can return, nor one where they feel truly welcome.<br/>
Cast: by Patric Chiha (Director), Patric Chiha (Screenplay)<br/>
Durata: 87 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202615476_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Tue Feb 17 13:00 - Bluemax Theater, Wed Feb 18 16:00 - Cubix 7, Thu Feb 19 10:00 - ADK am Hanseatenweg, Sat Feb 21 22:30 - Cubix 5, Sun Feb 22 10:15 - Cubix 7]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202615476.html</guid></item><item><title>Dao by Alain Gomis</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202615485.html</link><description><![CDATA[The film begins with a definition of its title: &ldquo;DAO is a perpetual and circular movement which flows in everything and unites the world.&rdquo; And then it proceeds to take us to the casting of Gloria, a character whose daughter is about to be married. An off-screen voice directing the casting session tells us that &ldquo;the first step is to make this family&rdquo;. Actors and non-actors are cast and brought together to become relatives who will all celebrate a wedding in Paris and commemorate the loss of their patriarch in Guinea-Bissau. Their individual stories and their common threads of heritage are woven together with fact and fiction as they travel between these two worlds; love, laughter, ritual, pain and history intertwined. Perpetual circular movement framing reality.<br/>
Cast: by Alain Gomis (Director), Alain Gomis (Screenplay) Cast: Katy Correa, D’Johé Kouadio, Samir Guesmi, Mike Etienne, Nicolas Gomis, Fara Baco Gomis, Poundo Gomis<br/>
Durata: 185 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202615485_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sat Feb 14 14:45 - Berlinale Palast, Mon Feb 16 10:00 - Uber Eats Music Hall, Tue Feb 17 20:30 - Haus der Berliner Festspiele, Wed Feb 18 16:45 - CinemaxX 6, Sun Feb 22 12:00 - Berlinale Palast]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202615485.html</guid></item><item><title>London by Sebastian Brameshuber</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202615540.html</link><description><![CDATA[Bobby is constantly in his car, driving back and forth on the autobahn linking Vienna and Salzburg. Other people travel the same route. Bobby picks them up to help with the petrol money and talks to them along the way: the soldier questioning what it means to fight; the supermarket trainee going to visit family; the academic researching the road&rsquo;s history; the queer woman about to get married. Many different paths, different accents and different stories, most of them true. Bobby listens, but also talks about himself, about his youth, about aging, about his friend in a coma in Salzburg who is the reason for all his trips. Mountains and forests pass by outside, broken up by junctions, barriers and bridges; the quality of light shifts along with the seasons. Neither a documentary, nor entirely fiction, <em class="film">London</em> is a quietly political portrait of today&rsquo;s Europe via its in-between spaces and those passing through them. Even in these strange times, anonymity and kindness can still go hand in hand.<br/>
Cast: by Sebastian Brameshuber (Director), Sebastian Brameshuber (Screenplay) Cast: Bobby Sommer<br/>
Durata: 122 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/media/filmstills/2026/plakate-2026/202615540_9_RWD_1920.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Mon Feb 16 18:45 - Zoo Palast 2, Tue Feb 17 16:00 - Cubix 6, Wed Feb 18 18:30 - Cubix 7, Sat Feb 21 21:45 - Cubix 9, Sun Feb 22 10:00 - Urania]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202615540.html</guid></item><item><title>Im Glanze dieses Glückes by Johann Feindt</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202615577.html</link><description><![CDATA[Rhine wine in Saxony! It is being served at an information stand set up by West Germany&rsquo;s Christian Democratic Union party (CDU) just before the first and only free elections to East Germany&rsquo;s People&rsquo;s Assembly; the ballot will give the CDU almost 41% of the vote. But while the East Germans appear entirely sober about it all despite the sweet swill on offer, during the election campaign in February/March of 1990 the West Germans seem drunk on the new order. &ldquo;Socialism is over. Nobody wants it anymore&rdquo;, exults Helmut Kohl. Meanwhile, his finance minister is speaking of an &ldquo;expanded economic territory&rdquo;. And very soon, a Nazi banner is proclaiming the &ldquo;east regions&rdquo; of Germany as the next goal for a &ldquo;reunification&rdquo;.
 &ldquo;How do various generations experience the uncertainty, the disorientation and the reconsideration of East Germany&rsquo;s old values?&rdquo;, asked the East-West German documentary film collective Blick ins Land. In their questioning of workers, schoolchildren, border guards and police, a teacher and an East German state security (Stasi) officer about their experiences and feelings, the collective provided an unvarnished look at the downsides of the &ldquo;splendid happiness&rdquo;.<br/>
Cast: by Johann Feindt (Director), Jeanine Meerapfel (Director), Helga Reidemeister (Director), Dieter Schumann (Director), Tamara Trampe (Director)<br/>
Durata: 83 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202615577_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sun Feb 15 11:00 - Cubix 5, Wed Feb 18 17:00 - Cubix 5, Fri Feb 20 19:00 - Deutsche Kinemathek – Halle]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202615577.html</guid></item><item><title>Han ye deng zhu by Xu Zao</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202615603.html</link><description><![CDATA[The future. Winter. Space travel is no longer a dream. A once-thriving film studio faces bankruptcy. The enormous compound, with structures ranging from the Great Sphinx of Giza to the Forbidden City, is now completely covered in snow and stripped of its former glory. Zha, a lonely janitor, tends to this forgotten place, with only a cat that used to perform in films for company. Running out of money, the studio owner gives him a VR headset as partial compensation. Zha is immediately drawn into the virtual world and embarks on a romantic journey with a female player who invites him on a trip to the moon. Meanwhile, the studio, which is about to close permanently, is temporarily brought back to life when a film crew arrives to shoot an alien invasion movie on the expansive backlot &ndash; with the studio&rsquo;s actual destruction slated to be shot as the movie&rsquo;s final showdown.<br/>
Cast: by Xu Zao (Director), Xu Zao (Screenplay) Cast: Da Peng, Qing Yi<br/>
Durata: 90 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202615603_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sat Feb 14 21:45 - Bluemax Theater, Sun Feb 15 18:45 - Cubix 9, Mon Feb 16 16:30 - Cubix 8, Wed Feb 18 16:00 - Colosseum 1, Sun Feb 22 13:00 - Colosseum 1]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202615603.html</guid></item><item><title>Masayume by Nao Yoshigai</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202615647.html</link><description><![CDATA[<em class="program">Forum</em> audiences know Nao Yoshigai as the shadowy figure from Kaori Oda&lsquo;s <em class="film-other">Underground</em> (2025), a young woman as a medium between two realms: everyday kitchen gestures and haptic explorations of caves and the past. In her directorial debut, this artistic all-rounder uses a similar hybrid form to confront her soul and inner life &ndash; and with it the universal questions of life and death, stories and images, materiality and spirituality. Following her mother&rsquo;s passing, she seeks refuge and calm in a Zen temple to physically and mentally process what has engulfed her completely, paralysed her, stopped her in her tracks: her grief. In these Zen Buddhist surroundings, she learns to move her attention away from a human-centred perspective and on to the small hand movements and gestures, objects and rituals that make each single grain of rice a sensation. What in philosophy might be deemed an experience of transcendence is portrayed by Yoshigai with humour and sensual grace: she augments the retreat with family photos, performances and hand-drawn animations, from the rumbling stomach to the intestinal tract &ndash; and back to humility, acceptance, liberation. A moving three-acter without a story!<br/>
Cast: by Nao Yoshigai (Director), Nao Yoshigai (Screenplay) Cast: Nao Yoshigai<br/>
Durata: 110 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202615647_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Mon Feb 16 17:15 - Cinema Paris, Wed Feb 18 10:30 - Cubix 8, Fri Feb 20 15:30 - Cinema Betonhalle@Silent Green, Sun Feb 22 18:00 - Delphi Filmpalast]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202615647.html</guid></item><item><title>Lord of the Flies by Marc Munden</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202615659.html</link><description><![CDATA[Adapted from the 1954 novel by William Golding, <em class="film">Lord of the Flies</em> is the story of a group of young schoolboys who find themselves stranded on a Pacific island following a deadly plane crash during a nuclear war. In an attempt to remain civil, the boys organise themselves, led by Ralph and supported by the group&rsquo;s intellectual, Piggy. But as the youngest members begin to share sightings of a terrifying beast, hunter Jack begins to wrestle for leadership. Jack Thorne&rsquo;s adaptation marks the first time &ldquo;Lord of the Flies&rdquo; has been brought to television. Faithful to the original novel, the series delves further into the book&rsquo;s emotive themes: human nature, the loss of innocence and boyhood masculinity. Each of the four episodes is titled after a character at the core of the story &ndash; Ralph, Piggy, Simon and Jack &ndash; offering a subtly different perspective on the boys&rsquo; collective plight and manner in which they cope with their predicament.<br/>
Cast: by Marc Munden (Director), Jack Thorne (Screenplay) Cast: Winston Sawyers, Lox Pratt, David McKenna, Ike Talbut<br/>
Durata: 115 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202615659_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Fri Feb 13 20:30 - Haus der Berliner Festspiele, Sat Feb 14 16:15 - ADK am Hanseatenweg, Sun Feb 15 22:00 - Bluemax Theater, Wed Feb 18 17:15 - CinemaxX 5]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202615659.html</guid></item><item><title>The Day of Wrath: Tales from Tripoli by Rania Rafei</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202615703.html</link><description><![CDATA[The history of a city, its wars and uprisings. Taking the student protests that ushered in independence from France in 1943 as a starting point, Rania Rafei traces the back and forth between upheaval and consistency, discord and unity in Tripoli, Lebanon&rsquo;s second-biggest city. Connecting the personal and the political as well as the intimate and the collective, the film gives the city and its inhabitants a stage across different eras and generations, employing an open form that combines a cinematic letter to her dead father, family stories, archive material and the exploration of a present in which history has been forgotten. Listening, voiceover: ordered chronologically, kaleidoscopic in its effect. The hopes surrounding the Pan-Arabism of the 1960s and defeat in the Six-Day War are followed by days of fury &ndash; in the factions that formed during and after the civil war, and the protests since 2019 against the catastrophic economic situation, omnipresent corruption and the sectarian system. A film as an act of political tenderness between confidence and disillusionment, wrangling and confession. The desire for change is strong.<br/>
Cast: by Rania Rafei (Director), Rania Rafei (Screenplay)<br/>
Durata: 120 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202615703_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Tue Feb 17 17:30 - Cinema Paris, Wed Feb 18 10:00 - ADK am Hanseatenweg, Sat Feb 21 16:30 - Cubix 8]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202615703.html</guid></item><item><title>A Prayer for the Dying by Dara Van Dusen</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202615874.html</link><description><![CDATA[In 1870, the town of Friendship, Wisconsin, is enduring a dry, hot summer. The small town revolves around Jacob Hansen (Johnny Flynn), a hero of the American Civil War who, in spite of his many accomplishments, is unable to cast off the violence and darkness of his past as a soldier. Feeling compelled to atone for the wrongs he has committed, Jacob takes on the responsibility not only of providing for his young family but also of serving as sheriff, undertaker and pastor for Friendship. He thus considers Friendship to be under his protection &ndash; a claim that comes to haunt him when the town is hit by an epidemic that the town&rsquo;s doctor (John C. Reilly) cannot contain. As every decision becomes a choice between two evils, Jacob is increasingly haunted by his war-ridden past. It is unclear how much longer he can continue in his self-imposed role as the town&rsquo;s protector or whether he will ever be able to forgive himself for what he has done. <em class="film">A Prayer for the Dying</em>&nbsp;is a powerful account of the choices we must make when disaster strikes and everything we hold dear, including faith, family and community, is shaken to its very core.<br/>
Cast: by Dara Van Dusen (Director), Dara Van Dusen (Screenplay) Cast: Johnny Flynn, John C. Reilly, Kristine Kujath Thorp, Gustav Lindh<br/>
Durata: 95 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202615874_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Fri Feb 13 21:45 - Bluemax Theater, Sat Feb 14 18:45 - Cubix 9, Sun Feb 15 16:30 - Cubix 8, Tue Feb 17 13:00 - Colosseum 1, Wed Feb 18 16:00 - Bluemax Theater]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202615874.html</guid></item><item><title>Queen at Sea by Lance Hammer</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202616031.html</link><description><![CDATA[Amanda and her stepfather, Martin, struggle with a moral issue that divides them. Has Amanda&rsquo;s mother, Leslie, who is suffering from advanced dementia, lost the ability to make critical decisions in her own best interests? And, if so, who is responsible &ndash; a spouse, a child, an institution &ndash; for making such a determination? As Amanda and Martin are forced to make increasingly difficult choices, the repercussions spiral out of their control.<br/>
Cast: by Lance Hammer (Director), Lance Hammer (Screenplay) Cast: Juliette Binoche, Tom Courtenay, Anna Calder-Marshall, Florence Hunt<br/>
Durata: 121 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202616031_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Tue Feb 17 18:15 - Berlinale Palast, Wed Feb 18 12:45 - HKW 1 - Miriam Makeba Auditorium, Thu Feb 19 21:30 - Uber Eats Music Hall, Sat Feb 21 15:45 - Uber Eats Music Hall]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202616031.html</guid></item><item><title>Lust by Ralitza Petrova</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202616069.html</link><description><![CDATA[In her working life as a prison psychologist, Lilian deals with criminals who have experienced a lot. She herself is equally full of secrets, as it seems, a woman strongly led by her perception and intellect while keeping others and their emotions at a distance. A woman who does not say much and yet takes decisive actions, usually in a trench coat, quite motionless. When her estranged father dies, she returns home to Bulgaria; in the flat he has left her together with his debts, she encounters an amazing snake and her own extreme lust, which has long been held in check by a celibacy pact. The knots and ties come undone during the act of shibari, and liberation begins. Incredibly precise in cinematic, psychological and narrative terms alike, this headstrong second feature put together by Golden Leopard winner Ralitza Petrova (<em class="film-other">Godless</em>) is subtle and formally rigorous as it plays with genres, bodies and psyches. Carried by Lilian&rsquo;s unfathomable character, played by the amazing Snejanka Mihaylova, <em class="film">Lust</em> is a search for abstract joy and contains infinite suspense.<br/>
Cast: by Ralitza Petrova (Director), Ralitza Petrova (Screenplay) Cast: Snejanka Mihaylova, Nikola Mutafov, Mihail Milchev, Alexis Atmadjov<br/>
Durata: 77 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/media/filmstills/2026/plakate-2026/202616069_9_ORG.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Mon Feb 16 18:30 - Colosseum 1, Wed Feb 18 15:00 - Delphi Filmpalast, Fri Feb 20 21:00 - Cinema Paris, Sat Feb 21 22:15 - Cubix 8]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202616069.html</guid></item><item><title>Una mujer fantástica by Sebastián Lelio</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202616096.html</link><description><![CDATA[Marina and Orlando are in love and plan to spend their lives together. She is working as a waitress and adores singing. Her lover, twenty years her senior, has left his family for her. One night, when they return home after having exuberantly celebrated Marina&rsquo;s birthday at a restaurant, Orlando suddenly turns deathly pale and stops responding. At the hospital, all the doctors can do is confirm his death. Events follow thick and fast: Marina finds herself facing a female police inspector&rsquo;s unpleasant questions, and Orlando&rsquo;s family shows her nothing but anger and mistrust. Orlando&rsquo;s wife excludes Marina from the funeral; she also orders her to leave the apartment &ndash; which on paper at least belonged to Orlando &ndash; as soon as possible. Marina is a transgender woman. The deceased&rsquo;s family feels threatened by her sexual identity. With the same energy she once used to fight for her right to live as a woman, Marina, with her head held high, now insists on her right to grieve. Even if her environment conspires against her, the film at least is entirely on her side, showing us a protagonist who, although increasingly sidelined, is nonetheless strong and worldly-wise &ndash; a truly fantastic woman.<br/>
Cast: by Sebastián Lelio (Director), Sebastián Lelio (Screenplay) Cast: Daniela Vega, Francisco Reyes, Luis Gnecco, Aline Kuppenheim, Nicolas Saavedra, Amparo Noguera, Nestor Cantillana, Alejandro Goic, Antonia Zegers, Sergio Hernandez<br/>
Durata: 104 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202616096_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Tue Feb 17 22:00 - Zoo Palast 2, Wed Feb 18 16:00 - Deutsche Kinemathek – Halle]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202616096.html</guid></item><item><title>Yön Lapsi by Hanna Bergholm</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202616114.html</link><description><![CDATA[With dreams of starting a perfect family, Saga and her British husband Jon move to the isolated house deep in the Finnish forest where Saga spent much of her childhood. But as soon as their baby is born, despite the reassurances of everyone around her, Saga knows something is terribly wrong. As their marriage starts to crack and Jon struggles to support his wife, only Saga suspects the disturbing truth about their newborn child.<br/>
Cast: by Hanna Bergholm (Director), Ilja Rautsi (Screenplay) Cast: Seidi Haarla, Rupert Grint, Pamela Tola, Pirkko Saisio, Rebecca Lacey, John Thomson<br/>
Durata: 92 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202616114_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sat Feb 14 22:00 - Berlinale Palast, Sun Feb 15 15:00 - Uber Eats Music Hall, Mon Feb 16 13:00 - Urania, Wed Feb 18 21:30 - Haus der Berliner Festspiele]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202616114.html</guid></item><item><title>Black Lions – Roman Wolves by Haile Gerima</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202616228.html</link><description><![CDATA[In 1896, Ethiopia gained victory over Italy, hitting back at its first attempt to conquer the East African country. When Mussolini and the fascists came to power in 1922, the still abstract risk of a further attack became concrete. In 1935, Italy began an assault on Ethiopia once again, subjecting the country to a brutal war, not shying away from the use of poisonous gas: a crime, paradoxically, at once omnipresent and barely remembered in today&rsquo;s Italy. Haile Gerima, veteran of the L.A. Rebellion and New Black Cinema, worked for 30 years on his monumental exploration of the history and mythology of Italian colonialism, and also commemoration of the Ethiopian resistance. From archive material, conversations with historical witnesses and his father&rsquo;s plays, he weaves together a panorama of self-affirmation and colonial murder, of European complicity and Black solidarity. <em class="film">Black Lions &ndash; Roman Wolves</em> sets Ethiopian voices against lasting colonialist lies &ndash; and the recordings of the resistance against the reproduction of colonial images; against the entrenched visual dominance of the colonisers. A film for the present as well as for the coming decades.<br/>
Cast: by Haile Gerima (Director), Haile Gerima (Screenplay)<br/>
Durata: 531 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202616228_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Mon Feb 16 15:00 - Delphi Filmpalast, Tue Feb 17 16:00 - Delphi Filmpalast, Wed Feb 18 10:00 - CinemaxX 9, Wed Feb 18 14:30 - CinemaxX 9]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202616228.html</guid></item><item><title>Ang Pagdadalaga ni Maximo Oliveros by Kanakan-Balintagos</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202616555.html</link><description><![CDATA[This film pits the purity of first love against the poverty and corruption that dominate the slums of Manila. The Philippine capital is home to twelve-year-old Maxi, who comes from a poor family. Maxi cleans the house, cooks, washes clothes and repairs tattered jeans for his relatives, who are all petty thieves. He even supplies them with the odd alibi, when needed. Maxi&rsquo;s homosexuality is accepted by his nearest and dearest. Loved and protected by his relatives, he has a calming influence on the family and is the one in charge of the day-to-day running of the household. Things are working out fine until Maxi meets Victor, a respected and principled policeman who awakens his dreams of a better life &ndash; on the straight and narrow. This is a recipe for disaster as far as the family is concerned, and it is not long before the situation incurs the wrath of Maxi&rsquo;s father, brothers and sisters.<br/>
Cast: by Kanakan-Balintagos (Director), Michiko Yamamoto (Screenplay) Cast: Nathan Lopez<br/>
Durata: 100 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202616555_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Wed Feb 18 22:00 - Zoo Palast 2, Thu Feb 19 16:00 - Deutsche Kinemathek – Halle]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202616555.html</guid></item><item><title>A Family by Mees Peijnenburg</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202616575.html</link><description><![CDATA[Fourteen-year-old Eli and 16-year-old Nina are both suffering in the breakdown of their parents&rsquo; once loving marriage. In the battle for custody, the siblings must express their wishes, fears and feelings to a judge. While Nina wants to get away from the family as soon as possible, Eli longs for everything to return to how it was before. Their desires are miles apart. Told in two chapters, the film follows the same three weeks twice: first from Nina&rsquo;s perspective and then from Eli&rsquo;s. These mirrored timelines reveal how the same moments can be lived, felt and understood in entirely different ways. Eli and Nina retreat into their own isolated worlds until Nina begins to realise that her younger brother has been carrying the same weight all along, quietly, invisibly, beside her. He has always been there; it is only now that she is truly seeing him. Eli, meanwhile, comes to understand that Nina&rsquo;s turning away from him was not a rejection but an act of survival and she has been struggling as much as he has. Beneath their opposing choices lies the same longing: for love, recognition and emotional security. <em class="film">A Family</em> reveals how love can fracture under pressure but still find its way back home.<br/>
Cast: by Mees Peijnenburg (Director), Bastiaan Kroeger (Screenplay) Cast: Finn Vogels, Celeste Holsheimer, Carice van Houten, Pieter Embrechts<br/>
Durata: 89 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202616575_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sun Feb 15 12:30 - Zoo Palast 1, Mon Feb 16 16:00 - HKW 1 - Miriam Makeba Auditorium, Tue Feb 17 18:45 - Filmtheater am Friedrichshain, Wed Feb 18 10:15 - Cubix 6, Sat Feb 21 19:45 - HKW 1 - Miriam Makeba Auditorium]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202616575.html</guid></item><item><title>The Story of Documentary Film by Mark Cousins</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202616639.html</link><description><![CDATA[<em class="film">The Story of Documentary Film</em> traces the history of documentary from its very beginnings to the present day. Drawing on Mark Cousins&rsquo; decades of research, the series re-examines classics of the genre including <em class="film-other">Hoop Dreams</em>, <em class="film-other">The Gleaners and I</em>, <em class="film-other">Shoah</em>, <em class="film-other">Stop Making Sense</em> and <em class="film-other">Paris Is Burning</em>. Alongside these celebrated films, it introduces audiences to striking new discoveries and overlooked works from across the globe, with a spotlight on the many great female filmmakers who have too often been written out of the history of documentary filmmaking. Structured chronologically, but interspersed with stand-alone thematic sections, the series challenges prevailing assumptions about what documentary is, offering a captivating new perspective on the history of a form that continues to shape how we understand the world around us. The Berlinale is presenting Chapters 1 to 4 of the film, with this screening being the world premiere of Chapters 2, 3 and 4.<br/>
Cast: by Mark Cousins (Director)<br/>
Durata: 240 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202616639_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Fri Feb 13 11:15 - ADK am Hanseatenweg, Wed Feb 18 18:00 - CinemaxX 7]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202616639.html</guid></item><item><title>Vier minus drei by Adrian Goiginger</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202616642.html</link><description><![CDATA[Barbara and her partner Heli lead a happy and loving family life with their two children, Fini and Thimo. As professional clowns, they do not take life too seriously and try to laugh at whatever fails to work out. But when Barbara suddenly loses her family to a car accident, her world falls apart. The loss makes her question her existence as a clown and the meaning of her own life. Yet Barbara confronts her fate. Courageous and unconventional, she finds her own way of dealing with her grief. Step by step, she realises that life goes on despite everything &ndash; if you dare to embrace it anew.<br/>
Cast: by Adrian Goiginger (Director), Senad Halilbašić (Screenplay) Cast: Valerie Pachner, Robert Stadlober, Stefanie Reinsperger, Hanno Koffler, Margarethe Tiesel, Paul Wolff-Plottegg, Michael Gampe, Petra Morzé, Michael Fuith, Ronald Zehrfeld<br/>
Durata: 121 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202616642_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Mon Feb 16 18:00 - Zoo Palast 1, Tue Feb 17 10:45 - Haus der Berliner Festspiele, Wed Feb 18 21:45 - Cubix 7, Fri Feb 20 16:45 - Kino Casablanca, Sat Feb 21 10:00 - Cubix 9, Sun Feb 22 15:00 - Urania]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202616642.html</guid></item><item><title>Saccharine by Natalie Erika James</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202616696.html</link><description><![CDATA[When first-year medical student Hana runs into an old friend who has lost so much weight she is almost unrecognisable, Hana is introduced to the world of weight-loss pills. Her quest for a slimmer body is spurred on by her crush, Alanya, a fitness influencer and personal trainer at Hana&rsquo;s university gym, who convinces her to take part in a twelve-week &ldquo;body transformation&rdquo; programme. Unable to afford the expensive pills, Hana brings one of the samples she has been given free-of-charge to the university lab. She tests the pills and makes a surprising discovery about their contents that leads her to begin stealing bones from the cadaver she is dissecting in her anatomy class. And while the pills seem to be very effective, and her body shrinks, Hana quickly finds herself being haunted by a ghost that grows in size and strength as her waistline slims.<br/>
Cast: by Natalie Erika James (Director), Natalie Erika James (Screenplay) Cast: Midori Francis, Danielle Macdonald, Madeleine Madden, Robert Taylor, Showko Showfukutei<br/>
Durata: 112 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202616696_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Wed Feb 18 21:45 - Zoo Palast 1, Thu Feb 19 22:00 - HKW 1 - Miriam Makeba Auditorium, Fri Feb 20 22:00 - Haus der Berliner Festspiele, Sun Feb 22 22:15 - Uber Eats Music Hall]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202616696.html</guid></item><item><title>Berlinale Camera for Max Richter</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202616698.html</link><description><![CDATA[One of the most influential composers and sound artists of his generation, Max Richter is celebrated for his ability to seamlessly blend classical composition techniques with electronic elements. With his unique talent for translating profound human experiences into music, Richter has redefined the standards of cinematic composition. His scores for international productions such as <em class="film-other">Waltz with Bashir</em>, <em class="film-other">Ad Astra</em>, <em class="film-other">Mary Queen of Scots</em> and <em class="film-other">Spaceman</em> enrich the visual narrative with a sonic dimension that deepens moods and renders inner emotions audible.
 The festival is honouring Max Richter with the Berlinale Camera in recognition of his outstanding contributions at the intersection of music, cinema and cultural reflection. The laudatory speech is being delivered by Oscar-winning director Chlo&eacute; Zhao, with whom Richter recently collaborated on her latest film, <em class="film-other">Hamnet</em>. In the subsequent onstage discussion, Max Richter will use practical examples to offer insights into his creative process and collaborations with other artists in film and art.<br/>
Durata: 75 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202616698_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Wed Feb 18 16:30 - Haus der Berliner Festspiele]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202616698.html</guid></item><item><title>Composer’s Talk with Daniel Blumberg</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202616898.html</link><description><![CDATA[Academy Award&ndash;winning composer Daniel Blumberg (<em class="film-other">The Brutalist</em>) has built a career by trusting instinct over certainty. His music begins in a place of raw emotion, leaning into tension and unpredictability, where discomfort becomes part of the creative spark. His scores, most recently for <em class="film-other">The Testament of Ann Lee</em> (in <em class="program">Berlinale Special</em>), are opening space for feelings that are often difficult to frame. In this conversation, Daniel dives into his musical curiosity, exploring his love for improvisation, and his willingness to get lost in the process, shaping a body of work that thrives on chaos and confusion, and the surprising clarity that can emerge from both.<br/>
Durata: 90 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202616898_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Wed Feb 18 14:00 - Radialsystem]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202616898.html</guid></item><item><title>The Power of Discomfort: Crafting Sentimental Value</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202616899.html</link><description><![CDATA[Academy Award-nominated editor Olivier Bugge&nbsp;Coutt&eacute;&nbsp;and <em class="program">Berlinale Talents</em> alum Eskil Vogt discuss their collaboration with Joachim Trier, another alum of <em class="program">Berlinale Talents</em>, on <em class="film-other">Sentimental Value</em>. The film earned nine Academy Award nominations, including Best Editing for Olivier and Best Original Screenplay for Eskil and Joachim Trier. Their conversation focuses on filmmaking as a space of productive confusion, where discomfort sharpens&nbsp;perception&nbsp;and opens new ways of seeing.&nbsp;<br/>
Durata: 90 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202616899_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Wed Feb 18 17:00 - Radialsystem]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202616899.html</guid></item><item><title>Chloé Zhao – In Conversation</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202617101.html</link><description><![CDATA[Chlo&eacute; Zhao, Oscar winning director of <em class="film-other">Nomadland</em>, is known for her intimate, naturalistic storytelling and her focus on overlooked communities and emotional fractures. With <em class="film-other">Hamnet</em>, her acclaimed drama on the love and loss of Shakespeare&rsquo;s family, she deepens her exploration of rupture and transformation. The film won the Golden Globe for Best Picture, Drama and has earned eight Oscar nominations and eleven BAFTA nominations. She joins <em class="program">Berlinale Talents</em> to discuss her career thus far from <em class="film-other">Songs My Brothers Taught Me</em> through to <em class="film-other">Hamnet</em>, and reflect on how this year&rsquo;s theme of embracing chaos and discomfort has impacted her work.<br/>
Durata: 60 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202617101_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Wed Feb 18 12:00 - Radialsystem]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202617101.html</guid></item><item><title>Lost in the 90s #1</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/2026332940.html</link><description><![CDATA[Durata: 121 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/_platzhalter.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Mon Feb 16 15:00 - Cubix 5, Wed Feb 18 19:00 - Deutsche Kinemathek – Halle, Sun Feb 22 12:30 - Deutsche Kinemathek – Halle]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/2026332940.html</guid></item><item><title>Borderlining</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/2026333840.html</link><description><![CDATA[Durata: 119 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/_platzhalter.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Wed Feb 18 21:30 - ADK am Hanseatenweg, Sun Feb 22 16:30 - ADK am Hanseatenweg]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/2026333840.html</guid></item><item><title>14plus Short Films 1</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/2026334530.html</link><description><![CDATA[Durata: 127 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/_platzhalter.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Tue Feb 17 12:30 - Urania, Wed Feb 18 19:15 - Cubix 6, Thu Feb 19 10:00 - Bluemax Theater, Fri Feb 20 12:45 - Filmtheater am Friedrichshain, Sun Feb 22 15:15 - Zoo Palast 2]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/2026334530.html</guid></item><item><title>14plus Short Films 2</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/2026334950.html</link><description><![CDATA[Durata: 135 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/_platzhalter.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Wed Feb 18 12:30 - Urania, Thu Feb 19 19:15 - Cubix 6, Fri Feb 20 10:00 - Bluemax Theater, Sat Feb 21 15:45 - Filmtheater am Friedrichshain, Sun Feb 22 12:30 - Zoo Palast 2]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/2026334950.html</guid></item><item><title>Kplus Short Films 3</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/2026335050.html</link><description><![CDATA[Durata: 109 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/_platzhalter.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Mon Feb 16 09:30 - Zoo Palast 1, Tue Feb 17 10:00 - Zoo Palast 2, Wed Feb 18 18:45 - Filmtheater am Friedrichshain, Fri Feb 20 16:15 - Cubix 6, Sun Feb 22 12:45 - Filmtheater am Friedrichshain]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/2026335050.html</guid></item><item><title>Kplus Short Films 2</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/2026335220.html</link><description><![CDATA[Durata: 123 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/_platzhalter.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Wed Feb 18 09:30 - Zoo Palast 1, Thu Feb 19 10:00 - Zoo Palast 2, Fri Feb 20 13:15 - Cubix 6, Sat Feb 21 10:00 - Zoo Palast 2, Sun Feb 22 15:45 - Filmtheater am Friedrichshain]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/2026335220.html</guid></item><item><title>Kplus Short Films 1</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/2026335360.html</link><description><![CDATA[Durata: 98 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/_platzhalter.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Tue Feb 17 09:30 - Zoo Palast 1, Wed Feb 18 12:45 - Filmtheater am Friedrichshain, Fri Feb 20 09:45 - Filmtheater am Friedrichshain, Sat Feb 21 10:15 - Cubix 6, Sun Feb 22 13:30 - Cubix 6]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/2026335360.html</guid></item><item><title>Programme 7</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/2026336180.html</link><description><![CDATA[Durata: 123 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/_platzhalter.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Mon Feb 16 21:00 - Cinema Betonhalle@Silent Green, Wed Feb 18 15:30 - Cinema Betonhalle@Silent Green]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/2026336180.html</guid></item><item><title>Programme 11</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/2026336230.html</link><description><![CDATA[Durata: 54 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/_platzhalter.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Wed Feb 18 20:30 - Cinema Betonhalle@Silent Green]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/2026336230.html</guid></item><item><title>Programme 10</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/2026336440.html</link><description><![CDATA[Durata: 123 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/_platzhalter.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Wed Feb 18 18:00 - Delphi Filmpalast, Fri Feb 20 18:30 - Cinema Betonhalle@Silent Green]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/2026336440.html</guid></item><item><title>Berlinale Shorts 1</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/2026339670.html</link><description><![CDATA[Durata: 85 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/_platzhalter.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sat Feb 14 09:30 - Cubix 5, Sun Feb 15 18:15 - Urania, Mon Feb 16 21:30 - Colosseum 1, Tue Feb 17 16:00 - Zoo Palast 2, Wed Feb 18 16:30 - Cubix 8, Fri Feb 20 12:00 - Cinema Betonhalle@Silent Green]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/2026339670.html</guid></item><item><title>Berlinale Shorts 3</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/2026339830.html</link><description><![CDATA[Durata: 91 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/_platzhalter.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sat Feb 14 13:10 - Cubix 5, Tue Feb 17 18:15 - Urania, Wed Feb 18 12:00 - Cinema Betonhalle@Silent Green, Wed Feb 18 19:00 - Colosseum 1, Thu Feb 19 16:00 - Zoo Palast 2, Sun Feb 22 16:30 - Cubix 8]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/2026339830.html</guid></item><item><title>Berlinale Shorts 4</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/2026339900.html</link><description><![CDATA[Durata: 89 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/_platzhalter.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sat Feb 14 15:10 - Cubix 5, Wed Feb 18 18:15 - Urania, Thu Feb 19 11:00 - Cinema Betonhalle@Silent Green, Thu Feb 19 19:00 - Colosseum 1, Fri Feb 20 16:00 - Zoo Palast 2, Sat Feb 21 13:30 - Cubix 8]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/2026339900.html</guid></item><item><title>Berlinale Shorts 2</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/2026340010.html</link><description><![CDATA[Durata: 85 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/_platzhalter.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sat Feb 14 11:20 - Cubix 5, Mon Feb 16 18:15 - Urania, Tue Feb 17 12:00 - Cinema Betonhalle@Silent Green, Tue Feb 17 18:30 - Colosseum 1, Wed Feb 18 16:00 - Zoo Palast 2, Thu Feb 19 16:30 - Cubix 8]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/2026340010.html</guid></item></channel></rss>