<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Berlinale - Berlin International Film Festival</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/programme/on-sale-from-today.html</link><description>Films in the Berlinale programme (on sale / in programme).</description><item><title>The Education of Jane Cumming by Sophie Heldman</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202601323.html</link><description><![CDATA[Edinburgh, 1810. Teachers Jane Pirie and Marianne Woods embark on their dream of an independent life together and open a boarding school. Their lives are changed forever when a wealthy aristocrat enrols Jane Cumming, her &ldquo;illegitimate&rdquo;&nbsp;15-year-old grandchild from India. The teachers struggle to integrate the girl who remains an outsider among her classmates. Miss Pirie and Miss Woods are brought closer to Jane when her grandmother insists they look after her over the summer. Private and professional lines blur, affection between them grows and they start to form an unlikely family. Tensions rise, however, as the new term begins. The two teachers are overwhelmed by the girl&rsquo;s increasing desire for closeness as well as by their own changing relationship. As Jane begins to feel excluded from her new family, she demands to be taken home to her grandmother. An accusation follows which leaves the teachers in an existential battle, resulting in a legal fight that would last a decade and scandalise the Scottish establishment. Based on true events.<br/>
Cast: by Sophie Heldman (Director), Sophie Heldman (Screenplay) Cast: Flora Nicholson, Clare Dunne, Mia Tharia, Fiona Shaw, Sadie Shimmin<br/>
Durata: 114 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/media/filmstills/2026/plakate-2026/202601323_9_RWD_1920.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sun Feb 15 18:15 - Zoo Palast 1, Mon Feb 16 10:45 - Haus der Berliner Festspiele, Tue Feb 17 21:45 - Cubix 7, Thu Feb 19 21:30 - Urania, Sun Feb 22 18:45 - Cubix 9]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202601323.html</guid></item><item><title>Traces by Marysia Nikitiuk</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202601639.html</link><description><![CDATA[The film shines a light on Ukrainian women who, after surviving conflict-related sexual violence and torture during the Russian war of aggression, refuse to remain silent. Through the journey of Iryna Dovhan, a former captive turned activist who documents testimonies of affected women in the de-occupied territories of Ukraine, the film weaves a portrait of a collective trauma while opening space for hope. Iryna gathers other survivors into a circle of courage and care. Together, they transform their pain into a force for truth, justice and mutual support. More than a record of war crimes, <em class="film">Traces</em> is a testament to resilience and the solidarity of women standing side by side.<br/>
Cast: by Alisa Kovalenko (Screenplay) Cast: Iryna Dovhan, Tetiana Vasylenko, Liudmyla Mefodiivna, Galyna Tyshchenko, Olha Cherniak, Nina<br/>
Durata: 85 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202601639_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Mon Feb 16 17:30 - Haus der Berliner Festspiele, Tue Feb 17 15:30 - Urania, Wed Feb 18 10:00 - Cubix 7, Sat Feb 21 17:50 - Cubix 7, Sun Feb 22 22:30 - Cubix 5]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202601639.html</guid></item><item><title>El Tren Fluvial</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202602169.html</link><description><![CDATA[Nine-year-old Milo is growing up with the pressure to become a great Malambo dancer and the &ldquo;perfect&rdquo; son. He dreams of taking control of his life and escaping his responsibilities of washing dishes, cooking and practicing the Malambo at night. Milo wants another life. He fantasises about travelling by train and exploring the city of Buenos Aires, which he has seen so many times in the movies and on television. However, in order to break free from his family and the countryside, and make his big dreams come true, he must dare to take a new journey: a journey into solitude, and the unknown adventures and pleasures of the big city.<br/>
Cast: by Lorenzo Ferro (Screenplay) Cast: Milo Barria, Rita Pauls, Mariano Barria, Fabián Casas, Lucrecia Pazos, Pehuen Pedre, Mailén Barría, Diego Puente<br/>
Durata: 75 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/media/filmstills/2026/plakate-2026/202602169_9_RWD_1920.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Mon Feb 16 19:00 - Bluemax Theater, Tue Feb 17 16:00 - Cubix 9, Wed Feb 18 22:15 - Cubix 8, Fri Feb 20 13:00 - Colosseum 1, Sun Feb 22 14:30 - Cubix 9]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202602169.html</guid></item><item><title>Tristan Forever</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202602348.html</link><description><![CDATA[For thirty years, Loran Bonnardot, a doctor from Paris, has been visiting Tristan da Cunha, the world&rsquo;s remotest inhabited island, in the middle of the South Atlantic. The volcanic island has become Loran&rsquo;s spiritual refuge, its inhabitants his chosen family and the fisherman Martin his best friend. Now, at the age of 50, Loran takes the boat once more but this time he does not plan to return: he wants to become one of the 230 permanent residents &ndash; no easy endeavour since the island council will decide whether or not to accept him. Meanwhile, his friend Martin has his own point of view and Loran himself is confronted by his lifelong search for solitude. <em class="film">Tristan Forever</em> is a journey to a utopia far beyond the horizon. A film that pursues the question of where one&rsquo;s soul belongs, oscillating between documentary, fiction and the dreams of its protagonist.&nbsp;&nbsp;<br/>
Cast: by Tobias Nölle (Screenplay) Cast: Loran Bonnardot, Martin Green, Glenda Rogers<br/>
Durata: 90 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202602348_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sun Feb 15 13:00 - Bluemax Theater, Mon Feb 16 16:00 - Cubix 7, Tue Feb 17 22:00 - Cubix 6, Sat Feb 21 11:45 - Cubix 7, Sun Feb 22 12:15 - Cubix 7]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202602348.html</guid></item><item><title>The Lights, They Fall by Saša Vajda</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202602524.html</link><description><![CDATA[Sixteen-year-old Ilay aimlessly drifts through the outskirts of Berlin. His mother, Maria, lies on her deathbed, cared for by Ana, a Mexican palliative nurse. Refusing to accept his mother&rsquo;s impending death, Ilay retreats further into himself, increasingly shutting himself off from reality. Through slow, contemplative images, the film follows Ilay and Ana in their daily routines, from Ana&rsquo;s quiet dedication to Maria&rsquo;s care to her struggles with her own addiction. Ilay works in a logistics centre, does community service and spends his afternoons hanging out with his friends at a lake. At night, he is restless, wandering the city in a sleepless daze like a ghost. During one of his nocturnal outings, he impulsively steals a dog, prompting Ana to take him to a psychologist. There, Ilay reveals his deep-seated belief in the impossibility of death. As his mother&rsquo;s passing approaches, it becomes less an inevitability and more a matter of mystery and speculation.<br/>
Cast: by Saša Vajda (Director), Saša Vajda (Screenplay) Cast: Mohammed Yassin Ben Majdouba, Flor Prieto Catemaxca, Mahira Hakberdieva, Safet Bajraj, Shanthi Philipp, Solomon Guye, Mahir Özel<br/>
Durata: 87 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202602524_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sat Feb 14 12:30 - Zoo Palast 1, Sun Feb 15 19:15 - Cubix 6, Mon Feb 16 16:00 - Zoo Palast 2, Tue Feb 17 09:45 - Filmtheater am Friedrichshain, Sun Feb 22 18:45 - HKW 1 - Miriam Makeba Auditorium]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202602524.html</guid></item><item><title>Auslandsreise by Ted Fendt</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202602774.html</link><description><![CDATA[In his fourth feature, Ted Fendt once again creates a portrait of a set of people linked together by friendship. At its heart is Leonie, who spends a year going through the texts of Anna Maria Ortese. A loose reading group consisting of Florian, Alejo and Hanna joins her in her endeavour. Different seasons and thoughts duly unfold around Berlin&rsquo;s Chamissoplatz. Fendt shines a spotlight on many small narratives and allows fleeting moments to manifest, captured on 16mm stock at once glowing and matter-of-fact. Florian looks for a flat without success, Alejo has moved from Argentina to Berlin, Hanna is soon to be a mother. Anna Maria Ortese&rsquo;s books form vanishing points that simultaneously function as an invitation to reflect: Who likes to be led up the garden path by literature? How do realism and fantasy merge? In the meantime, a long conversation between Leonie and Ortese translator Sigrid Vagt becomes the film&rsquo;s centrepiece, making the mysterious author tangible and spurring Leonie on. <em class="film">Auslandsreise</em> shows a search that takes place in caf&eacute;s and courtyards, in sentences both spoken and written. Everyday life and literature intertwine. A distillation of life.<br/>
Cast: by Ted Fendt (Director), Ted Fendt (Screenplay) Cast: Leonie Rodrian, Florian Model, Alejo Franzetti, Hanna Döring, Mia Sellmann, Sigrid Vagt<br/>
Durata: 63 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/media/filmstills/2026/plakate-2026/202602774_9_ORG.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sun Feb 15 20:30 - Cinema Paris, Tue Feb 17 13:30 - Cubix 8, Sat Feb 21 21:30 - Delphi Filmpalast]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202602774.html</guid></item><item><title>Isabel by Gabe Klinger</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202602856.html</link><description><![CDATA[Isabel, a sommeli&egrave;re in S&atilde;o Paulo&rsquo;s fine-dining scene, dreams of escaping her controlling boss and opening her own wine bar where she decides what goes in the glass. When her plans fail to ferment as expected, Isabel must decide between playing it safe and taking her one bold chance to uncork her destiny on her own terms.<br/>
Cast: by Gabe Klinger (Director), Gabe Klinger (Screenplay) Cast: Marina Person, Caio Horowicz, John Ortiz<br/>
Durata: 85 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/media/filmstills/2026/plakate-2026/202602856_9_RWD_1920.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Mon Feb 16 21:30 - Urania, Tue Feb 17 10:00 - Cubix 9, Wed Feb 18 13:30 - ADK am Hanseatenweg, Thu Feb 19 13:15 - Cubix 6, Fri Feb 20 22:00 - Cubix 6]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202602856.html</guid></item><item><title>Truly Naked by Muriel d’Ansembourg</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202602884.html</link><description><![CDATA[Alec, a soft-spoken, introverted teenager, has always viewed life through the lens of his father&rsquo;s small-time pornography business where their home doubles as a set. Since his mother&rsquo;s death, Alec has been drawn deeper into the family business and he now films and edits the content that his rough and ready father, Dylan, produces and stars in. As an ageing performer, Dylan is struggling to keep things afloat and relies on girls such as Lizzie, a free-spirited adult entertainer who has become something like an older sister to Alec. As financial pressures mount, Dylan&rsquo;s swagger begins to unravel, exposing Alec to the growing chaos around him. When the father and son relocate from London to a sleepy seaside town, Alec hopes for a fresh start and tries to make new friends without revealing his unconventional life. Events take a turn when he meets classmate Nina, a fiercely independent and feminist young woman whose world view could not be further from the one that Alec grew up with. As their bond deepens, Nina invites Alec into a realm of intimacy and vulnerability that cannot be captured on camera and challenges him to explore what it means to be truly seen.<br/>
Cast: by Muriel d’Ansembourg (Director), Muriel d'Ansembourg (Screenplay) Cast: Caolán O'Gorman, Andrew Howard, Alessa Savage, Safiya Benaddi, Lyndsey Marshal<br/>
Durata: 102 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/media/filmstills/2026/plakate-2026/202602884_9_RWD_1920.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Mon Feb 16 21:30 - Bluemax Theater, Tue Feb 17 18:30 - Cubix 9, Wed Feb 18 13:00 - Cubix 9, Sat Feb 21 19:45 - Colosseum 1, Sun Feb 22 21:30 - Cubix 8]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202602884.html</guid></item><item><title>Staatsschutz by Faraz Shariat</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202603082.html</link><description><![CDATA[With all the resources and authority of the state behind her, young prosecutor Seyo Kim is determined to confront far-right violence in eastern Germany. But when she, herself, becomes a target &ndash; surviving a racist attack on her life &ndash; Seyo decides to investigate on her own, defying explicit orders from her superiors and putting her life further at risk. Seyo finally succeeds in bringing one of the attackers to trial and fights to expose him as part of a wider right-wing network. She digs deep into her office&rsquo;s archives, reopens long-closed &ldquo;isolated cases&rdquo; and manoeuvres seemingly harmless witnesses into revealing their ties &ndash; not only to the network but also to the attack on her own life. Germany&rsquo;s public prosecution service is the most objective institution in the world &ndash; or so the myth goes. But throughout the trial, Seyo learns firsthand what it means to entrust the pursuit of justice to a state that applies double standards and not only downplays far-right violence, but at times even protects it.<br/>
Cast: by Faraz Shariat (Director), Claudia Schaefer (Screenplay) Cast: Chen Emilie Yan, Julia Jentsch, Alev Irmak, Arnd Klawitter, Sebastian Urzendowsky<br/>
Durata: 113 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202603082_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sun Feb 15 21:30 - Zoo Palast 1, Mon Feb 16 13:00 - Cubix 7, Tue Feb 17 10:00 - ADK am Hanseatenweg, Fri Feb 20 13:00 - Bluemax Theater, Sat Feb 21 15:00 - Cubix 9]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202603082.html</guid></item><item><title>Ghost School by Seemab Gul</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202603120.html</link><description><![CDATA[Ten-year-old Rabia discovers that the only school in her village has closed. Rumour has it that the school is haunted and the teacher is possessed by a jinn. A fellow pupil brags that he is now going to a boys&rsquo; school in the neighbouring village. Jealous and confused, Rabia goes around asking the adults what is going on, but only receives vague responses. As the rumours about the haunted school take over the village, Rabia increasingly comes to doubt them. She dares the village kids to go into the school and exorcise the jinn. But this leads to devastating consequences. Ultimately, Rabia is left with the choice of either becoming a servant or doing something drastic to be able to go to school again. She decides to make a sacrifice, unleashing magical forces.<br/>
Cast: by Seemab Gul (Director), Seemab Gul (Screenplay) Cast: Nazualiya Arsalan, Samina Seher, Adnan Shah Tipu, Vajdaan Shah, Muhammad Zaman<br/>
Durata: 88 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/media/filmstills/2026/plakate-2026/202603120_9_RWD_1920.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sat Feb 14 15:00 - Cubix 6, Mon Feb 16 10:00 - HKW 1 - Miriam Makeba Auditorium, Tue Feb 17 13:00 - Zoo Palast 2, Wed Feb 18 16:15 - Cubix 6, Fri Feb 20 15:45 - Filmtheater am Friedrichshain, Sun Feb 22 10:00 - Zoo Palast 2]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202603120.html</guid></item><item><title>What Will I Become? by Lexie Bean</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202603286.html</link><description><![CDATA[According to the American Academy of Pediatrics, more than half of trans boys attempt suicide. Directors Lexie Bean and Logan Rozos explore the vulnerability of their transmasculine community. They delve into their own personal experiences, intertwining them with the stories of two young trans men who died by suicide. Homecoming king Blake Brockington and soft-spoken Kyler Prescott were poets, musicians and community advocates. The film traces their joys and challenges, their tragic deaths and resulting media attention, as well as the larger aftermath within their communities. The film also uplifts resources that affirm trans boys and the LGBTQIA2S+ community to provide an understanding of suicide-prevention practices. <em class="film">What Will I Become?</em> asks why people from the transmasculine community are particularly vulnerable to living briefly and dying quietly.<br/>
Cast: by Lexie Bean (Director), Logan Rozos (Director)<br/>
Durata: 86 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202603286_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Tue Feb 17 16:00 - HKW 1 - Miriam Makeba Auditorium, Wed Feb 18 10:15 - Zoo Palast 2, Thu Feb 19 15:45 - Filmtheater am Friedrichshain, Fri Feb 20 13:00 - Zoo Palast 2, Sun Feb 22 09:45 - Filmtheater am Friedrichshain]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202603286.html</guid></item><item><title>The Weight by Padraic McKinley</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202604113.html</link><description><![CDATA[Oregon, 1933. Samuel Murphy is torn from his daughter and sent to a brutal work camp. Warden Clancy tempts him with early release if he smuggles gold through the deadly wilderness. How far will Murphy go to see his child again?
 Padraic McKinley&rsquo;s tense, atmospheric Depression-era drama follows a group of desperate convicts on a journey through a physically and morally treacherous backcountry. Set against the stark beauty of the Oregon landscape, <em class="film">The Weight</em> draws on the introspective action cinema of the 1970s to depict a gritty survivalist scenario supported by brothers Latham and Shelby Gaines&rsquo; score and Matteo Cocco&rsquo;s cinematography. Ethan Hawke gives a muscular performance as the film&rsquo;s reluctant but resourceful hero, while Russell Crowe is quietly menacing as his foil. Julia Jones brings dignity and defiance to her role as Anna, the sole woman in the group.<br/>
Cast: by Padraic McKinley (Director), Matthew Booi (Screenplay) Cast: Ethan Hawke, Russell Crowe, Julia Jones, Austin Amelio, Avi Nash<br/>
Durata: 115 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202604113_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Tue Feb 17 21:30 - Zoo Palast 1, Wed Feb 18 22:00 - HKW 1 - Miriam Makeba Auditorium, Thu Feb 19 12:45 - Uber Eats Music Hall, Sat Feb 21 10:00 - ADK am Hanseatenweg]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202604113.html</guid></item><item><title>Douglas Gordon by Douglas Gordon by Finlay Pretsell</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202604430.html</link><description><![CDATA[Douglas Gordon grew up in Glasgow, Scotland during the economically and politically grim era of Margaret Thatcher and is among the most important and influential artists of his generation. He is best known for his large-scale video installations and films such as the Turner Prize winning <em class="film-other">24 Hour Psycho</em>, and <em class="film-other">Zidane: A 21st Century Portrait</em>, which premiered at Cannes. In this unsparingly honest and intimate portrait, which tests the boundaries between reality and performance, the artist bares his soul and innermost thoughts whilst making new work. In spontaneous acts and conversations, he reflects on his advancing years. As the filmmaker-subject relationship shifts from collaborative intimacy to a more complex dynamic, the question increasingly arises: Who actually is making this film? This multifaceted portrait bears witness to the fact that Douglas Gordon is ready to sacrifice everything for his art.<br/>
Cast: by Finlay Pretsell (Director) Cast: Douglas Gordon<br/>
Durata: 88 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/media/filmstills/2026/plakate-2026/202604430_9_RWD_1920.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Tue Feb 17 17:30 - Haus der Berliner Festspiele, Wed Feb 18 15:30 - Urania, Thu Feb 19 10:15 - Cubix 7, Fri Feb 20 10:45 - Colosseum 1, Sat Feb 21 20:15 - Cubix 7]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202604430.html</guid></item><item><title>Bucks Harbor by Pete Muller</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202604750.html</link><description><![CDATA[Downeast Maine is a narrow stretch of rugged coastline chiselled between the forest and the sea. Here, boys are shaped by the brutal winters, their harvesting of the ocean&rsquo;s bounty and the rigid codes of their fathers. <em class="film">Bucks Harbor</em> explores the inner lives of these fishermen, young and old, and the emotional complexity of growing up in a community where a man&rsquo;s worth is often defined by the strength of his back. The lobsters they hunt, deep on the ocean floor, serve as a metaphor for the adversity, survival and guarded vulnerability on land.<br/>
Cast: by Pete Muller (Director)<br/>
Durata: 98 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202604750_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sat Feb 14 13:00 - Bluemax Theater, Sun Feb 15 22:00 - Cubix 6, Tue Feb 17 17:00 - BALI KINO, Wed Feb 18 15:45 - Filmtheater am Friedrichshain, Fri Feb 20 10:00 - Cubix 9, Sun Feb 22 18:15 - Cubix 7]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202604750.html</guid></item><item><title>Chicas Tristes by Fernanda Tovar</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202604753.html</link><description><![CDATA[Paula and La Maestra are 16 and inseparable. The strongest swimmers on their team, they are training together over the summer to represent Mexico at the Junior Pan American Swimming Championships. One night at a party, Paula ends up alone with Daniel, a good friend and her long-time crush. Amid reggaeton, flirting and shots, Paula and Daniel slip into the bathroom together. Soon after, La Maestra senses that something has changed. Paula seems distant and deeply sad. At first, she insists nothing is wrong, but La Maestra keeps pushing until her friend begins to talk about what happened that night. Searching for answers, they try to name the experience, and what they find feels devastating. As the two girls respond in different ways, their bond is put to the test. Paula needs time, while La Maestra feels compelled to speak out. Fear, feelings of guilt and anger begin to fracture their friendship, pushing them towards a decision that will redefine who they are, together and apart.<br/>
Cast: by Fernanda Tovar (Director), Fernanda Tovar (Screenplay) Cast: Rocio Guzmán, Darana Álvarez, Tatsumi Milori, Tomás García-Agraz, Mónica del Carmen, Raúl Villegas, Lucio Lemus, Luisa Almaguer, Andrea Camacho, Áyax, Óscar Lever, Mario Flores, Héctor Kuri, Daniel Aranzubia<br/>
Durata: 90 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202604753_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sat Feb 14 09:30 - Cubix 6, Sat Feb 14 20:00 - HKW 1 - Miriam Makeba Auditorium, Mon Feb 16 10:15 - Cubix 6, Tue Feb 17 12:30 - Zoo Palast 1, Thu Feb 19 13:00 - Zoo Palast 2, Sat Feb 21 18:45 - Filmtheater am Friedrichshain]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202604753.html</guid></item><item><title>Where To? by Assaf Machnes</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202604888.html</link><description><![CDATA[In the endless Berlin nights, Hassan, a 55-year-old Palestinian Uber driver, shuttles night owls from one party to the next. Estranged from his eldest daughter, who is determined to marry her German boyfriend, Hassan often finds himself driving the streets without any sense of purpose. One night, Amir, a 25-year-old Israeli tourist who is exploring his sexual identity far away from home, stumbles into Hassan&rsquo;s cab. Months later, Amir makes a reappearance. He is now living in Berlin and suffering from heartbreak after the tortuous end of a love affair. As their rides together recur across two years, Hassan begins to recognise echoes of his own buried pain in Amir&rsquo;s struggles. Eventually, their late-night journeys help Hassan to confront his own past &ndash; including the events that led him to leaving his homeland 30 years ago.<br/>
Cast: by Assaf Machnes (Director), Assaf Machnes (Screenplay) Cast: Ehab Salami, Ido Tako, Milan Peschel, Rama Nasrallah, Raheeq Haj Yahia-Suleiman, Dov Navon, Sarit Vino Elad, Enzo Brumm<br/>
Durata: 95 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202604888_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Tue Feb 17 19:00 - Bluemax Theater, Wed Feb 18 16:00 - Cubix 9, Thu Feb 19 22:15 - Cubix 8, Sat Feb 21 12:45 - Colosseum 1, Sun Feb 22 12:15 - Cubix 9]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202604888.html</guid></item><item><title>Rumaragasa by Ryan Machado</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202604970.html</link><description><![CDATA[The lush but troubled landscape of mid-1990s Sibuyan Island in the Philippines. Eli is a reserved young man carrying the weight of a trauma that his community refuses to acknowledge. After surviving a sexual assault by a peer, an event dismissed by local authorities and friends as nothing more than rough play, he retreats into a world of silence and isolation. When he witnesses a mysterious plane crash in the island&rsquo;s densely forested mountains, his attempt to alert others is met with the same incredulity that greeted his earlier disclosure. In his solitude, Eli clings to fragments of sound and memory &ndash; often via the cassette tapes he carries with him &ndash; as he searches for some means of expression and truth. As the film unfolds, the personal and the communal collide: Eli&rsquo;s internal unravelling mirrors the larger spectre of the environmental exploitation that is threatening his hometown. What begins as a quiet examination of one individual&rsquo;s anguish evolves into a parable about how silence and denial can corrode both human lives and the natural world that sustains them.<br/>
Cast: by Ryan Machado (Director), Ryan Machado (Screenplay) Cast: Elijah Canlas, Ron Angeles, Reynald Raissel Santos, Glenn Sevilla Mas, Rodney Galicha, Nathan Sotto<br/>
Durata: 87 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202604970_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Tue Feb 17 15:30 - Zoo Palast 1, Wed Feb 18 21:30 - Cubix 9, Thu Feb 19 13:00 - Cubix 7, Fri Feb 20 21:45 - Filmtheater am Friedrichshain, Sat Feb 21 17:30 - Cubix 9]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202604970.html</guid></item><item><title>Forêt Ivre by Manon Coubia</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202605344.html</link><description><![CDATA[In the northern Alps, Anne, H&eacute;l&egrave;ne and Suzanne take turns looking after a mountain hut. Through the seasons, hikers come and go; stories bloom and fade, leaving each of them facing the silence.&nbsp;<em class="film">For&ecirc;t Ivre</em>&nbsp;tells the story of three women who have made the choice to withdraw from the world down in the valley. Each of them harbours a secret; and each of them is put to the test by their chosen solitude.<br/>
Cast: by Manon Coubia (Director), Manon Coubia (Screenplay) Cast: Salomé Richard, Aurélia Petit, Anne Coesens, Arthur Marbaix, Yoann Zimmer<br/>
Durata: 102 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202605344_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Mon Feb 16 16:00 - Bluemax Theater, Tue Feb 17 13:00 - Cubix 9, Wed Feb 18 19:30 - Cubix 8, Thu Feb 19 19:00 - Bluemax Theater, Fri Feb 20 16:00 - Colosseum 1]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202605344.html</guid></item><item><title>Trop c’est trop by Elisé Sawasawa</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202605439.html</link><description><![CDATA[The Kivu War is a series of armed conflicts that have been ongoing for decades in the eastern part of the Democratic Republic of the Congo. It is a situation of great violence in which civilians are the main victims of the fighting, particularly women and children who are subjected to rape, assault and forced recruitment. The conflicts are mainly driven by economic motives due to an abundance of natural resources. Alongside oil, the region is rich in copper, cobalt, zinc, manganese, gold, uranium and germanium. It is also a valuable source of tantalum, a rare earth used in the manufacture of microelectronics including phones and laptops. In January 2025, Goma, the capital of North Kivu, falls to rebels. It takes only four days for the M23 group to defeat the Congolese army supported by soldiers from Kenya, Uganda, Tanzania, Malawi, South Africa and Burundi fighting alongside mercenaries and militias under the watchful eye of the UN&rsquo;s largest base in the region, MONUSCO. <em class="film">Trop c&rsquo;est trop</em> bears witness to the incredible vitality of the Congolese people trapped in the tragedy of an endless war.<br/>
Cast: by Elisé Sawasawa (Director), Elisé Sawasawa (Screenplay) Cast: Eliane Feza, Moses Sawasawa, Francis Zihindula Milindwa<br/>
Durata: 65 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/media/filmstills/2026/plakate-2026/202605439_9_ORG.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Fri Feb 13 13:00 - Bluemax Theater, Sat Feb 14 19:15 - Cubix 6, Mon Feb 16 14:00 - ADK am Hanseatenweg, Tue Feb 17 12:00 - CinemaxX 5, Tue Feb 17 12:00 - CinemaxX 6, Sat Feb 21 10:00 - Cubix 7, Sun Feb 22 14:30 - Cubix 7]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202605439.html</guid></item><item><title>Árru by Elle Sofe Sara</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202605447.html</link><description><![CDATA[Amid the breathtaking landscapes of S&aacute;pmi, Sami reindeer herder Maia fights to protect her ancestral lands from a looming mining project. As protests increase, she turns to her uncle Lemme for help, but his presence reignites deep-buried familial traumas. Maia must choose: save the land at the cost of her family, or surrender it to break the silence.<br/>
Cast: by Elle Sofe Sara (Director), Johan Fasting (Screenplay) Cast: Sara Marielle Gaup Beaska, Simon Issát Marainen, Ayla Gáren Nutti, Mikkel Gaup<br/>
Durata: 95 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202605447_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Mon Feb 16 15:15 - Zoo Palast 1, Tue Feb 17 21:30 - Cubix 9, Wed Feb 18 13:00 - Cubix 7, Thu Feb 19 21:45 - Filmtheater am Friedrichshain, Fri Feb 20 12:15 - Cubix 9, Sun Feb 22 22:15 - Urania]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202605447.html</guid></item><item><title>Who Killed Alex Odeh? by Jason Osder</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202605733.html</link><description><![CDATA[In October 1985, Santa Ana, California was shaken by a brazen act of political violence: Palestinian American Alex Odeh, a beloved teacher and community leader, was killed by a tripwire bomb planted in his office. Despite having identified suspects, the police made no arrests and the case went cold. <em class="film">Who Killed Alex Odeh?</em> reopens the mystery, tracking the work of an Israeli journalist who, decades later, takes up the investigation. New leads emerge, long-buried records come to light and the forces behind a political assassination are finally uncovered. The case exposes a trail of unanswered questions that have international implications.<br/>
Cast: by Jason Osder (Director), William Lafi Youmans (Director)<br/>
Durata: 82 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202605733_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Tue Feb 17 14:00 - Haus der Berliner Festspiele, Wed Feb 18 16:30 - ADK am Hanseatenweg, Fri Feb 20 16:00 - ADK am Hanseatenweg, Sat Feb 21 22:00 - Colosseum 1]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202605733.html</guid></item><item><title>Panelstory, aneb jak se rodí sídliště by Věra Chytilová</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202605881.html</link><description><![CDATA[Life is a construction site for the tenants of the only partially finished prefab housing development in Prague. Between the buildings, young mothers struggle to push their prams through mounds of mud. And things are not any better inside. Here, a corpulent man is stuck because the door will not open; there, no water comes out of the taps, but a conversation in the neighbouring apartment can be heard clear as day through the pipes. And there is no way out of the boiler room because the door has no handle &hellip;
 Věra Chytilov&aacute;&rsquo;s film depicts one day in that construction chaos through the eyes of a handful of people of various ages who have to deal with the hodgepodge of permanently makeshift solutions in what was conceived as a &ldquo;garden city&rdquo;. In 2002, the director said: &ldquo;It&rsquo;s not a critical reaction to the regime; it&rsquo;s more actually a view of human behaviour.&rdquo; Nonetheless, her amusing social satire was held back by the authorities and not shown in Czechoslovakia until 1981.&nbsp;The digitisation was undertaken from the original picture negative and sound held at the N&aacute;rodn&iacute; filmov&yacute; archiv in Prague.<br/>
Cast: by Věra Chytilová (Director), Eva Kačírková (Screenplay) Cast: Lukáš Bech, Antonín Vaňha, Eva Kačírková, Oldřich Navrátil, Jiří Kodet, Bronislav Poloczek, Daniela Šrajerová, Milan Klásek, Ladislav Potměšil, Hana Hejduková<br/>
Durata: 100 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202605881_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Tue Feb 17 19:00 - ADK am Hanseatenweg, Wed Feb 18 11:15 - Cubix 5, Sun Feb 22 15:15 - Cubix 5]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202605881.html</guid></item><item><title>The Moths &amp; the Flame by Kevin Contento</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202605954.html</link><description><![CDATA[Over one year, Kevin Contento accompanies a group of young men in Pahokee, Florida, a small community marked by agriculture and rabbit hunting. He has been friends with them since they were children and has, like them, recently become a father. Whether in the kitchen or the laundromat, this is filming as giving and taking. In calmly shot vignettes full of solidarity, the everyday lives, thoughts and dreams of Black fathers become visible, interwoven with the spiritual poems they recite. Lines from Farid ud-Din Attar&rsquo;s Sufi parable &ldquo;The Moths and the Flame&rdquo;, for example, whose message is that true insight is not reached through talking or thinking, but rather by total dedication. Contento thus bathes the sugar cane plantations in golden light, shows Pahokee in wide shots and elevates it to a place of enlightenment. A free, poetic form of cinematic language that takes time to observe children&rsquo;s birthdays and housework alike and contradicts the myth of the absent Black father on a day-to-day basis. Accompanied by the wistful, mystical compositions by legendary hip hop producer 4th Disciple, <em class="film">The Moths &amp; the Flame</em> becomes an intense, very much optimistic viewing experience.<br/>
Cast: by Kevin Contento (Director) Cast: Jean Voltaire, Malik Hall, Wiltavious McKelton, Tavion Jamal Dent, Helen Contento, Willy<br/>
Durata: 97 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202605954_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sun Feb 15 11:30 - Cinema Paris, Tue Feb 17 19:30 - Cubix 8, Thu Feb 19 21:00 - Cinema Betonhalle@Silent Green, Sat Feb 21 18:00 - Delphi Filmpalast]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202605954.html</guid></item><item><title>In Which Annie Gives It Those Ones by Pradip Krishen</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202605965.html</link><description><![CDATA[In 1974 New Delhi, Anand &ldquo;Annie&rdquo; Grover is a student at the state architecture institute. And has been for quite some time. At the moment, he is repeating the fifth year &ndash; for the fourth time. Four years ago, he made a derogatory joke about the dean in the men&rsquo;s toilet. Since then, he has received a &ldquo;fail&rdquo; in every exam. No wonder he and his fellow students have nicknamed the dean &ldquo;Yamdoot&rdquo;, meaning &ldquo;angel of death&rdquo;. He is planning to fail Annie this semester, too. But this time, his fellow students come to his aid &hellip;
 In her first screenplay, Indian writer Arundhati Roy brought memories of her own architecture studies to bear, in particular with her depiction of Radha as a critical, individualistic student. Her husband Pradip Krishen beautifully captures the zeitgeist, with a Che Guevara poster, books by Lenin and Beatles songs evoking the academic pop culture of the 1970s. The film was disseminated largely privately via VHS cassettes and achieved cult status.&nbsp;The 4K restoration was undertaken in collaboration with the director using the 16mm camera negative and a 35mm print.<br/>
Cast: by Pradip Krishen (Director), Arundhati Roy (Screenplay) Cast: Roshan Seth, Arjun Raina, Arundhati Roy, Rituraj Singh, Shah Rukh Khan, Raghuvir Yadav, Isaac Thomas, Divya Seth, Moses Uboh, Benoy Thomas<br/>
Durata: 112 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202605965_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Mon Feb 16 19:00 - ADK am Hanseatenweg, Tue Feb 17 12:00 - Cubix 5, Fri Feb 20 19:00 - Cubix 5]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202605965.html</guid></item><item><title>Wolfram by Warwick Thornton</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202606004.html</link><description><![CDATA[On the colonial frontier of 1930s Australia, two swaggering outlaws roll into a mining town and unleash a wave of cruelty, leading two siblings to break free from their white masters who have forced them to work as child labourers in the mines. The children escape and set off across the desert &ldquo;sweet country&rdquo; of central Australia, in search of safety and a way home. Set in the same universe as Thornton&rsquo;s multi award-winning film <em class="film-other">Sweet Country</em> from 2017, <em class="film">Wolfram</em> features standout performances from Deborah Mailman and its young actors, playing siblings who must rely on each other as they search for the truth about themselves and their family, escape a nightmare and make unexpected connections on their way to freedom. An outback Western but also a historical drama about survival, reckoning, resilience and love.<br/>
Cast: by Warwick Thornton (Director), Steven McGregor (Screenplay) Cast: Deborah Mailman, Erroll Shand, Joe Bird, Thomas M Wright, Ferdinand Hoang<br/>
Durata: 102 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202606004_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Tue Feb 17 15:15 - Berlinale Palast, Wed Feb 18 10:00 - Urania, Wed Feb 18 22:15 - Uber Eats Music Hall, Sat Feb 21 17:45 - Haus der Berliner Festspiele, Sun Feb 22 20:00 - Urania]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202606004.html</guid></item><item><title>Prénoms by Nurith Aviv</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202606131.html</link><description><![CDATA[A film of rules whose narrative varies, multiplies and expands into a novel of nomadic world knowledge. Nurith Aviv visits her friends. She arrives with flowers in her hand, finds the appropriate framing and listens. She speaks for Agn&egrave;s V., whose actual name was Arlette. All the others speak themselves and soon get talking, about nothing less than the story of their first names. Chowra, Gulya, Hind, etcetera, 13 in number, 13 miniatures from A for Agn&egrave;s Varda to Z for Zeynep Jouvenaux. They are colleagues from the film industry (filmmakers like herself, or stagehands), psychoanalysts, literature professors, engineers. Every meaning produced here is somehow connected to their first names. How fascinatingly simple this film seems and yet what gifts one receives while listening. Like herself, Nurith&rsquo;s friends regard their names as messages, as a point of connection to their family and cultural backgrounds and as a trace of the desires and yearnings of those who brought them into the world. In her cinematic oeuvre, Nurith Aviv taps into signs, letters, words, languages. She herself also speaks many, including that of the camera. What a gift &ndash; and piece of luck.<br/>
Cast: by Nurith Aviv (Director), Nurith Aviv (Screenplay) Cast: Chowra Makaremi, Edouard Rosenblatt, Gulya Mirzoeva, Hind Meddeb, Judith Guy, Marc-Alain Ouaknin, Nathalie Bély, Rim Bouhedda, Sarah Lawan Gana, Tewfik Allal, Yue Zhuo, Zeynep Jouvenaux<br/>
Durata: 82 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/media/filmstills/2026/plakate-2026/202606131_9_RWD_1920.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sun Feb 15 15:00 - Delphi Filmpalast, Tue Feb 17 13:00 - ADK am Hanseatenweg, Fri Feb 20 14:30 - Cinema Paris, Sun Feb 22 13:30 - Cinema Paris]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202606131.html</guid></item><item><title>Take Me Home by Liz Sargent</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202606137.html</link><description><![CDATA[Anna, a 38-year-old Korean woman with a cognitive disability, cares for her ageing adoptive parents in a fragile balance of meeting each other&rsquo;s needs. When a Florida heatwave shatters both the family&rsquo;s and Anna&rsquo;s routines, her future looks uncertain &ndash; until she manages to create a world in which she can thrive.
 ​Liz Sargent&rsquo;s intimate debut drama examines the shifting demands placed on a uniquely vulnerable family in a Florida suburb. The film exposes the indignities of the American healthcare system and the structural challenges faced by disabled people and their families. It also gently and imaginatively traces Anna&rsquo;s path to finding independence and a connection to a community of chosen family. By turns quietly devastating and bracingly optimistic,&nbsp;<em class="film">Take Me Home</em>&nbsp;confronts us with an impossible situation, while holding out hope for Anna&rsquo;s future.<br/>
Cast: by Liz Sargent (Director), Liz Sargent (Screenplay) Cast: Anna Sargent, Victor Slezak, Ali Ahn, Marceline Hugot, Shane Harper<br/>
Durata: 91 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/media/filmstills/2026/plakate-2026/202606137_9_RWD_1920.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Tue Feb 17 16:00 - Bluemax Theater, Wed Feb 18 18:45 - Cubix 9, Thu Feb 19 19:30 - Cubix 8, Sat Feb 21 15:00 - Colosseum 1, Sun Feb 22 22:00 - Colosseum 1]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202606137.html</guid></item><item><title>Piedras preciosas by Simón Vélez</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202606145.html</link><description><![CDATA[Young Colombian immigrant Machado has a job harvesting grapes in the French countryside. He also seems to have a criminal past, as a female gangster boss hires him to steal a valuable emerald &ndash; dressed up as a priest &ndash; from a famous church close to Medell&iacute;n. Yet this supposedly watertight plan quickly goes awry ... Images and moments, woven together with fine threads: amusingly and with considerable lightness of touch, director Sim&oacute;n V&eacute;lez gets to grips with and reconfigures the gangster film genre. The plot is characterised by original dramatic paths rather than a classical linear narration: pared down in terms of action and dialogue, unfolding at unique locations that do not just frame the plot but enter into a congenial unity with the characters. The striking camerawork carries out expeditions through Colombia&rsquo;s multifaceted flora &ndash; at once shimmering and shining, just like the object of desire. Imposing colour compositions, energetic dances, cool costume design: <em class="film">Piedras preciosas</em> is a feature debut that elegantly eschews Colombian stereotypes, relates to colonial history and cultivates a timeless pop aesthetic.<br/>
Cast: by Simón Vélez (Director), Paulo Carneiro (Screenplay) Cast: Juan Lugo, Laura Taurines, Sofía Jaramillo, Yira Plaza, Daniel Cortés, Chiara Spolaor<br/>
Durata: 70 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202606145_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Tue Feb 17 21:00 - Cinema Paris, Wed Feb 18 14:00 - Cubix 8, Fri Feb 20 16:00 - Bluemax Theater, Sat Feb 21 20:00 - Zoo Palast 2]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202606145.html</guid></item><item><title>Black Burns Fast by Sandulela Asanda</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202606248.html</link><description><![CDATA[Seventeen-year-old Luthando, adorkable, bookish and forever drifting between reality and her vivid inner world, returns for another year at a prestigious South African all-girls&rsquo; boarding school. The place is governed by a conservative culture where reputation is everything, and nonconformity is quietly disciplined. As the lone scholarship girl, Luthando has learned to keep her head down, her marks up, and her single mother&rsquo;s high expectations close to her heart. Her world is turned upside down by the arrival of a bold and effortlessly charismatic new pupil, Ayanda. The two begin a secret romance and Luthando is ushered into Ayanda&rsquo;s orbit of confident, carefree friends, tasting a freedom she has never experienced at the school before. But juggling her old life, new friendships and first love becomes too much. When jealousy pushes Ayanda into a reckless decision, this not only threatens Luthando&rsquo;s scholarship, but also her future and her relationship with her mother. Luthando finds an unexpected courage and firmly stands up for her truth: she is queer, and she will no longer shrink from anyone. A film about the joy that comes from owning one&rsquo;s own story and identity.<br/>
Cast: by Sandulela Asanda (Director), Sandulela Asanda (Screenplay) Cast: Esihle Ndleleni, Muadi Ilung, Mila Smith, Khensani Khoza, Ntsimedi Gwangwa, Basetsana Motloung<br/>
Durata: 100 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/media/filmstills/2026/plakate-2026/202606248_9_RWD_1920.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sun Feb 15 19:00 - HKW 1 - Miriam Makeba Auditorium, Mon Feb 16 13:00 - Filmtheater am Friedrichshain, Tue Feb 17 19:15 - Cubix 6, Fri Feb 20 09:30 - Zoo Palast 1, Sun Feb 22 13:00 - HKW 1 - Miriam Makeba Auditorium]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202606248.html</guid></item><item><title>Ravalear by Isaki Lacuesta</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202606276.html</link><description><![CDATA[&ldquo;Can Mosques&rdquo;&nbsp;is a hundred-year-old family-run restaurant in Barcelona&rsquo;s El Raval district, adored and respected by everyone. But, after falling into the hands of an investment fund whose aim is to empty the building and accelerate the transformation of the neighbourhood, it is now facing eviction. The news plunges the family into deep despair. When they decide to stand up for themselves with the help of their neighbours, the fight quickly spirals out of control and becomes increasingly dangerous. In order to save Can Mosques, they will have to cross lines they never thought themselves capable of crossing and ask themselves just how far they are prepared to go to secure the restaurant&rsquo;s survival.<br/>
Cast: by Isabel Campo (Screenplay) Cast: Enric Auquer Sardà, María Rodríguez Soto, Sergi López, Quim Ávila, Francesc Orella<br/>
Durata: 95 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202606276_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Tue Feb 17 19:00 - Zoo Palast 2, Wed Feb 18 10:00 - Bluemax Theater, Fri Feb 20 19:15 - Cubix 8, Sun Feb 22 12:00 - ADK am Hanseatenweg]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202606276.html</guid></item><item><title>Papaya by Priscilla Kellen</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202606578.html</link><description><![CDATA[Passionate about the idea of flying, Papaya is a tiny seed in a world governed by laws of nature with sprinkles of fantasy. She struggles to conform to expectations because her curiosity and an uncontrollable desire for freedom make her different from other seeds. When she realises that her destiny is to become a tree, she rebels. Fighting against her own nature, Papaya tries to stay in constant motion to avoid rooting. On her journey away from the mother tree, she learns a great deal about the creatures of the forest. But even Papaya must eventually take root &ndash; on the median strip of a highway, of all places. There she discovers the power within her, triggers a revolution and transforms her environment. Papaya&rsquo;s emotional development is accompanied by a moving soundtrack as she learns that the world is shaped by ancestral wisdom. As her dream comes true, albeit in an unexpected way, the film imaginatively tells a story of resistance and of coming to terms with change.<br/>
Cast: by Priscilla Kellen (Director), Priscilla Kellen (Screenplay)<br/>
Durata: 74 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202606578_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sun Feb 15 09:30 - Zoo Palast 1, Mon Feb 16 16:00 - Filmtheater am Friedrichshain, Tue Feb 17 13:15 - Cubix 6, Wed Feb 18 09:45 - Filmtheater am Friedrichshain, Fri Feb 20 14:00 - Kino Casablanca, Sun Feb 22 16:00 - HKW 1 - Miriam Makeba Auditorium]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202606578.html</guid></item><item><title>Two Mountains Weighing Down My Chest by Viv Li</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202606587.html</link><description><![CDATA[Viv, a Chinese wannabe artist, found herself stuck in Berlin after the pandemic and accidentally ventured into the city&rsquo;s vibrant alternative culture scene. Drifting between new environments and traditional expectations, Viv is constantly adapting to shifting opinions about herself, the world and, of course, China, only to feel more lost than ever. <em class="film">Two Mountains Weighing Down My Chest</em> follows Viv&rsquo;s eclectic encounters and the nuanced culture clashes that shape them. Told in a deeply personal and humorous voice, the film takes a witty yet sharp look at the quest for a sense of belonging in a globalised world and how different societies define our lives. ' A story of the perpetual search for oneself, identity and acceptance, woven into a spiral of surreal yet tangible moments.<br/>
Cast: by Viv Li (Director), Viv Li (Screenplay) Cast: Viv Li<br/>
Durata: 85 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/media/filmstills/2026/plakate-2026/202606587_9_RWD_1920.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Fri Feb 13 21:30 - Zoo Palast 2, Sat Feb 14 22:00 - Cubix 7, Sun Feb 15 13:15 - Cubix 7, Tue Feb 17 16:00 - Cubix 7, Wed Feb 18 22:00 - Cubix 6, Sat Feb 21 18:00 - Zoo Palast 2]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202606587.html</guid></item><item><title>Joy Boy: A Tribute to Julius Eastman by Mawena Yehouessi</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202606712.html</link><description><![CDATA[An homage to Julius Eastman (1940&ndash;1980), African American pianist, composer, homosexual &ndash; legendary for his voice and his stage presence, who died in poverty. In 1979, he wrote &ldquo;Evil Nigger&rdquo; and &ldquo;Gay Guerrilla&rdquo; for piano quartet. <em class="film">Joy Boy</em> is a concert performance alternating between his music and archival recordings &ndash; visualised by a trans-national, six-headed collective in four chapters. Music and images autonomous. The compositions show his skill, the texts his attitude. Inflamed by colonial and life history, raw, radical and crystal clear, he downright hurls the words out (including the N-word &ndash; beyond all possible, necessary trigger warnings), spews them out, becomes thoughtful, quiet. Coming from a wide spectrum of theoretical and artistic practices &ndash; film, performance, dance; textile, archive, research &ndash; the directors partake in a complex collaboration, independent and collective, in solidarity with Eastman and each other. A film that packs a political punch and is beautiful to boot, especially the contact of bodies, colours and rhythms, and the choreography of the Gay Guerrilla along the highway, taking up space, threatening, vulnerable, strong.<br/>
Cast: by Mawena Yehouessi (Director), Fallon Mayanja (Director), Rob Jacobs (Director), Victoire Karera Kampire (Director), Paul Shemisi (Director), Anne Reijniers (Director)<br/>
Durata: 64 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/media/filmstills/2026/plakate-2026/202606712_9_ORG.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sat Feb 14 14:30 - Cinema Paris, Sun Feb 15 13:30 - Cubix 8, Tue Feb 17 22:00 - Bluemax Theater, Wed Feb 18 15:00 - CinemaxX 6]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202606712.html</guid></item><item><title>Safe Exit by Mohammed Hammad</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202607047.html</link><description><![CDATA[A psychological thriller following Samaan, a young security guard who belongs to a generation whose parents were murdered by religious violence in the Arab region over the past decade. Then children, they are now young adults in their early twenties, still struggling with inherited trauma.<br/>
Cast: by Mohammed Hammad (Director), Mohammed Hammad (Screenplay) Cast: Marwan Waleed, Noha Foad, Hazem Essam<br/>
Durata: 113 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202607047_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sat Feb 14 21:30 - Urania, Sun Feb 15 10:00 - Cubix 9, Mon Feb 16 19:00 - Cubix 7, Tue Feb 17 14:00 - CinemaxX 5, Tue Feb 17 14:00 - CinemaxX 6, Fri Feb 20 22:00 - Zoo Palast 2, Sat Feb 21 12:35 - Cubix 9]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202607047.html</guid></item><item><title>Ich verstehe Ihren Unmut by Kilian Armando Friedrich</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202607173.html</link><description><![CDATA[Heike (59) works as a customer service manager at a cleaning company, mediating daily between clients, company management and cleaning staff. Her firm is having problems with an important subcontractor because Heike tried to poach one of his unofficial workers, contrary to regulations. The subcontractor is now threatening to stop his support unless Heike secures more hours and revenue for him. To meet his demands, she must dismiss one of her own employees&nbsp;&ndash; a colleague who is highly valued by her friend, Taja. Heike finds herself increasingly caught between her responsibility for her own employees and the conditions of the low-wage sector.<br/>
Cast: by Kilian Armando Friedrich (Director), Kilian Armando Friedrich (Screenplay) Cast: Sabine Thalau, Nada Kosturin, Werner Posselt, Sadibou Diabang, Nigyar Velagic<br/>
Durata: 93 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/media/filmstills/2026/plakate-2026/202607173_9_RWD_1920.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Fri Feb 13 16:15 - Zoo Palast 2, Sat Feb 14 19:15 - Cubix 7, Mon Feb 16 15:30 - Urania, Tue Feb 17 10:45 - Colosseum 1, Wed Feb 18 12:45 - CinemaxX 5, Wed Feb 18 12:45 - CinemaxX 6, Fri Feb 20 09:45 - Haus der Berliner Festspiele]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202607173.html</guid></item><item><title>Leaving Las Vegas by Mike Figgis</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202607309.html</link><description><![CDATA[Screenwriter Ben Sanderson is a hopeless alcoholic. His wife has left him, his friends avoid him, and his boss sends him packing with a payoff. Ben leaves Hollywood behind. He plans to drink himself to death &ndash; in Las Vegas, where the bars never close. On the neon streets, he meets sex worker Sera. She too is a lonely heart; her pimp abuses and humiliates her. Ben leaves his sleazy hotel and moves in with her. They make a deal that she will not prevent him from drinking and he will never criticise her profession. Things go well for a while. Then Sera begins to fall in love with Ben. That means responsibilities &hellip;
 Audiences will be shaken not stirred by this chronicle of a planned suicide. <em class="film">Leaving Las Vegas</em>, searingly unemotional and unsentimental, was based on an autobiography. Only the bar jazz score by Mike Figgis and Sting&rsquo;s dulcet singing soften its flintiness.&nbsp;The Super 16 camera negative provided the basis for the 4K restoration. The smaller camera was necessary for the authentic shots in Las Vegas&rsquo; streets and casinos that are key to this realistic film drama.<br/>
Cast: by Mike Figgis (Director), Mike Figgis (Screenplay) Cast: Nicolas Cage, Elisabeth Shue, Julian Sands, Richard Lewis, Steven Weber, Kim Adams, R. Lee Ermey, Shawnee Smith, Emily Procter, Mariska Hargitay<br/>
Durata: 112 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202607309_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sun Feb 15 19:00 - ADK am Hanseatenweg, Tue Feb 17 21:30 - Cubix 5, Sat Feb 21 13:00 - Cubix 5]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202607309.html</guid></item><item><title>At the Sea by Kornél Mundruczó</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202608333.html</link><description><![CDATA[After rehab, Laura returns to her family&rsquo;s Cape Cod home. Once the face of her late father&rsquo;s renowned dance company, she built an identity tethered to his legacy and the cost of growing up in his shadow. Laura&rsquo;s functional alcoholism, long ignored by everybody, finally reached a breaking point after a drunk-driving accident with her young son in the car. Now sober, she comes home changed, but to a family unprepared for this. Her husband Martin welcomes her cautiously, torn between devotion and mistrust. Their teenage daughter Josie meets Laura with hostility, while her son Felix remains distant. Over several days by the sea, family moments become pressure points, revealing buried anger, financial strain and the fragility of reconciliation. As Laura&rsquo;s former colleagues push her to return to the career she abandoned, she confronts a deeper question: Who is she without the identity that once justified her self-destruction?
 The film unfolds as an intimate character study that charts Laura&rsquo;s path from denial towards acceptance as she approaches an understanding that healing is not linear and that love, sobriety and family demand a willingness to remain present in uncertainty.<br/>
Cast: by Kornél Mundruczó (Director), Kata Wéber (Screenplay) Cast: Amy Adams, Murray Bartlett, Chloe East, Brett Goldstein, Dan Levy, Redding L. Munsell, Jenny Slate, Rainn Wilson<br/>
Durata: 112 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/media/filmstills/2026/plakate-2026/202608333_9_ORG.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Mon Feb 16 18:45 - Berlinale Palast, Tue Feb 17 10:00 - Urania, Wed Feb 18 19:00 - Uber Eats Music Hall, Fri Feb 20 16:00 - Uber Eats Music Hall, Sun Feb 22 21:45 - Berlinale Palast]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202608333.html</guid></item><item><title>Uchronia by Fil Ieropoulos</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202608348.html</link><description><![CDATA[In this docu-essay inspired by Arthur Rimbaud&rsquo;s &ldquo;Une Saison en Enfer&rdquo;, we meet the French poet&rsquo;s ghost embarking on a time-travel adventure. His delirious visions become portals opening onto alternative timelines &ndash; or &ldquo;uchronias&rdquo;. Rimbaud gains the opportunity to meet revolutionary figures such as Emma Goldman, David Wojnarowicz and Marsha P. Johnson. Together, they explore the possibility of social change and reflect on the meaning of revolution in times of disillusionment. Inspired by the rich history of 20<sup>th</sup>-century experimental queer cinema, the film is a celebration of enfants terribles and dissident freaks across the globe. Ultimately, the film considers the current political milieu and its parallels with Rimbaud&rsquo;s own time. Could post-internet ennui and widespread defeatism be understood through the eyes of a late 19<sup>th</sup>-century decadent poet? Can his critique of national identity and European concepts of barbarism be relevant to today&rsquo;s far-right EU turn? How do we navigate mainstream queer visibility while transphobia remains rampant? Dealing with these rhetorical yet pertinent questions, the film is simultaneously an alternative history, a synesthetic poem and a rollercoaster of affect.<br/>
Cast: by Fil Ieropoulos (Director), Foivos Dousos (Screenplay) Cast: Kristof, Flomaria Papadaki, Marlo Mortimer, Amani Cosmo, Robert Carithers, Eve Libertine, Antoinetta Angelidi<br/>
Durata: 97 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202608348_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Tue Feb 17 21:00 - Cinema Betonhalle@Silent Green, Sat Feb 21 15:30 - Cinema Betonhalle@Silent Green]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202608348.html</guid></item><item><title>Nosso segredo by Grace Passô</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202608389.html</link><description><![CDATA[A Black Brazilian family in the city of Belo Horizonte struggles to rebuild their lives after a recent loss. Caught between memories and nightmares, and unable to express what they feel to each other, a mother and her children try to evade the pain of grief by immersing themselves in their individual routines. Only the youngest child understands the secret that the house holds within its four walls and attempts to reveal it to the others, but it falls on deaf ears. When the family is finally confronted with the truth, they face the deep roots of their grief and come together to traverse this moment with love and courage.<br/>
Cast: by Grace Passô (Director), Grace Passô (Screenplay) Cast: Efraim Santos, Flip, Jéssica Gaspar, Ju Colombo, Marisa Revert, Robert Frank, Juan Queiroz, Gláucia Vandeveld, Mateus Aleluia, Tássia Reis<br/>
Durata: 108 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202608389_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sat Feb 14 16:00 - Bluemax Theater, Sun Feb 15 13:00 - Cubix 9, Mon Feb 16 19:15 - Cubix 8, Tue Feb 17 16:00 - Colosseum 1, Thu Feb 19 13:00 - Cubix 9]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202608389.html</guid></item><item><title>The Other Side of the Sun by Tawfik Sabouni</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202608798.html</link><description><![CDATA[Years ago, filmmaker Tawfik Sabouni was released from Saidnaya, the infamous Syrian prison also known as &ldquo;the other side of the sun&rdquo;. In the immediate aftermath of the fall of Assad&rsquo;s regime in December 2024, the filmmaker returns to the site of his detention. He does not intend to reopen wounds but instead to restore what systematic violence tried to erase: voices, stories and humanity. Sabouni invites four fellow survivors of Saidnaya to join him. Together, they return to the physical spaces where they were tortured and dehumanised for years, and engage in a carefully constructed re-enactment of their confinement: daily rituals, gestures and moments of survival. Filmed inside the former prison, these re-enactments become a means to express what language alone cannot contain. With restraint, the film confronts the viewer with the enduring marks of imprisonment and gives a voice not only to these five men but also to those thousands who did not survive the Assad regime and whose families are still searching for answers.<br/>
Cast: by Tawfik Sabouni (Director), Tawfik Sabouni (Screenplay) Cast: Tawfik Sabouni, Mahmoud Alqadah, Abdelkafi Alhaj, Mohammad Hamki, Abdelhamid Jadoue<br/>
Durata: 90 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/media/filmstills/2026/plakate-2026/202608798_9_RWD_1920.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sun Feb 15 17:30 - Haus der Berliner Festspiele, Mon Feb 16 22:00 - Cubix 6, Tue Feb 17 10:00 - Cubix 7, Wed Feb 18 10:00 - CinemaxX 7, Sat Feb 21 15:45 - Cubix 7, Sun Feb 22 20:30 - Zoo Palast 2]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202608798.html</guid></item><item><title>La Face cachée de la Terre by Arnaud Alain</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202608889.html</link><description><![CDATA[Dimitri loves to photograph the people around him. But for years, images have been slipping away from his sight. He knows that, one day, he will no longer see. He is unable to take photos as he used to. So, night and day, hidden behind his camera, he gathers light and bodies. The film accompanies Dimitri through the streets of Paris, New York and elsewhere; as he captures his objects, the film camera captures him. Along the way, the director and his protagonist encounter friends including Pierre, who lost his eyesight twenty years ago, but also lovers and strangers, met by chance or during a photo shoot. Imaginations and gazes overlay. Dimitri&rsquo;s photographs converse with the filmmaker&rsquo;s reveries. Dimitri invites him and the audience to discover the hidden face of the Earth.<br/>
Cast: by Arnaud Alain (Director), Arnaud Alain (Screenplay) Cast: Dimitri Jean, Pierre Marragou<br/>
Durata: 68 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/media/filmstills/2026/plakate-2026/202608889_9_RWD_1920.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Tue Feb 17 21:30 - Urania, Wed Feb 18 10:00 - Cubix 9, Thu Feb 19 19:00 - Cubix 7, Sat Feb 21 14:00 - Cubix 7, Sun Feb 22 13:00 - Bluemax Theater]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202608889.html</guid></item><item><title>TUTU by Sam Pollard</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202609071.html</link><description><![CDATA[The South African cleric Desmond Tutu was more than just an archbishop, he was a moral compass, a fearless champion of justice and a global beacon of hope for a more peaceful future. <em class="film">TUTU</em> is a powerful documentary that reveals the man behind the icon through previously unpublished archive footage and first-hand accounts from those who walked beside him. The film traces Tutu&rsquo;s rise as the unwavering voice of the oppressed. In the face of brutality, he stood resolute, guided by faith, fuelled by hope and driven by an unshakable belief in the humanity of all people. At its heart, this is a story of the transformative power of forgiveness, a message from which Tutu never wavered.<br/>
Cast: by Sam Pollard (Director)<br/>
Durata: 101 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202609071_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Mon Feb 16 14:00 - Haus der Berliner Festspiele, Tue Feb 17 14:00 - BALI KINO, Tue Feb 17 16:00 - ADK am Hanseatenweg, Fri Feb 20 21:45 - Colosseum 1, Sat Feb 21 13:00 - ADK am Hanseatenweg]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202609071.html</guid></item><item><title>Feito Pipa by Allan Deberton</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202609138.html</link><description><![CDATA[Gugu is almost twelve and dreams of becoming a football player. He is growing up in a small community near the Ara&uacute;jo Lima reservoir that is slowly drying up to expose the ghostly remains of a submerged town. Gugu is cared for by his grandmother Dilma, whose warmth and open-mindedness gives him the space to simply be himself. The pair share a quiet but powerful bond that shields them from the disapproval of Gugu&rsquo;s father and the community around them. As old memories resurface, subtle changes begin to unsettle their routine. Dilma becomes increasingly frail. Worrying that he might lose the only safe space he has ever known, Gugu grows ever more determined to keep their world intact.<br/>
Cast: by Allan Deberton (Director), André Araújo (Screenplay) Cast: Yuri Gomes, Teca Pereira, Lázaro Ramos, Carlos Francisco, Georgina Castro<br/>
Durata: 93 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/media/filmstills/2026/plakate-2026/202609138_9_ORG.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sat Feb 14 13:00 - Cubix 6, Sun Feb 15 15:30 - HKW 1 - Miriam Makeba Auditorium, Mon Feb 16 10:00 - Zoo Palast 2, Tue Feb 17 12:45 - Filmtheater am Friedrichshain, Fri Feb 20 19:15 - Cubix 6, Sat Feb 21 09:45 - Filmtheater am Friedrichshain]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202609138.html</guid></item><item><title>A Fabulosa Máquina do Tempo by Eliza Capai</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202609628.html</link><description><![CDATA[&ldquo;Before everything, it was dark. Then God started playing and making all things up. He made the man from the dust, and the woman from the man &hellip; Would women be different if they were made from dust, too? I&rsquo;m glad I&rsquo;m not a woman yet. Not me or my girlfriends.&rdquo; This is how <em class="film">A Fabulosa M&aacute;quina do Tempo</em> begins. Told from the perspective of a ten-year-old girl, the film follows her and her friends&rsquo; journey from childhood to adolescence. Despite living in houses with dirt floors, without tap water, amid the aridity of the Brazilian sert&atilde;o, they state that they were born with perks &ndash; able to eat, study, play, and dream of better futures. The girls invent time machines and travel to a past that was all about pure survival. They playfully deal with complex issues such as gender differences, alcoholism and religion. They joke about death, frustration and fears. Childhood innocence gradually gives way to a mixture of curiosity and anxiety about becoming teenagers. When they realise that fighting against the passage of time is futile, they travel to the future and envision becoming independent and successful women.<br/>
Cast: by Eliza Capai (Director), Eliza Capai (Screenplay) Cast: Manuellinha, Manu, Sophia<br/>
Durata: 70 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202609628_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Fri Feb 13 15:30 - HKW 1 - Miriam Makeba Auditorium, Sat Feb 14 10:00 - Zoo Palast 2, Sat Feb 14 11:30 - Cubix 6, Sun Feb 15 13:15 - Cubix 6, Tue Feb 17 10:00 - HKW 1 - Miriam Makeba Auditorium, Sun Feb 22 16:15 - Cubix 6]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202609628.html</guid></item><item><title>Matapanki by Diego &quot;Mapache&quot; Fuentes</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202609924.html</link><description><![CDATA[Ricardo is a punk who spends his days drinking cheap alcohol, going to gigs and wandering the streets of the outskirts with his two best friends, Mella and Claudia. Beneath his tough exterior lies a fragile tenderness: he lives with and cares for his grandmother, Mar&iacute;a Luisa, the only emotional anchor in his chaotic life. One night, during a reckless drinking session, Ricardo tries a strange, clandestinely brewed alcoholic drink known as Matapanki. From that moment on, he gains alcohol-fuelled superpowers that activate every time he drinks the potion. This places Ricardo in a dilemma: he is unsure whether to become a superhero and embrace the responsibility of changing society. But when alcohol and rage take over, Ricardo recklessly springs into action and commits a brutal, irreversible mistake that ignites an international conflict.<br/>
Cast: by Diego "Mapache" Fuentes (Director), Diego "Mapache" Fuentes (Screenplay) Cast: Ramón Gávez, Diego Bravo, Antonia McCarthy, Rosa Peñaloza, Rodrigo Lisboa<br/>
Durata: 71 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/media/filmstills/2026/plakate-2026/202609924_9_ORG.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Tue Feb 17 19:00 - HKW 1 - Miriam Makeba Auditorium, Wed Feb 18 12:30 - Zoo Palast 1, Thu Feb 19 10:15 - Cubix 6, Sat Feb 21 16:15 - Cubix 6, Sun Feb 22 18:45 - Filmtheater am Friedrichshain]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202609924.html</guid></item><item><title>The Watermelon Woman by Cheryl Dunye</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202610071.html</link><description><![CDATA[Cheryl is a young Black lesbian who aspires to make movies and works in a video store. Researching the representation of Black lesbians in film history, she stumbles upon a bit player in the southern melodrama &ldquo;Plantation Memories&rdquo; identified in the opening credits as &ldquo;The Watermelon Woman&rdquo;. With interviews and snippets of found footage, Cheryl figures out who she really was: Fae Richards, a singer popular on the Philadelphia club circuit, who had a relationship with the film&rsquo;s white director, although the latter&rsquo;s sister denies it. Cheryl hopes for answers from Fae&rsquo;s long-term lover who, however, is well advanced in years &hellip;
 Director Cheryl Dunye sensuously weaves together elements of queer media studies with her heroine&rsquo;s crush on a white academic. At the same time, her mockumentary delivers a profound example of bringing your own story into a film, with a fictional narrative about an &ldquo;erased&rdquo; minority. Meanwhile, her interviews, including with feminist icon Camille Paglia at the (fictional) Center for Lesbian Information and Technology, or CLIT, most definitely simulate serious-mindedness.&nbsp;<em class="film">The Watermelon Woman</em> won the Teddy award for best narrative feature at the 1996 Berlinale.<br/>
Cast: by Cheryl Dunye (Director), Cheryl Dunye (Screenplay) Cast: Cheryl Dunye, Guinevere Turner, Valerie Walker, Lisa Marie Bronson, Cheryl Clarke, Irene Dunye, Brian Freeman, Ira Jeffries, Camille Paglia<br/>
Durata: 83 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202610071_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Mon Feb 16 22:00 - Zoo Palast 2, Tue Feb 17 16:00 - Deutsche Kinemathek – Halle, Thu Feb 19 17:00 - SİNEMA TRANSTOPIA]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202610071.html</guid></item><item><title>Se eu fosse vivo... vivia by André Novais Oliveira</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202610152.html</link><description><![CDATA[Brazil, the 1970s. Contagem is still a growing town and the home of a young couple in love. Gilberto asks for Jacira&rsquo;s forgiveness just before an unexpected encounter changes the course of their lives. Fifty years later, Gilberto and Jacira are still together. A charismatic and gentle couple in their mid-seventies, they lead a happy life despite the health problems that come with age, sharing almost all of their daily activities side by side. When Jacira is suddenly hospitalised, Gilberto begins to experience disturbing events &ndash; in a spiral through time and space &ndash; that lead him towards the unknown.<br/>
Cast: by André Novais Oliveira (Director), André Novais Oliveira (Screenplay) Cast: Conceição Evaristo, Norberto Novais Oliveira, Jean Paulo Campos, Tainá Evaristo<br/>
Durata: 101 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202610152_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sun Feb 15 15:15 - Zoo Palast 1, Mon Feb 16 21:45 - Cubix 9, Tue Feb 17 13:00 - Cubix 7, Wed Feb 18 21:45 - Filmtheater am Friedrichshain, Fri Feb 20 18:30 - Zoo Palast 1, Sat Feb 21 15:30 - Urania]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202610152.html</guid></item><item><title>Wo Men Bu Shi Mo Sheng Ren by Anthony Chen</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202610539.html</link><description><![CDATA[In bustling contemporary Singapore, 21-year-old Junyang is enjoying the ease of youth while his father struggles to hold their modest life together. When Junyang&rsquo;s relationship with his girlfriend takes an unexpected and life-altering turn, the young couple is forced to face the realities of adulthood far sooner than anticipated. At the same time, an exuberant woman enters his father&rsquo;s life and heart, quietly reshaping the fragile balance between father and son. As both generations confront love, loss and responsibility, they must redefine what family means &ndash; and learn to live with the imperfect bonds between the family they were born into and the one they now choose to love.<br/>
Cast: by Anthony Chen (Director), Anthony Chen (Screenplay) Cast: Yeo Yann Yann, Koh Jia Ler, Andi Lim, Regene Lim<br/>
Durata: 157 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202610539_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Mon Feb 16 14:45 - Berlinale Palast, Tue Feb 17 12:30 - HKW 1 - Miriam Makeba Auditorium, Wed Feb 18 15:15 - Uber Eats Music Hall, Thu Feb 19 21:15 - Haus der Berliner Festspiele, Sat Feb 21 12:15 - Urania]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202610539.html</guid></item><item><title>Flying Tigers by Madhusree Dutta</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202610591.html</link><description><![CDATA[Spurred by her Alzheimer&rsquo;s-afflicted mother&rsquo;s strange evocation of home-invading tigers, filmmaker Madhusree Dutta travels to Assam, India. Here, she learns about the Flying Tigers: US aircraft that transferred military supplies during WWII across the perilous Himalayas, from Assam to Kunming in China. So begins a globetrotting, decades-spanning docufiction essay on the human-scale experience of monumental logistical phenomena, featuring small histories that unfold in the quiet shadows of History writ large. Teaming up with Kunming-born media theorist Mi You and Assam-based researcher Purav Goswami, Dutta contrasts the smooth international flow of goods today with increasing restrictions on people&rsquo;s movement across borders. Her film reveals how lived realities of frontier populations have always been fluid and malleable, refusing the homogeneity demanded by cartographic political imagination. Appropriately, Dutta adopts a heterogeneous, genre-defying form, mixing interviews, archival material, performances, animation and musical numbers to craft a personal, wide-ranging work at once intimate and colossal.<br/>
Cast: by Madhusree Dutta (Director), Madhusree Dutta (Screenplay) Cast: Madhusree Dutta, Mi You, Purav Goswami, Devika Hazarika<br/>
Durata: 105 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/media/filmstills/2026/plakate-2026/202610591_9_ORG.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Mon Feb 16 15:00 - Cinema Betonhalle@Silent Green, Tue Feb 17 14:00 - Cinema Paris, Wed Feb 18 20:00 - CinemaxX 5, Sat Feb 21 17:30 - Cinema Paris]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202610591.html</guid></item><item><title>Chronicles From the Siege by Abdallah Alkhatib</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202610606.html</link><description><![CDATA[When their city is placed under siege, the lives of a group of ordinary people are turned upside down, forcing each of them to confront impossible choices in pursuit of survival in a war zone. Bodies and minds are equally under attack; and ordinary people are forced to reckon with starvation, inadequate medical treatment, snipers and bomb blasts, as they continue to live, seeking friendship, love, intimacy and the pleasure of a cigarette. At one point, a small group of cinephiles sheltering in their neighbourhood video store is confronted with the moral conundrum of whether or not to burn the movies they have rented, and cherish, to keep warm. The mental impact of the siege is boldly expressed in writing on the door of one of the characters in the ensemble which reads: &ldquo;I don&rsquo;t see my life outside the confines of the siege. And I don&rsquo;t see an end to the siege outside of the confines of my life.&rdquo;<br/>
Cast: by Abdallah Alkhatib (Director), Abdallah Alkhatib (Screenplay) Cast: Nadeem Rimawi, Saja Kilani, Ahmad Kontar, Samer Bisharat, Ahmed Zitouni, Wassim Fedriche, Idir Benaibouche, Abdallah Alkhatib, Emad Azmi, Maria Zreik, Omar Rammal, Hamzeh Mahadin, Nour Serraj, Hayet Abu Samar, Majd Hijawi, Omar Almajali<br/>
Durata: 98 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202610606_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sun Feb 15 16:00 - Bluemax Theater, Mon Feb 16 13:00 - Cubix 9, Tue Feb 17 10:30 - Cubix 8, Thu Feb 19 16:00 - Colosseum 1, Fri Feb 20 19:00 - Bluemax Theater]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202610606.html</guid></item><item><title>La casa de los espíritus</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202610672.html</link><description><![CDATA[Based on Isabel Allende&rsquo;s bestselling book, <em class="film">The House of the Spirits</em> is an eight-episode, multi-generational family saga spanning half a century, centred on the revolutionary Trueba women &ndash; Clara, Blanca and Alba &ndash; in a conservative South American country shaped by class struggle, political upheaval and magic. Told through Alba&rsquo;s perspective in the 1970s, the series moves between past and present as she turns to her grandmother Clara&rsquo;s diaries to make sense of her family&rsquo;s history and her country&rsquo;s fractured soul. Through Clara&rsquo;s memories, we trace the rise of the Trueba family alongside the violent entrenchment of social hierarchies, as love, power and ideology collide on a rural hacienda and in gilded halls. Across generations, the women of the family resist oppression through compassion, forbidden love and political awakening &ndash; until private lives and national history become inseparable, and memory itself emerges as the most radical act of survival.<br/>
Cast: by Francisca Alegría (Screenplay) Cast: Alfonso Herrera, Dolores Fonzi, Nicole Wallace, Fernanda Castillo, Antonia Zegers<br/>
Durata: 136 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202610672_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Mon Feb 16 20:30 - Haus der Berliner Festspiele, Tue Feb 17 21:30 - Colosseum 1, Thu Feb 19 16:00 - ADK am Hanseatenweg, Sun Feb 22 10:00 - Bluemax Theater]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202610672.html</guid></item><item><title>Meine Frau weint by Angela Schanelec</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202610706.html</link><description><![CDATA[An ordinary workday on a building site. Forty-year-old crane operator Thomas receives a call from his wife, Carla: he has to pick her up from the hospital. Once there, he finds her crying and discovers that she has had a car crash. Carla tells him about her dance partner David, with whom she was going to view a house in the country and who has died in the accident. She tries to tell her husband everything openly and honestly, but Thomas increasingly withdraws into himself. They simply do not understand each other. A film about the challenge that is life and about the search for a common language.<br/>
Cast: by Angela Schanelec (Director), Angela Schanelec (Screenplay) Cast: Vladimir Vulević, Agathe Bonitzer, Birte Schnöink, Pauline Rebmann, Ben Carter, Thorbjörn Björnsson, Clara Gostynski, Laure-Lucile Simon<br/>
Durata: 93 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202610706_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Tue Feb 17 21:45 - Berlinale Palast, Wed Feb 18 12:30 - Uber Eats Music Hall, Thu Feb 19 10:00 - Urania, Sat Feb 21 20:00 - Haus der Berliner Festspiele, Sun Feb 22 17:45 - Urania]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202610706.html</guid></item><item><title>Boyz n the Hood by John Singleton</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202611167.html</link><description><![CDATA[In violence-ridden South Central L.A. in 1984, 10-year-old Tre lives with his mother. She is worried about Tre&rsquo;s future and sends him to live with his father. Her ex-husband, Furious, is a real estate agent who is a strict father and exhorts his son to take responsibility for his actions. The lessons stick. Seven years later, Tre has matured into a serious young man, while other young men in the &rsquo;hood have landed in prison, become teen fathers or, in one case, been crippled by a gunshot wound. Tre and his friend Ricky, a football star, have plans to go to college. But then Ricky&rsquo;s half-brother provokes a confrontation with a local gangbanger.
 With its commitment to realistic discourse on the economic situation in the Black neighbourhood, its nuanced characters, and a hip-hop soundtrack, <em class="film">Boyz n the Hood</em> was intended to appeal to a broad audience, underlining that it was possible to escape the &rsquo;hood. Shot on location in South Central, it depicts both the strengths and the dysfunction of the Black community, ranging from a welfare recipient to a sadistic cop. For this, his debut film, John Singleton became the first African-American to be nominated for an Oscar as best director.<br/>
Cast: by John Singleton (Director), John Singleton (Screenplay) Cast: Laurence Fishburne, Ice Cube, Cuba Gooding Jr., Nia Long, Desi Arnez Hines II, Morris Chestnut, Tyra Ferrell, Angela Bassett, Meta King, Whitman Mayo<br/>
Durata: 112 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202611167_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Fri Feb 13 21:15 - ADK am Hanseatenweg, Tue Feb 17 19:00 - Cubix 5, Fri Feb 20 21:30 - Deutsche Kinemathek – Halle]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202611167.html</guid></item><item><title>D’Est by Chantal Akerman</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202611169.html</link><description><![CDATA[&ldquo;When I make a documentary film, I become an empty sponge, soaking up everything.&rdquo; <em class="film">D&rsquo;Est</em> is a road movie made up almost entirely of still lifes. Chronologically and without commentary, Chantel Akermann ties together her subjective impressions on a journey from West to East. She travels through Poland, Ukraine and Russia; from a summer day in East Germany to wintery Moscow, from carefree fun at the beach, through agrarian landscapes, all the way to snowy streets in the big city. The director filmed the things along the way that moved her &ndash; trees and bridges, men and women, the old and the young, in their living rooms and kitchens, out in the fields and dancing in the evening. The camera keeps its distance. The highlight of the travelogue is a travelling shot several minutes in length along labourers waiting at a bus station in Moscow, a cross-section of post-Soviet society.
 In 1993, Akerman said: &ldquo;Amid all that, I will show the faces that are isolated from the crowd, have something unaffected about them, so often express the opposite of the uniformity that sometimes strikes one with a crowd, and therefore the opposite of our uniformity.&rdquo;<br/>
Cast: by Chantal Akerman (Director), Chantal Akerman (Screenplay)<br/>
Durata: 115 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202611169_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sat Feb 14 19:00 - Cubix 5, Tue Feb 17 21:30 - Deutsche Kinemathek – Halle, Sun Feb 22 16:30 - Deutsche Kinemathek – Halle]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202611169.html</guid></item><item><title>Gorilla Bathes at Noon by Dušan Makavejev</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202611170.html</link><description><![CDATA[In 1991, the Yugoslavian Black Wave made its way to Berlin with director Du&scaron;an Makavejev, who shows us the post-Wall city from the perspective of one Major Lazutkin. Just released from the hospital, the officer realises that the Red Army left him behind when it withdrew and his wife has also moved on to greener pastures. Clad in his uniform and carrying a Soviet flag, the somewhat dim-witted outsider wanders around the reunified city, including a visit to the zoo. He naively gets involved in weapons and child trafficking, and becomes &ldquo;bewitched&rdquo; by an apparition of Vladimir Lenin, before a happy future as a family man appears to him.
 Using images of heroism from the Stalinist war propaganda film <em class="film-other">The Fall of Berlin</em> (USSR, 1949), Makavejev portrays the vicissitudes of history as theatre of the absurd in which changed political portents lead to a reappraisal of inherited values. The documentary highlight of his anarchic satire is footage of the dismantling under protest of a larger-than-life Lenin statue in Berlin&rsquo;s Friedrichshain neighbourhood, as well as a travelling shot along the East Side Gallery with its original graffiti, including the famed painting of the Fraternal Kiss.<br/>
Cast: by Dušan Makavejev (Director), Dušan Makavejev (Screenplay) Cast: Svetozar Cvetković, Anita Manćić, Alexandra Rohmig, Petar Bozović, Andreas Lucius, Eva Ras, Davor Janjić, Zoran Ratković, Suleyman Boyraz, Alfred Holighaus<br/>
Durata: 83 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202611170_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Tue Feb 17 17:00 - Cubix 5, Thu Feb 19 19:00 - Deutsche Kinemathek – Halle, Sat Feb 21 11:00 - Cubix 5]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202611170.html</guid></item><item><title>La double vie de Véronique by Krzysztof Kieślowski</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202611174.html</link><description><![CDATA[In 1990 Poland, singer Weronika feels that she is &ldquo;not alone in the world&rdquo;. And indeed, her double is living in France &ndash; V&eacute;ronique. The two almost meet in Krakow, but V&eacute;ronique is already riding off in a tour bus. Unbeknownst to her, she has inadvertently photographed Weronika. V&eacute;ronique is also a singer and, like her Polish counterpart, she also suffers from a heart condition. But while Weronika gives her life for song, V&eacute;ronique gives up singing and becomes a music teacher. At a puppet show, she falls in love with a puppeteer. When he calls her a few nights later, V&eacute;ronique suddenly hears the song that Weronika sang just before her death.
 The magic triangle of Krzysztof Kieślowski, actor Ir&egrave;ne Jacob and composer Zbigniew Preisner gives off an incandescent light. Using just a few historical anchors, the director takes ownership of the French post-modern style. Open to a variety of interpretations, the &ldquo;affairs of the heart&rdquo; depicted in the film, and the glowing golden light in both Poland and Paris, can be interpreted as the director&rsquo;s visions &ndash; of a latent spiritual kinship, but also as an aesthetic convergence between East and West Europe.<br/>
Cast: by Krzysztof Kieślowski (Director), Krzysztof Kieślowski (Screenplay) Cast: Irène Jacob, Philippe Volter, Sandrine Dumas, Halina Gryglaszewska, Kalina Jędrusik, Aleksander Bardini, Władysław Kowalski, Jerzy Gudejko<br/>
Durata: 98 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202611174_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sun Feb 15 15:00 - Cubix 5, Tue Feb 17 19:00 - Deutsche Kinemathek – Halle, Fri Feb 20 16:30 - Cubix 5]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202611174.html</guid></item><item><title>Videogramme einer Revolution by Harun Farocki</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202611186.html</link><description><![CDATA[&ldquo;Television is on our side! We have won!&rdquo; This chronicle of the 1989 revolution in Romania is put together from live coverage by the state broadcaster TVR and video recorded by numerous amateurs. Harun Farocki and Romanian writer and director Andrei Ujica had access to 125 hours of material, from which they compiled a minute-by-minute account of the period from December 21<sup>st</sup> to the 25<sup>th</sup>. Seen from multiple perspectives, these videograms cover the rapid succession of events from Nicolae Ceaușescu&rsquo;s last public speech in Bucharest to the execution of the dictator and his wife four days later. The digital images are condensed to shape a historical drama, and the audiovisual historiography takes on the form of a classic stage play: &ldquo;The people revolt, power is overthrown, the rulers are executed.&rdquo; In 1992, the directors said: &ldquo;Our goal was to untangle the existing bundle of images and edit them into sequences so that the viewer has the impression that they are moving through the same film loop from one camera to the next for five days.&rdquo; The work has been presented as an installation in museums, including in New York&rsquo;s Museum of Modern Art in 2023.<br/>
Cast: by Harun Farocki (Director), Andrei Ujica (Director)<br/>
Durata: 107 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202611186_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Mon Feb 16 21:30 - Deutsche Kinemathek – Halle, Tue Feb 17 14:30 - Cubix 5, Thu Feb 19 16:30 - Cubix 5]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202611186.html</guid></item><item><title>No Salgas by Victoria Linares Villegas</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202611243.html</link><description><![CDATA[Liz, a closeted gay college student pretending to be straight, is still haunted by the gruesome death of her girlfriend, Wendy. Desparate for escape, she joins her friends on a weekend trip away. But as Liz grows close to a mysterious young woman on the trip, unresolved sorrow and long-buried desires stir something unnatural within her. An unseen force that twists suspicion into violence spreads through the group, threatening to consume it. In a society where being seen can be dangerous, Liz must confront not only her grief, but also the brutal cost of being herself.<br/>
Cast: by Victoria Linares Villegas (Director), Victoria Linares Villegas (Screenplay) Cast: Cecile van Welie, Gabriela Cortés, Camila Issa, Camila Santana, Mariela Guerrero, Jonathan López, Johnny Morales, José Beato<br/>
Durata: 105 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/media/filmstills/2026/plakate-2026/202611243_9_RWD_1920.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sat Feb 14 16:50 - Cubix 6, Mon Feb 16 19:00 - HKW 1 - Miriam Makeba Auditorium, Tue Feb 17 15:45 - Filmtheater am Friedrichshain, Wed Feb 18 20:00 - Xenon Kino, Thu Feb 19 18:45 - Filmtheater am Friedrichshain, Fri Feb 20 10:00 - Zoo Palast 2, Sat Feb 21 19:00 - Cubix 6]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202611243.html</guid></item><item><title>Mint by Charlotte Regan</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202613250.html</link><description><![CDATA[Twenty-two-year-old Shannon is the daughter of the dominant crime family in the area. Standing in the shadow of her father Dylan, she is desperately searching for romance and falls head over heels for Arran, a member of a rival crime family which has recently arrived in town. They develop a deep bond that changes both their lives for good, but not everyone around them is willing to accept it. While Shannon and Arran are pursuing their forbidden love, elsewhere things are imploding for Shannon&rsquo;s family. However, rather than focusing on the crime world or the politics of succession, our gaze is directed towards the distinct emotional worlds of Shannon&rsquo;s family &ndash; her parents Dylan and Cat, her older brother Luke and her indomitable grandma Ollie.<br/>
Cast: by Charlotte Regan (Director), Charlotte Regan (Screenplay) Cast: Emma Laird, Ben Coyle-Larner, Sam Riley, Laura Fraser, Lindsay Duncan, Lewis Gribben<br/>
Durata: 113 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202613250_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sun Feb 15 19:00 - Zoo Palast 2, Mon Feb 16 18:45 - Cubix 9, Tue Feb 17 10:00 - Bluemax Theater, Fri Feb 20 14:30 - Urania]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202613250.html</guid></item><item><title>Entotsumachi no Poupelle – Yakusoku no Tokeidai by Hirota Yusuke</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202613780.html</link><description><![CDATA[A young boy called Lubicchi is filled with sorrow after losing his best friend, Poupelle. Then he accidentally wanders into a mysterious realm that governs time. In this world, any clock that stops ticking is immediately discarded. But one strange tower remains standing despite its clock being frozen at 11:59. Lubicchi discovers that the only way to return to his own world is to restart this stopped clock. Together with his companion, Fluff, he begins to unravel the mystery of the clock tower. During his journey, he encounters Gus, a man who has kept the faith and waited for a hundred years, and Nagi, a tree spirit who once took human form. When Lubicchi finally regains the courage to believe, a miracle occurs on Halloween night.<br/>
Cast: by Hirota Yusuke (Director), Nishino Akihiro (Screenplay) Cast: Nagase Yuzuna, Kubota Masataka<br/>
Durata: 98 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/media/filmstills/2026/plakate-2026/202613780_9_ORG.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Mon Feb 16 12:15 - Zoo Palast 1, Tue Feb 17 10:15 - Cubix 6, Thu Feb 19 16:00 - HKW 1 - Miriam Makeba Auditorium, Fri Feb 20 18:45 - Filmtheater am Friedrichshain, Sat Feb 21 13:15 - Cubix 6]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202613780.html</guid></item><item><title>Narciso by Marcelo Martinessi</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202614171.html</link><description><![CDATA[Paraguay, 1959. Asunci&oacute;n vibrates for the first time with a foreign rhythm. Rock &rsquo;n&rsquo; roll has found its way onto the radio carrying heat, speed and the faint illusion that the times might suddenly move forward. The city feels younger, looser &ndash; briefly out of sync with itself. At the same time, another rhythm settles in. Slower. Heavier. A disciplined pulse that orders gestures, silences voices and redraws the limits of what can be seen or desired. Words like virtue, decency, tradition begin to circulate with unusual force, shaping a shared fear. In this charged atmosphere, the charismatic musician Narciso becomes a symbol of freedom. His youth, his body, his way of inhabiting the night resonate with the music and with the threat it carries. Desire becomes visible. And visibility, dangerous. What once passed unnoticed now attracts attention, suspicion, judgment. As the regime consolidates its power, morality determines the situation &ndash; both intimate and oppressive. The future does not disappear all at once; it tightens. It learns to watch itself. Between dance and discipline, a new order takes shape, and an entire generation feels it closing in.<br/>
Cast: by Marcelo Martinessi (Director), Marcello Martinessi (Screenplay) Cast: Diro Romero, Manuel Cuenca, Arturo Fleitas, Margarita Irun, Mona Martinez, Nahuel Perez Biscayart<br/>
Durata: 101 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202614171_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Tue Feb 17 18:30 - Zoo Palast 1, Wed Feb 18 10:00 - Haus der Berliner Festspiele, Thu Feb 19 21:30 - Cubix 7, Sat Feb 21 22:00 - Cubix 6, Sun Feb 22 21:30 - Cubix 9]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202614171.html</guid></item><item><title>Shibire by Takuya Uchiyama</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202614502.html</link><description><![CDATA[In the snowy coastal city of Niigata, which is blanketed in grey skies and the roar of winter waves, Daichi, a boy who lost his voice under the tyranny of his father in early childhood, lives in a prefab room on the rooftop of an old multi-tenant building with his mother, Aki. She works in the nightlife trade, pours her earnings into men and is rarely home. The days of the two are defined by their extreme poverty and deep separation from society. The shy and withdrawn Daichi is searching for small traces of solace and love, yet finds no place to belong. Aki, now suffering from severe liver cirrhosis caused by years of alcoholism, moves with Daichi into the home of her sister, a devout follower of a new religious sect. There, Aki endures oppressive demands from her controlling lover, but clings to him even as she is harmed, while Daichi can do nothing but watch. Then, a faint light shines into his life: he experiences a sudden, breathtaking love and his fate, buffeted by forces far beyond his grasp, begins to shift.<br/>
Cast: by Takuya Uchiyama (Director), Takuya Uchiyama (Screenplay) Cast: Takumi Kitamura, Rie Miyazawa, Tsukasa Enomoto, Anji Kato, Masatoshi Nagase<br/>
Durata: 118 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/media/filmstills/2026/plakate-2026/202614502_9_RWD_1920.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sun Feb 15 21:30 - Urania, Mon Feb 16 10:00 - Cubix 9, Tue Feb 17 18:30 - Cubix 7, Wed Feb 18 10:15 - CinemaxX 5, Wed Feb 18 10:15 - CinemaxX 6, Fri Feb 20 21:30 - Cubix 5, Sat Feb 21 15:30 - Zoo Palast 1]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202614502.html</guid></item><item><title>Un hiver russe by Patric Chiha</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202615476.html</link><description><![CDATA[Following the full-scale invasion of Ukraine in 2022, many people in Russia face a weighty choice: military service, prison or exile. Margarita, Yuri and their friends refuse to comply with the regime and leave the country in search of a new home. They no longer have a place to which they can return, nor one where they feel truly welcome.<br/>
Cast: by Patric Chiha (Director), Patric Chiha (Screenplay)<br/>
Durata: 87 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202615476_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Tue Feb 17 13:00 - Bluemax Theater, Wed Feb 18 16:00 - Cubix 7, Thu Feb 19 10:00 - ADK am Hanseatenweg, Sat Feb 21 22:30 - Cubix 5, Sun Feb 22 10:15 - Cubix 7]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202615476.html</guid></item><item><title>Dao by Alain Gomis</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202615485.html</link><description><![CDATA[The film begins with a definition of its title: &ldquo;DAO is a perpetual and circular movement which flows in everything and unites the world.&rdquo; And then it proceeds to take us to the casting of Gloria, a character whose daughter is about to be married. An off-screen voice directing the casting session tells us that &ldquo;the first step is to make this family&rdquo;. Actors and non-actors are cast and brought together to become relatives who will all celebrate a wedding in Paris and commemorate the loss of their patriarch in Guinea-Bissau. Their individual stories and their common threads of heritage are woven together with fact and fiction as they travel between these two worlds; love, laughter, ritual, pain and history intertwined. Perpetual circular movement framing reality.<br/>
Cast: by Alain Gomis (Director), Alain Gomis (Screenplay) Cast: Katy Correa, D’Johé Kouadio, Samir Guesmi, Mike Etienne, Nicolas Gomis, Fara Baco Gomis, Poundo Gomis<br/>
Durata: 185 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202615485_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sat Feb 14 14:45 - Berlinale Palast, Mon Feb 16 10:00 - Uber Eats Music Hall, Tue Feb 17 20:30 - Haus der Berliner Festspiele, Wed Feb 18 16:45 - CinemaxX 6, Sun Feb 22 12:00 - Berlinale Palast]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202615485.html</guid></item><item><title>London by Sebastian Brameshuber</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202615540.html</link><description><![CDATA[Bobby is constantly in his car, driving back and forth on the autobahn linking Vienna and Salzburg. Other people travel the same route. Bobby picks them up to help with the petrol money and talks to them along the way: the soldier questioning what it means to fight; the supermarket trainee going to visit family; the academic researching the road&rsquo;s history; the queer woman about to get married. Many different paths, different accents and different stories, most of them true. Bobby listens, but also talks about himself, about his youth, about aging, about his friend in a coma in Salzburg who is the reason for all his trips. Mountains and forests pass by outside, broken up by junctions, barriers and bridges; the quality of light shifts along with the seasons. Neither a documentary, nor entirely fiction, <em class="film">London</em> is a quietly political portrait of today&rsquo;s Europe via its in-between spaces and those passing through them. Even in these strange times, anonymity and kindness can still go hand in hand.<br/>
Cast: by Sebastian Brameshuber (Director), Sebastian Brameshuber (Screenplay) Cast: Bobby Sommer<br/>
Durata: 122 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/media/filmstills/2026/plakate-2026/202615540_9_RWD_1920.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Mon Feb 16 18:45 - Zoo Palast 2, Tue Feb 17 16:00 - Cubix 6, Wed Feb 18 18:30 - Cubix 7, Sat Feb 21 21:45 - Cubix 9, Sun Feb 22 10:00 - Urania]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202615540.html</guid></item><item><title>Lola rennt by Tom Tykwer</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202615578.html</link><description><![CDATA[Lola has to come up with 100,000 marks in the next 20 minutes. If she fails, a Berlin racketeer will kill her boyfriend, a bagman who screwed up and left the loot in the metro. Three sequences show Lola&rsquo;s three attempts to get the money. The first involves a store robbery, the second a bank robbery. On the third run-through, Lola heads to a casino.
 A fairy-tale motif meets the dramatic structure of a video game. The three variations are slightly time-shifted, and the three plot twists have life-altering consequences, including for secondary characters. Playing out the three scenarios as breakneck flash-forward photo stories is part of a post-modern bricolage for which Tom Tykwer tapped all the resources of cinema. Driven by trance and techno tracks, <em class="film">Run Lola Run</em> is a cinematic loop, with video and 35 mm film, colour and black-and-white, split screens and slow motion, jump cuts and match cuts, animation and 360-degree dolly shots all wed together in a playful exploration of parallel realities &ndash; and in the first German film for the 21st century. The editing gives us a metropolitan Berlin in which East and West have merged into an imaginary playing field.<br/>
Cast: by Tom Tykwer (Director), Tom Tykwer (Screenplay) Cast: Franka Potente, Moritz Bleibtreu, Herbert Knaup, Nina Petri, Joachim Król, Armin Rohde, Heino Ferch, Suzanne von Borsody, Lars Rudolph, Ludger Pistor<br/>
Durata: 81 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202615578_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Tue Feb 17 21:45 - ADK am Hanseatenweg, Sun Feb 22 21:30 - ADK am Hanseatenweg]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202615578.html</guid></item><item><title>The Day of Wrath: Tales from Tripoli by Rania Rafei</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202615703.html</link><description><![CDATA[The history of a city, its wars and uprisings. Taking the student protests that ushered in independence from France in 1943 as a starting point, Rania Rafei traces the back and forth between upheaval and consistency, discord and unity in Tripoli, Lebanon&rsquo;s second-biggest city. Connecting the personal and the political as well as the intimate and the collective, the film gives the city and its inhabitants a stage across different eras and generations, employing an open form that combines a cinematic letter to her dead father, family stories, archive material and the exploration of a present in which history has been forgotten. Listening, voiceover: ordered chronologically, kaleidoscopic in its effect. The hopes surrounding the Pan-Arabism of the 1960s and defeat in the Six-Day War are followed by days of fury &ndash; in the factions that formed during and after the civil war, and the protests since 2019 against the catastrophic economic situation, omnipresent corruption and the sectarian system. A film as an act of political tenderness between confidence and disillusionment, wrangling and confession. The desire for change is strong.<br/>
Cast: by Rania Rafei (Director), Rania Rafei (Screenplay)<br/>
Durata: 120 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202615703_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Tue Feb 17 17:30 - Cinema Paris, Wed Feb 18 10:00 - ADK am Hanseatenweg, Sat Feb 21 16:30 - Cubix 8]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202615703.html</guid></item><item><title>Beaucoup parler by Pascale Bodet</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202615708.html</link><description><![CDATA[Amre and Pascale live and move around within the same residential area in Paris. He is an immigrant from Egypt without papers for 17 years, she is a filmmaker and critic. When Amr asks Pascale for help in dealing with the authorities, she asks him if she can film how they fare. <em class="film">Beaucoup parler</em>: what Amre cannot express in words in French &ndash; his thoughts, his fears and living circumstances &ndash; Pascale attempts to gauge and translate. An excruciatingly funny, honest process of understanding in which baker Karim pragmatically intervenes from time to time, being well aware of all the scattered experiences it entails. And so the two of them, she ladylike, he mischievous, put on a real-life migration fairy tale in their neighbourhood. Both of them simultaneously play themselves and the exaggerated roles which populate debates about immigration not just in France. For despite a mix of French, Arabic-French and Google Translate, true gibberish is far from being reached. It is the language of the immigration office that is by far the least comprehensible in this clear-sighted film about opportunities in life and loss of chance.<br/>
Cast: by Pascale Bodet (Director), Pascale Bodet (Screenplay) Cast: Amr Hanafy<br/>
Durata: 78 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202615708_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Fri Feb 13 14:30 - Cinema Paris, Sat Feb 14 21:30 - Cubix 8, Tue Feb 17 21:30 - CinemaxX 5, Tue Feb 17 21:30 - CinemaxX 6]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202615708.html</guid></item><item><title>Was an Empfindsamkeit bleibt by Daniela Magnani Hüller</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202615725.html</link><description><![CDATA[A film like a house full of dark chambers long closed. Yet every room will be opened: puppet shows, butterflies, colour, light! This autobiographical documentary debut sets out to deprive silence of its power. Fourteen years ago, the director survived an attempted femicide carried out by a schoolmate, who had harassed her before. An act whose subjective and objective inconceivability Daniela Magnani H&uuml;ller will not accept. In images of great sensitivity, she uncovers memories, makes her voice audible in voiceover, enabling herself to find a stronger, own perspective &ndash; on what happened, the present of the trauma, a future life without fear. She wants conversations to happen and conducts them in large spaces often shot with considerable distance, with a teacher, a school friend, a detective, the state prosecutor; trying to find out why each of them did (or did not) act the way they did. Matter-of-fact, consistent and impressively composed, she reconstructs events and failures and &ndash; years after the crime &ndash; poses the question of responsibility: to the individuals, the school, the justice system and society. Violence against women &ndash; the unfolding of an internal and external perspective.<br/>
Cast: by Daniela Magnani Hüller (Director), Daniela Magnani Hüller (Screenplay)<br/>
Durata: 91 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/media/filmstills/2026/plakate-2026/202615725_9_RWD_1920.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sun Feb 15 14:30 - Cinema Paris, Tue Feb 17 16:30 - Cubix 8, Sat Feb 21 18:30 - Cinema Betonhalle@Silent Green]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202615725.html</guid></item><item><title>Filipiñana by Rafael Manuel</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202615741.html</link><description><![CDATA[The Maynila Country Club is a 74-hectare compound with enough facilities to keep the creme-de-la-creme of Philippine society distracted and insulated from the country&rsquo;s socio-political problems. Among its facilities is the driving range where 17-year-old Isabel works as a tee-girl. Despite being new to her job, she starts slipping away from the driving range to explore the lush greenery of the surrounding golf course which reminds her of the hometown she has left behind. On the course, she spots Dr. Palanca, a man in his 60s who is the club&rsquo;s president. Isabel develops an infatuation with him and, eventually, has the chance to meet him when she is tasked with returning a golf iron he has left behind. Isabel explores the various alcoves of the country club&rsquo;s facilities looking for Dr. Palanca, but is unable to find him. Instead, she uncovers a clearer, deeply disenchanting portrait of the country club and of Dr. Palanca himself.<br/>
Cast: by Rafael Manuel (Director), Rafael Manuel (Screenplay) Cast: Jorrybell Agoto, Carmen Castellanos, Teroy Guzman, Carlitos Siguion-Reyna, Nour Hooshmand, Isabel Sicat<br/>
Durata: 100 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/media/filmstills/2026/plakate-2026/202615741_9_RWD_1920.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sun Feb 15 19:15 - Bluemax Theater, Mon Feb 16 16:00 - Cubix 9, Tue Feb 17 22:30 - Cubix 8, Thu Feb 19 13:00 - Colosseum 1, Thu Feb 19 20:00 - SİNEMA TRANSTOPIA, Fri Feb 20 14:15 - Cubix 9]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202615741.html</guid></item><item><title>A Prayer for the Dying by Dara Van Dusen</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202615874.html</link><description><![CDATA[In 1870, the town of Friendship, Wisconsin, is enduring a dry, hot summer. The small town revolves around Jacob Hansen (Johnny Flynn), a hero of the American Civil War who, in spite of his many accomplishments, is unable to cast off the violence and darkness of his past as a soldier. Feeling compelled to atone for the wrongs he has committed, Jacob takes on the responsibility not only of providing for his young family but also of serving as sheriff, undertaker and pastor for Friendship. He thus considers Friendship to be under his protection &ndash; a claim that comes to haunt him when the town is hit by an epidemic that the town&rsquo;s doctor (John C. Reilly) cannot contain. As every decision becomes a choice between two evils, Jacob is increasingly haunted by his war-ridden past. It is unclear how much longer he can continue in his self-imposed role as the town&rsquo;s protector or whether he will ever be able to forgive himself for what he has done. <em class="film">A Prayer for the Dying</em>&nbsp;is a powerful account of the choices we must make when disaster strikes and everything we hold dear, including faith, family and community, is shaken to its very core.<br/>
Cast: by Dara Van Dusen (Director), Dara Van Dusen (Screenplay) Cast: Johnny Flynn, John C. Reilly, Kristine Kujath Thorp, Gustav Lindh<br/>
Durata: 95 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202615874_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Fri Feb 13 21:45 - Bluemax Theater, Sat Feb 14 18:45 - Cubix 9, Sun Feb 15 16:30 - Cubix 8, Tue Feb 17 13:00 - Colosseum 1, Wed Feb 18 16:00 - Bluemax Theater]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202615874.html</guid></item><item><title>Heysel 85 by Teodora Ana Mihai</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202615949.html</link><description><![CDATA[Heysel Stadium, Brussels, May 1985. Thirty-year-old Marie, daughter and press attach&eacute; of the mayor of Brussels, attends the European Cup Final between Juventus and Liverpool FC with her parents. Also present is 31-year-old Luca Rossi, a journalist covering the match for Italian TV, accompanied by family who have arrived from Italy. Before kick-off, hooligans go on the rampage. Dozens of people die; chaos ensues. While continuing to report, Luca searches for his family. And Marie has to step in for her father who, drunk and overwhelmed, is no longer capable of taking command. The politicians and police are faced with the question: cancel the match or let it go on? As fear takes hold that stopping the game could escalate the situation further, a questionable decision takes shape.<br/>
Cast: by Teodora Ana Mihai (Director), Lode Desmet (Screenplay) Cast: Violet Braeckman, Matteo Simoni, Josse De Pauw, Fabrizio Rongione, Paolo Calabresi, Bobby Schofield, Ben Segers<br/>
Durata: 91 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202615949_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sat Feb 14 18:30 - Zoo Palast 1, Sun Feb 15 10:45 - ADK am Hanseatenweg, Mon Feb 16 22:00 - HKW 1 - Miriam Makeba Auditorium, Tue Feb 17 19:00 - Uber Eats Music Hall, Tue Feb 17 20:00 - BALI KINO, Thu Feb 19 10:00 - Uber Eats Music Hall]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202615949.html</guid></item><item><title>Allegro Pastell by Anna Roller</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202615975.html</link><description><![CDATA[<em class="film">Allegro Pastell</em> tells the story of a long-distance relationship that is almost flawless. At its core lie the individual perceptions of two lovers who have mostly had things go their way and who seem to have everything under control. Tanja is 33 and lives in Berlin as an up-and-coming writer. Jerome is 35, works as a web designer and has returned to his Hessian hometown of Maintal near Frankfurt, moving into the bungalow left by his parents. The couple visit each other often and remain constantly connected through email. A website for Tanja &ndash; intended as a 34<sup>th</sup>-birthday gift from Jerome &ndash; unexpectedly leads to the first rupture in their relationship. The two lovers drift apart, draw close again, then risk losing each other once more &hellip; A generational and mood-driven story, rendered in the pastel tones of a beautiful memory &ndash; thoughtful, entertaining, and tinged with melancholy.<br/>
Cast: by Anna Roller (Director), Leif Randt (Screenplay) Cast: Sylvaine Faligant, Jannis Niewöhner, Haley Louise Jones, Luna Wedler, Martina Gedeck<br/>
Durata: 100 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202615975_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sat Feb 14 15:30 - Zoo Palast 1, Sun Feb 15 21:30 - Cubix 9, Mon Feb 16 10:00 - Cubix 7, Tue Feb 17 21:45 - Filmtheater am Friedrichshain, Sat Feb 21 09:30 - Haus der Berliner Festspiele]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202615975.html</guid></item><item><title>Queen at Sea by Lance Hammer</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202616031.html</link><description><![CDATA[Amanda and her stepfather, Martin, struggle with a moral issue that divides them. Has Amanda&rsquo;s mother, Leslie, who is suffering from advanced dementia, lost the ability to make critical decisions in her own best interests? And, if so, who is responsible &ndash; a spouse, a child, an institution &ndash; for making such a determination? As Amanda and Martin are forced to make increasingly difficult choices, the repercussions spiral out of their control.<br/>
Cast: by Lance Hammer (Director), Lance Hammer (Screenplay) Cast: Juliette Binoche, Tom Courtenay, Anna Calder-Marshall, Florence Hunt<br/>
Durata: 121 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202616031_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Tue Feb 17 18:15 - Berlinale Palast, Wed Feb 18 12:45 - HKW 1 - Miriam Makeba Auditorium, Thu Feb 19 21:30 - Uber Eats Music Hall, Sat Feb 21 15:45 - Uber Eats Music Hall]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202616031.html</guid></item><item><title>Only Rebels Win by Danielle Arbid</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202616058.html</link><description><![CDATA[Beirut, Lebanon. Suzanne gets to know Osmane after saving him from a racist attack. Osmane is Sudanese, young, undocumented and searching for a better future. Suzanne is a middle-class widow with Palestinian roots, a mother of two adult children and well over twice his age. Unexpectedly, the two lonely souls open up to each other and connect. Shy at first, they grow closer, until they admit they are in love. As a fractured Lebanon teeters on the brink of collapse, their relationship provokes a wave of anger and indignation all around them. Suzanne&rsquo;s children stop seeing her. Colleagues turn their backs on her. Priests refuse to marry them. Their neighbours call the police on them. The same people who threw the country into civil war now stand there, judging, forcing Suzanne and Osmane to face the hostility, and to resist.<br/>
Cast: by Danielle Arbid (Director), Danielle Arbid (Screenplay) Cast: Hiam Abbass, Amine Benrachid, Shaden Fakih, Charbel Kamel, Alexandre Paulikevitch<br/>
Durata: 98 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202616058_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Thu Feb 12 21:00 - Zoo Palast 1, Thu Feb 12 21:30 - Zoo Palast 2, Fri Feb 13 15:00 - Uber Eats Music Hall, Sat Feb 14 10:00 - Cubix 9, Tue Feb 17 17:00 - CinemaxX 5, Tue Feb 17 17:00 - CinemaxX 6, Thu Feb 19 22:00 - Cubix 6, Sat Feb 21 18:30 - Zoo Palast 1]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202616058.html</guid></item><item><title>Paradise by Jérémy Comte</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202616065.html</link><description><![CDATA[In Ghana, Kojo is a teenager torn between the freedom of the streets of Accra and the traditional values of his father, a fisherman. Then, during a storm, his father disappears at sea. Devastated and short on money, Kojo enters the world of street gangs. He rises quickly through the ranks, but his success fails to fill the void inside him. Meanwhile, in Quebec, Tony, a rebellious yet sensitive teenager, lives with his mother, Chantal. When he discovers her long-distance relationship with a mysterious cargo ship captain, Tony begins to suspect that this man might be the father he has never known. <em class="film">Paradise</em> is a story of distance, trust and the quiet gravity that binds us.<br/>
Cast: by Jérémy Comte (Director), Will Niava (Screenplay) Cast: Daniel Atsu Hukporti, Joey Boivin Desmeules, Evelyne de la Chenelière<br/>
Durata: 90 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202616065_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sat Feb 14 18:30 - Urania, Sun Feb 15 18:45 - Cubix 7, Mon Feb 16 13:00 - Cubix 6, Tue Feb 17 19:15 - CinemaxX 5, Tue Feb 17 19:15 - CinemaxX 6, Thu Feb 19 10:45 - Colosseum 1, Sat Feb 21 22:30 - Zoo Palast 2]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202616065.html</guid></item><item><title>Una mujer fantástica by Sebastián Lelio</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202616096.html</link><description><![CDATA[Marina and Orlando are in love and plan to spend their lives together. She is working as a waitress and adores singing. Her lover, twenty years her senior, has left his family for her. One night, when they return home after having exuberantly celebrated Marina&rsquo;s birthday at a restaurant, Orlando suddenly turns deathly pale and stops responding. At the hospital, all the doctors can do is confirm his death. Events follow thick and fast: Marina finds herself facing a female police inspector&rsquo;s unpleasant questions, and Orlando&rsquo;s family shows her nothing but anger and mistrust. Orlando&rsquo;s wife excludes Marina from the funeral; she also orders her to leave the apartment &ndash; which on paper at least belonged to Orlando &ndash; as soon as possible. Marina is a transgender woman. The deceased&rsquo;s family feels threatened by her sexual identity. With the same energy she once used to fight for her right to live as a woman, Marina, with her head held high, now insists on her right to grieve. Even if her environment conspires against her, the film at least is entirely on her side, showing us a protagonist who, although increasingly sidelined, is nonetheless strong and worldly-wise &ndash; a truly fantastic woman.<br/>
Cast: by Sebastián Lelio (Director), Sebastián Lelio (Screenplay) Cast: Daniela Vega, Francisco Reyes, Luis Gnecco, Aline Kuppenheim, Nicolas Saavedra, Amparo Noguera, Nestor Cantillana, Alejandro Goic, Antonia Zegers, Sergio Hernandez<br/>
Durata: 104 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202616096_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Tue Feb 17 22:00 - Zoo Palast 2, Wed Feb 18 16:00 - Deutsche Kinemathek – Halle]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202616096.html</guid></item><item><title>Black Lions – Roman Wolves by Haile Gerima</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202616228.html</link><description><![CDATA[In 1896, Ethiopia gained victory over Italy, hitting back at its first attempt to conquer the East African country. When Mussolini and the fascists came to power in 1922, the still abstract risk of a further attack became concrete. In 1935, Italy began an assault on Ethiopia once again, subjecting the country to a brutal war, not shying away from the use of poisonous gas: a crime, paradoxically, at once omnipresent and barely remembered in today&rsquo;s Italy. Haile Gerima, veteran of the L.A. Rebellion and New Black Cinema, worked for 30 years on his monumental exploration of the history and mythology of Italian colonialism, and also commemoration of the Ethiopian resistance. From archive material, conversations with historical witnesses and his father&rsquo;s plays, he weaves together a panorama of self-affirmation and colonial murder, of European complicity and Black solidarity. <em class="film">Black Lions &ndash; Roman Wolves</em> sets Ethiopian voices against lasting colonialist lies &ndash; and the recordings of the resistance against the reproduction of colonial images; against the entrenched visual dominance of the colonisers. A film for the present as well as for the coming decades.<br/>
Cast: by Haile Gerima (Director), Haile Gerima (Screenplay)<br/>
Durata: 531 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202616228_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Mon Feb 16 15:00 - Delphi Filmpalast, Tue Feb 17 16:00 - Delphi Filmpalast, Wed Feb 18 10:00 - CinemaxX 9, Wed Feb 18 14:30 - CinemaxX 9]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202616228.html</guid></item><item><title>Teddy Talents Talks: Confusion as Catalyst</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202616253.html</link><description><![CDATA[In this fourth edition of the Teddy Talents Talks, a joint venture of the TEDDY AWARD, Queer Academy and <em class="program">Berlinale Talents</em>, we invite five film professionals to reflect on the conceptual power of the queer form. How does queer cinema and us as creators, navigate the tension between ambiguity and transgression? Does that, what defies categorization, open the door to radical insight and play with this very disorientation to create new forms? By queering cinematic form, tracing new trajectories through heteronormative lines, perhaps we uncover a kind of brilliance that only emerges from the margins?<br/>
Durata: 90 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202616253_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Tue Feb 17 17:00 - Radialsystem]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202616253.html</guid></item><item><title>A Family by Mees Peijnenburg</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202616575.html</link><description><![CDATA[Fourteen-year-old Eli and 16-year-old Nina are both suffering in the breakdown of their parents&rsquo; once loving marriage. In the battle for custody, the siblings must express their wishes, fears and feelings to a judge. While Nina wants to get away from the family as soon as possible, Eli longs for everything to return to how it was before. Their desires are miles apart. Told in two chapters, the film follows the same three weeks twice: first from Nina&rsquo;s perspective and then from Eli&rsquo;s. These mirrored timelines reveal how the same moments can be lived, felt and understood in entirely different ways. Eli and Nina retreat into their own isolated worlds until Nina begins to realise that her younger brother has been carrying the same weight all along, quietly, invisibly, beside her. He has always been there; it is only now that she is truly seeing him. Eli, meanwhile, comes to understand that Nina&rsquo;s turning away from him was not a rejection but an act of survival and she has been struggling as much as he has. Beneath their opposing choices lies the same longing: for love, recognition and emotional security. <em class="film">A Family</em> reveals how love can fracture under pressure but still find its way back home.<br/>
Cast: by Mees Peijnenburg (Director), Bastiaan Kroeger (Screenplay) Cast: Finn Vogels, Celeste Holsheimer, Carice van Houten, Pieter Embrechts<br/>
Durata: 89 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202616575_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sun Feb 15 12:30 - Zoo Palast 1, Mon Feb 16 16:00 - HKW 1 - Miriam Makeba Auditorium, Tue Feb 17 18:45 - Filmtheater am Friedrichshain, Wed Feb 18 10:15 - Cubix 6, Sat Feb 21 19:45 - HKW 1 - Miriam Makeba Auditorium]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202616575.html</guid></item><item><title>Vier minus drei by Adrian Goiginger</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202616642.html</link><description><![CDATA[Barbara and her partner Heli lead a happy and loving family life with their two children, Fini and Thimo. As professional clowns, they do not take life too seriously and try to laugh at whatever fails to work out. But when Barbara suddenly loses her family to a car accident, her world falls apart. The loss makes her question her existence as a clown and the meaning of her own life. Yet Barbara confronts her fate. Courageous and unconventional, she finds her own way of dealing with her grief. Step by step, she realises that life goes on despite everything &ndash; if you dare to embrace it anew.<br/>
Cast: by Adrian Goiginger (Director), Senad Halilbašić (Screenplay) Cast: Valerie Pachner, Robert Stadlober, Stefanie Reinsperger, Hanno Koffler, Margarethe Tiesel, Paul Wolff-Plottegg, Michael Gampe, Petra Morzé, Michael Fuith, Ronald Zehrfeld<br/>
Durata: 121 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202616642_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Mon Feb 16 18:00 - Zoo Palast 1, Tue Feb 17 10:45 - Haus der Berliner Festspiele, Wed Feb 18 21:45 - Cubix 7, Fri Feb 20 16:45 - Kino Casablanca, Sat Feb 21 10:00 - Cubix 9, Sun Feb 22 15:00 - Urania]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202616642.html</guid></item><item><title>Kurtuluş by Emin Alper</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202616780.html</link><description><![CDATA[In a remote village high in the Turkish mountains, the return of an exiled clan reignites a decades-old land feud. While dormant resentments resurface, Mesut, the local leader&rsquo;s brother, is seized by unsettling visions. Believing them to be divine warnings, he starts to challenge his brother&rsquo;s leadership. Religious convictions, power struggles and tensions surge in the community. Will this all lead to tragedy or salvation?<br/>
Cast: by Emin Alper (Director), Emin Alper (Screenplay) Cast: Caner Cindoruk, Berkay Ateş, Feyyaz Duman, Naz Göktan, Özlem Taş<br/>
Durata: 120 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202616780_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sun Feb 15 15:15 - Berlinale Palast, Mon Feb 16 21:45 - Uber Eats Music Hall, Tue Feb 17 21:45 - HKW 1 - Miriam Makeba Auditorium, Sun Feb 22 12:30 - Haus der Berliner Festspiele]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202616780.html</guid></item><item><title>World Cinema Fund Talk: Alain Gomis</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202616897.html</link><description><![CDATA[Co-hosted by the World Cinema Fund, Alain Gomis (Silver Bear Grand Jury Prize for <em class="film-other">F&eacute;licit&eacute;</em>) joins to discuss his filmmaking practice shaped across borders, various languages, and production contexts. With this year&#39;s <em class="program">Competition</em> entry <em class="film-other">Dao</em>, Alain Gomis explores new artistic choices and the challenges of financing and positioning diasporic films that fall into neither European nor African categories. The conversation places the film within his broader journey, marked by stories of disorientation, resilience, and characters seeking belonging. It also highlights his role as a cultural leader in Senegal through the Yennenga Center in Dakar, a training and screening hub for young filmmakers, reflecting his belief in cinema as a humanist in a community-driven practice.<br/>
Durata: 90 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/767px/202616897_1.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Tue Feb 17 11:15 - Radialsystem]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/202616897.html</guid></item><item><title>14plus Short Films 1</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/2026334530.html</link><description><![CDATA[Durata: 127 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/_platzhalter.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Tue Feb 17 12:30 - Urania, Wed Feb 18 19:15 - Cubix 6, Thu Feb 19 10:00 - Bluemax Theater, Fri Feb 20 12:45 - Filmtheater am Friedrichshain, Sun Feb 22 15:15 - Zoo Palast 2]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/2026334530.html</guid></item><item><title>Kplus Short Films 3</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/2026335050.html</link><description><![CDATA[Durata: 109 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/_platzhalter.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Mon Feb 16 09:30 - Zoo Palast 1, Tue Feb 17 10:00 - Zoo Palast 2, Wed Feb 18 18:45 - Filmtheater am Friedrichshain, Fri Feb 20 16:15 - Cubix 6, Sun Feb 22 12:45 - Filmtheater am Friedrichshain]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/2026335050.html</guid></item><item><title>Kplus Short Films 1</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/2026335360.html</link><description><![CDATA[Durata: 98 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/_platzhalter.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Tue Feb 17 09:30 - Zoo Palast 1, Wed Feb 18 12:45 - Filmtheater am Friedrichshain, Fri Feb 20 09:45 - Filmtheater am Friedrichshain, Sat Feb 21 10:15 - Cubix 6, Sun Feb 22 13:30 - Cubix 6]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/2026335360.html</guid></item><item><title>Programme 9</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/2026336050.html</link><description><![CDATA[Durata: 143 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/_platzhalter.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Tue Feb 17 21:00 - Cinema Betonhalle@Silent Green, Sat Feb 21 15:30 - Cinema Betonhalle@Silent Green]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/2026336050.html</guid></item><item><title>Programme 4</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/2026336140.html</link><description><![CDATA[Durata: 127 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/_platzhalter.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sun Feb 15 17:30 - Cinema Betonhalle@Silent Green, Tue Feb 17 18:00 - Cinema Betonhalle@Silent Green]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/2026336140.html</guid></item><item><title>Programme 8</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/2026336150.html</link><description><![CDATA[Durata: 110 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/_platzhalter.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Tue Feb 17 15:30 - Cinema Betonhalle@Silent Green]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/2026336150.html</guid></item><item><title>Berlinale Shorts 1</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/2026339670.html</link><description><![CDATA[Durata: 85 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/_platzhalter.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sat Feb 14 09:30 - Cubix 5, Sun Feb 15 18:15 - Urania, Mon Feb 16 21:30 - Colosseum 1, Tue Feb 17 16:00 - Zoo Palast 2, Wed Feb 18 16:30 - Cubix 8, Fri Feb 20 12:00 - Cinema Betonhalle@Silent Green]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/2026339670.html</guid></item><item><title>Berlinale Shorts 3</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/2026339830.html</link><description><![CDATA[Durata: 91 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/_platzhalter.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sat Feb 14 13:10 - Cubix 5, Tue Feb 17 18:15 - Urania, Wed Feb 18 12:00 - Cinema Betonhalle@Silent Green, Wed Feb 18 19:00 - Colosseum 1, Thu Feb 19 16:00 - Zoo Palast 2, Sun Feb 22 16:30 - Cubix 8]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/2026339830.html</guid></item><item><title>Berlinale Shorts 2</title><link>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/2026340010.html</link><description><![CDATA[Durata: 85 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://www.berlinale.de/external/programme/current/filmstills/_platzhalter.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sat Feb 14 11:20 - Cubix 5, Mon Feb 16 18:15 - Urania, Tue Feb 17 12:00 - Cinema Betonhalle@Silent Green, Tue Feb 17 18:30 - Colosseum 1, Wed Feb 18 16:00 - Zoo Palast 2, Thu Feb 19 16:30 - Cubix 8]]></description><guid>https://www.berlinale.de/en/2026/programme/2026340010.html</guid></item></channel></rss>