<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The New Beverly Cinema</title><link>https://thenewbev.com/schedule/</link><description>Schedule and program for The New Beverly Cinema (Quentin Tarantino&apos;s revival theater in Los Angeles).</description><item><title>The Lickerish Quartet       / Therese and Isabelle</title><link>https://thenewbev.com/program/march-22-the-lickerish-quartet-therese-and-isabelle</link><description><![CDATA[An aristocratic married couple and their adult son decide to end their boring night watching stag films by visiting a traveling carnival. When the trio realize that one of the stars of the stunt show bears a striking resemblance to one of the performers in the film they’ve just watched, they invite her back to their castle for a night of mind-bending fun and games that’ll see each of the members of the family fulfill their deepest fantasies.  Dubbed “an outrageously kinky masterpiece” by Andy Warhol, Radley Metzger’s The Lickerish Quartet is a deliriously psychedelic – yet classily elegant! – classic of softcore erotica. (Muscle Distribution)

One of erotic arthouse auteur Radley Metzger’s best loved but rarely screened films follows a pair of young students at a prestigious Swiss boarding school for girls, whose affectionate friendship flowers into something more.  Stunningly shot in black and white Panavision by director of photography Hans Jura and featuring a lush score by Georges Auric.

Print courtesy of the Nicolas Winding Refn Collection<br/>
Cast: Director: Radley Metzger | Starring: Silvana Venturelli, Frank Wolff, Erika Remberg, Paolo Turco | Year: 1970 | Country: Italy/West Germany/USA | Format: 35mm | Director: Radley Metzger | Writer: Screenplay by Jesse Vogel based on the novel by Violette Leduc | Starring: Essy Persson, Anna Gaël, Barbara Laage, Anne Vernon | Year: 1968 | Country: France/Netherlands/USA/West Germany | Format: 35mm<br/>
Durata: 118 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://thenewbev.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/02/Lickerish-Quartet-featured.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sun March 22 - 6:30 pm / 8:30 pm]]></description><guid>https://thenewbev.com/program/march-22-the-lickerish-quartet-therese-and-isabelle</guid></item><item><title>Faster, Pussycat! Kill! Kill!       / Motorpsycho</title><link>https://thenewbev.com/program/march-6-faster-pussycat-kill-kill-motorpsycho</link><description><![CDATA[Ladies and gentlemen – welcome to violence! Celebrate the greatest girl-power grindhouse explosion to ever ignite the screen as well as pay tribute to the legendary sexploitation maestro and breastman extraordinaire behind it all, the King of the Nudies himself, Russ Meyer! Go-Go for a wild ride with three buxom, larger-than-life superwomen, Tura Satana, Haji & Lori Williams, as they Watusi across the Mojave Desert destroying every man who dares stand in their way. These outlaw hellcats drive fast, kick ass and look great while pushing the boundaries of being bad. Full of pop imagery, exuberant action and kinetic excitement, Faster, Pussycat! Kill! Kill! is one of the most iconic cult films EVER! Don’t miss it!

“ Faster, Pussycat! Kill! Kill! is, beyond a doubt, the best movie ever made. It is possibly better than any film that will be made in the future.” – John Waters

A gang of murder-cycle maniacs led by a sadistic Vietnam Vet are out for kicks and their voracious appetite for sex & violence will never be quenched! MOTORPSYCHO! But when the local sheriff proves ineffectual to stop them, a veterinarian (Alex Rocco) teams with a widow (Haji) to take the law into their own hands in a roaring rampage of revenge. Bursting with white-hot energy, Russ Meyer’s immediate precursor to his masterpiece Faster Pussycat! shows the exploitation icon shifting into entertainment overdrive in the trial run for his greatest picture.<br/>
Cast: Director: Russ Meyer | Starring: Tura Satana, Haji, Lori Williams, Susan Bernard,  Stuart Lancaster, Paul Trinka, Dennis Busch, Ray Barlow, Mickey Foxx | Year: 1965 | Country: USA | Format: 35mm | Director: Russ Meyer | Writer: Screenplay by W.E. Sprague and Russ Meyer from an original story by Russ Meyer and James Griffith and Hal Hopper | Starring: Stephen Oliver, Haji, Alex Rocco, Holle K. Winters, Joesph Cellini | Year: 1965 | Country: USA | Format: 35mm<br/>
Durata: 74 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://thenewbev.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/06/Faster-Pussycat-featured.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Fri March 06 - 6:30 pm / 8:25 pm]]></description><guid>https://thenewbev.com/program/march-6-faster-pussycat-kill-kill-motorpsycho</guid></item><item><title>Misbehavin’ (Adults Only)</title><link>https://thenewbev.com/program/march-7-misbehavin-midnight-show</link><description><![CDATA[Rita has a habit of marrying wealthy men, only to divorce them when someone with a bigger bank account comes along. With Rita ready for another round of nuptials, God and the devil have decided to make a wager on whether she’ll wed again for money or love. One of director Chuck Vincent’s first blockbusters, and one of hardcore cinema’s greatest tributes to Hollywood’s golden age of screwball comedies, Misbehavin’ offers a laugh a second paired with blistering sensuality from its acclaimed cast.<br/>
Cast: Director: Chuck Vincent | Starring: Gloria Leonard, Kurt Mann, Dick Galligan, Arcadia, Mark Valentine, Molly Malone, Sonny Landham, Jack Wrangler | Year: 1978 | Country: USA | Format: 35mm<br/>
Durata: 84 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://thenewbev.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/02/Misbehavin-featured.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sat March 07 - 11:59 pm]]></description><guid>https://thenewbev.com/program/march-7-misbehavin-midnight-show</guid></item><item><title>Fellini’s Casanova</title><link>https://thenewbev.com/program/march-20-fellinis-casanova</link><description><![CDATA[An extraordinary production four years in the making! The incomparable Federico Fellino directs the visually stunning portrait of Casanova, the infamous Italian womanizer, adventurer, author and libertine. In a remarkable performance, Donald Sutherland portrays the great seducer not as an amorous anomaly, but an everday man living in extraordinary times. Featuring dazzling European settings (although it was filmed entirely in Rome), an unforgettable musical score and Academy Award-winning costumes, Fellini’s Casanova is a cinematic experience to fall in love with. (Universal)<br/>
Cast: Director: Federico Fellini | Writer: Story and Screenplay by Federico Fellini and Bernardino Zapponi | Starring: Donald Sutherland, Tina Aumont, Cicely Browne, Carmen Scarpitta, Clara Algranti, Daniela Gatti | Year: 1976 | Country: Italy | Format: 35mm<br/>
Durata: 155 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://thenewbev.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/02/Casanova-featured.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Fri March 20 - 7:00 pm]]></description><guid>https://thenewbev.com/program/march-20-fellinis-casanova</guid></item><item><title>Amuck!       / Slaughter Hotel</title><link>https://thenewbev.com/program/march-27-amuck-slaughter-hotel</link><description><![CDATA[He kidnapped beautiful women, forcing them to do what he wanted… AND HE WANTED EVERYTHING! A secretary hunts for her missing friend but uncovers more than she bargained for in Amuck! , a stylish & sex-crazed Italian giallo from writer-director Silvio Amadio. International beauties Barbara Bouchet & Rosalba Neri star.

Cult icons Klaus Kinski, Margaret Lee, and Rosalba Neri in a sex-filled thriller from director Fernando Di Leo!

Fernando Di Leo, best known for a series of crime films, tried his hand at horror with this extremely sick little item loaded with nudity and violence. Set at a remote mental institution (inexplicably located in a castle), the film features Klaus Kinski as a doctor whose mostly female patients are being brutally dispatched by a psychopath. Margaret Lee and Rosalba Neri are among the frequently unclothed cast. (Kino Lorber)<br/>
Cast: Director: Silvio Amadio | Starring: Farley Granger, Barbara Bouchet, Rosalba Neri, Nino Segurini | Year: 1972 | Director: Fernando Di Leo | Writer: Screenplay & Story by Fernando Di Leo & Nino Latino | Starring: Klaus Kinski, Margaret Lee, Rosalba Neri, Jane Garret | Year: 1971 | Country: Italy | Format: 35mm<br/>
Durata: 91 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://thenewbev.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/02/Amuck-featured.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Fri March 27 - 6:30 pm / 8:25 pm]]></description><guid>https://thenewbev.com/program/march-27-amuck-slaughter-hotel</guid></item><item><title>Alice in Wonderland (1976)       / Cinderella (1977)</title><link>https://thenewbev.com/program/march-2-alice-in-wonderland-cinderella</link><description><![CDATA[The world’s favorite bedtime story is finally a bedtime story.. just NOT FOR KIDS! This sexy adult musical version of Lewis Carroll’s classic kids story Alice’s Adventures in Wonderland stars Playboy cover girl Kristine DeBelle as Alice. Alice is a naïve virgin who has never felt true desire. Stepping through an enchanted looking glass, she finds herself in Wonderland, the magical land of pleasure. Alice embarks on an erotic adventure where she meets the sex crazed Mad Hatter, the hot-blooded Wicked Queen, the “inseparable” Tweedledum and Tweedledee, and a host of carnal characters just waiting to take her innocence away. The musical kingdom of Wonderland is where all of Alice’s erotic fantasies finally come true! (Synapse Films)

Straight out of the swingin’ ’70s comes Cinderella , an early Charles Band classic that combines salacious sex, silly humor, ribald romance and best of all, utterly insane musical numbers! Perpetually abused by her incestuous stepsisters and wicked stepmother, poor Cinderella finally cuts loose when she gets the chance to attend the Prince’s gala orgiastic ball. After the sexually frustrated Prince beds every young woman at the party, he’s about to give up on love until he couples up with our enchanted heroine. But when the clock strikes midnight, Cinderella flees, leaving the smitten sovereign feeling blue. Will the prince find true happiness between the legs of his lady love and live lustfully ever after? Directed by Michael Pataki ( Mansion of the Doomed ) and starring cult actress Cheryl Lynn “Rainbeaux” Smith ( Lemora , Caged Heat , Parasite ), Sy Richardson ( They Live , Colors ) and British glam rocker Brett Smiley, Cinderella is a cheeky, hilarious and unapologetically horny song and dance-filled farce. (Full Moon Features)<br/>
Cast: Director: Bud Townsend | Writer: B.A. Fredricks | Starring: Kristine De Bell, Larry Gelman, Allan Novak, Terry Hall, Jason Williams | Year: 1976 | Country: USA | Format: 35mm | Director: Michael Pataki | Writer: Frank Ray Perilli | Starring: Cheryl "Rainbeaux" Smith, Yana Nirvana, Marilyn Corwin, Jennifer Stace, Brett Smiley, Sy Richardson | Year: 1977 | Country: USA | Format: 35mm<br/>
Durata: 94 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://thenewbev.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/02/Alice-in-Wonderland-featured.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Mon March 02 - 7:30 pm / 9:10 pm]]></description><guid>https://thenewbev.com/program/march-2-alice-in-wonderland-cinderella</guid></item><item><title>Forbidden Letters (Adults Only) + Second Feature</title><link>https://thenewbev.com/program/march-15-forbidden-letters</link><description><![CDATA[Shot in the midst of the gay community’s fight against Anita Bryant’s “Save Our Children” campaign, this critically acclaimed feature from Arthur J. Bressan, Jr. ( Gay USA , Buddies ) is a touching look at memory, fantasy, and the psychological tolls of the closet. Larry, a young gay man, is trying to pass the time on the day his older lover Richard is set to be released from prison. Unable to clear his head through casual sex, he reads through his letters to Richard – letters he knew he could never send out of fear that an outing would lead to a harsher sentence. As Richard’s release draws nearer, will the spark still be there when he gets out? (American Genre Film Archive)<br/>
Cast: Director: Arthur J. Bressan, Jr | Writer: Arthur J. Bressan, Jr | Starring: Richard Locke, Robert Adams, Victoria Young | Year: 1979 | Country: USA | Format: 16mm<br/>
Durata: 70 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://thenewbev.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/02/Forbidden-Letters-featured.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sun March 15 - 6:30 pm]]></description><guid>https://thenewbev.com/program/march-15-forbidden-letters</guid></item><item><title>Showgirls</title><link>https://thenewbev.com/program/march-10-showgirls</link><description><![CDATA[Leave your inhibitions at the door, the show is about to begin. Director Paul Verhoeven and screenwriter Joe Eszterhas go beyond your wildest dreams and beyond your wildest fantasies in their outrageously titillating, NC-17 rated tale of sex, seduction, betrayal, and backstage melodrama that follows a young drifter reaching, pulling, and clawing her way toward the dream of becoming a top Las Vegas showgirl. Elizabeth Berkley, Gina Gershon, and Kyle MacLachlan star.<br/>
Cast: Director: Paul Verhoeven | Writer: Joe Eszterhas | Starring: Elizabeth Berkley, Kyle MacLachlan, Gina Gershon, Glenn Plummer, Robert Davi, Rena Riffel | Year: 1995 | Country: USA/France | Format: 35mm<br/>
Durata: 131 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://thenewbev.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Showgirls-featured.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Tue March 10 - 7:30 pm]]></description><guid>https://thenewbev.com/program/march-10-showgirls</guid></item><item><title>The Depraved       / Campus Swingers</title><link>https://thenewbev.com/program/march-23-the-depraved-campus-swingers</link><description><![CDATA[Lena (Christina Lindberg) is a young teen in need of excitement and sexual satisfaction. Torn between her meek and innocent boyfriend Jan and the sadistic party-goer Helge, Lena’s life turns upside-down when Helge takes some nude photographs of her. These photos can destroy her life and Lena must do anything to get them, even if that means having a sadomasochistic encounter with Helge to make him happy. Can she get the photos and hide all this from her family and friends, or will her exploits leave her exposed? (Synapse Films)

The fourth film in the long-running German Schoolgirl Report series is, perhaps, its most famous entry, likely due to the inclusion of Swedish sexpot Christina Lindberg. A faux documentary about the sordid lives of teenagers presented across a number of sordid sequences, Campus Swings is a prime slice of taboo-pushing Euro sexploitation.<br/>
Cast: Director: Gustav Wiklund | Starring: Christina Lindberg, Heinz Hopf | Year: 1971 | Country: Sweden | Format: 35mm | Director: Ernst Hofbauer | Starring: Christina Lindberg, Ingrid Steeger | Year: 1972 | Country: West Germany | Format: 35mm<br/>
Durata: 88 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://thenewbev.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/02/Depraved-featured.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Mon March 23 - 7:30 pm / 9:15 pm]]></description><guid>https://thenewbev.com/program/march-23-the-depraved-campus-swingers</guid></item><item><title>Alice in Wonderland (1976)       / Cinderella (1977)</title><link>https://thenewbev.com/program/march-3-alice-in-wonderland-cinderella</link><description><![CDATA[The world’s favorite bedtime story is finally a bedtime story.. just NOT FOR KIDS! This sexy adult musical version of Lewis Carroll’s classic kids story Alice’s Adventures in Wonderland stars Playboy cover girl Kristine DeBelle as Alice. Alice is a naïve virgin who has never felt true desire. Stepping through an enchanted looking glass, she finds herself in Wonderland, the magical land of pleasure. Alice embarks on an erotic adventure where she meets the sex crazed Mad Hatter, the hot-blooded Wicked Queen, the “inseparable” Tweedledum and Tweedledee, and a host of carnal characters just waiting to take her innocence away. The musical kingdom of Wonderland is where all of Alice’s erotic fantasies finally come true! (Synapse Films)

Straight out of the swingin’ ’70s comes Cinderella , an early Charles Band classic that combines salacious sex, silly humor, ribald romance and best of all, utterly insane musical numbers! Perpetually abused by her incestuous stepsisters and wicked stepmother, poor Cinderella finally cuts loose when she gets the chance to attend the Prince’s gala orgiastic ball. After the sexually frustrated Prince beds every young woman at the party, he’s about to give up on love until he couples up with our enchanted heroine. But when the clock strikes midnight, Cinderella flees, leaving the smitten sovereign feeling blue. Will the prince find true happiness between the legs of his lady love and live lustfully ever after? Directed by Michael Pataki ( Mansion of the Doomed ) and starring cult actress Cheryl Lynn “Rainbeaux” Smith ( Lemora , Caged Heat , Parasite ), Sy Richardson ( They Live , Colors ) and British glam rocker Brett Smiley, Cinderella is a cheeky, hilarious and unapologetically horny song and dance-filled farce. (Full Moon Features)<br/>
Cast: Director: Bud Townsend | Writer: B.A. Fredricks | Starring: Kristine De Bell, Larry Gelman, Allan Novak, Terry Hall, Jason Williams | Year: 1976 | Country: USA | Format: 35mm | Director: Michael Pataki | Writer: Frank Ray Perilli | Starring: Cheryl "Rainbeaux" Smith, Yana Nirvana, Marilyn Corwin, Jennifer Stace, Brett Smiley, Sy Richardson | Year: 1977 | Country: USA | Format: 35mm<br/>
Durata: 94 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://thenewbev.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/02/Alice-in-Wonderland-featured.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Tue March 03 - 7:30 pm / 9:10 pm]]></description><guid>https://thenewbev.com/program/march-3-alice-in-wonderland-cinderella</guid></item><item><title>Fellini’s Casanova</title><link>https://thenewbev.com/program/march-19-fellinis-casanova</link><description><![CDATA[An extraordinary production four years in the making! The incomparable Federico Fellino directs the visually stunning portrait of Casanova, the infamous Italian womanizer, adventurer, author and libertine. In a remarkable performance, Donald Sutherland portrays the great seducer not as an amorous anomaly, but an everday man living in extraordinary times. Featuring dazzling European settings (although it was filmed entirely in Rome), an unforgettable musical score and Academy Award-winning costumes, Fellini’s Casanova is a cinematic experience to fall in love with. (Universal)<br/>
Cast: Director: Federico Fellini | Writer: Story and Screenplay by Federico Fellini and Bernardino Zapponi | Starring: Donald Sutherland, Tina Aumont, Cicely Browne, Carmen Scarpitta, Clara Algranti, Daniela Gatti | Year: 1976 | Country: Italy | Format: 35mm<br/>
Durata: 155 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://thenewbev.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/02/Casanova-featured.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Thu March 19 - 7:30 pm]]></description><guid>https://thenewbev.com/program/march-19-fellinis-casanova</guid></item><item><title>The Hot Box       / Terminal Island</title><link>https://thenewbev.com/program/march-29-the-hot-box-terminal-island</link><description><![CDATA[Award-winning filmmaker Jonathan Demme ( The Silence of the Lambs ) produces and co-writes The Hot Box , an action-thriller straight from the grimiest corner of the grindhouse. Four nurses working in the tropical Republic of San Rosario enter a hellish nightmare when they are kidnapped and delivered to a rebel army fighting a guerilla war against oppressive government forces. Tormented by every man that crosses their path, the four women must band together in the dense jungle in pursuit of a solitary goal: survival. (Shout! Factory)

A cult movie slayer from acclaimed filmmaker Stephanie Rothman ( The Velvet Vampire ), Terminal Island blends violent action with commentary on the American justice system. Carmen Simms has just been sentenced to life imprisonment on Terminal Island – an island created to house vicious criminals in the wake of prison overcrowding. With no guards, no cells, and no laws, Terminal Island has morphed into a defacto society with the tyrannical Bobby ruling over all. As tension and violence mount, Carmen finds her place as the unlikely leader of the island’s underground resistance, which is planning to overthrow Bobby’s reign of terror. Starring Phyllis Davis ( Sweet Sugar ) and Emmy winner Tom Selleck (Magnum P.I.) in one of his earliest roles. (American Genre Film Archive)<br/>
Cast: Director: Joe Viola | Writer: Joe Viola and Jonathan Demme | Starring: Andrea Cagan, Margaret Markov, Rickey Richardson, Laurie Rose, Carmen Argenziano, Charles Dierkop | Year: 1972 | Country: Philippines/USA | Format: 35mm | Director: Stephanie Rothman | Writer: Written by Jim Barnett and Charles S. Swartz & Stephanie Rothman | Starring: Phyllis Davis, Don Marshall, Ena Hartman, Marta Kristen, Barbara Leigh, Tom Selleck, Roger E. Mosley | Year: 1973 | Country: USA | Format: 35mm<br/>
Durata: 88 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://thenewbev.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/02/Hot-Box-featured.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sun March 29 - 6:30 pm / 8:30 pm]]></description><guid>https://thenewbev.com/program/march-29-the-hot-box-terminal-island</guid></item><item><title>How Funny Can Sex Be?       / Sex With A Smile</title><link>https://thenewbev.com/program/march-9-how-funny-can-sex-be-sex-with-a-smile</link><description><![CDATA[Italian director Dino Rosi and stars Giancarlo Giannini and Laura Antonelli humorously explore love, sex and marriage in the ‘70s in this erotic anthology. Across nine quick segments, Giannini shows his chameleonic range in a lasciviously fun sex romp.

After you’ve tried everything else… try Sex with a Smile . Sergio Martino helms a ribald sex comedy anthology featuring a bevvy of beauties, including Barbara Bouchet and Edwige Fenech. Plus, Marty Feldman! Across five shorts segments, there’s an indecent proposal, an over-attentive bodyguard, a sexy tryst with surprising secrets, a jealous dog, and more!<br/>
Cast: Director: Dino Risi | Writer: Screenplay by Ruggero Maccari, Story by Dino Risi and Ruggero Maccari | Starring: Giancarlo Giannini, Laura Antonelli, Alberto Lionello, Duilio Del Prete, Paola Borboni, Carla Mancini | Year: 1973 | Country: Italy | Format: 35mm | Director: Sergio Martino | Writer: Screenplay by Tonino Guerra and Giorgio Salvioni and Sergio Martino | Starring: Marty Feldman, Dayle Haddon, Sydne Rome, Barbara Bouchet, Edwige Fenech | Year: 1976 | Country: Italy | Format: 35mm<br/>
Durata: 100 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://thenewbev.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/02/How-Funny-featured.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Mon March 09 - 7:30 pm / 9:35 pm]]></description><guid>https://thenewbev.com/program/march-9-how-funny-can-sex-be-sex-with-a-smile</guid></item><item><title>The Lickerish Quartet       / Therese and Isabelle</title><link>https://thenewbev.com/program/march-21-the-lickerish-quartet-therese-and-isabelle</link><description><![CDATA[An aristocratic married couple and their adult son decide to end their boring night watching stag films by visiting a traveling carnival. When the trio realize that one of the stars of the stunt show bears a striking resemblance to one of the performers in the film they’ve just watched, they invite her back to their castle for a night of mind-bending fun and games that’ll see each of the members of the family fulfill their deepest fantasies.  Dubbed “an outrageously kinky masterpiece” by Andy Warhol, Radley Metzger’s The Lickerish Quartet is a deliriously psychedelic – yet classily elegant! – classic of softcore erotica. (Muscle Distribution)

One of erotic arthouse auteur Radley Metzger’s best loved but rarely screened films follows a pair of young students at a prestigious Swiss boarding school for girls, whose affectionate friendship flowers into something more.  Stunningly shot in black and white Panavision by director of photography Hans Jura and featuring a lush score by Georges Auric.

Print courtesy of the Nicolas Winding Refn Collection<br/>
Cast: Director: Radley Metzger | Starring: Silvana Venturelli, Frank Wolff, Erika Remberg, Paolo Turco | Year: 1970 | Country: Italy/West Germany/USA | Format: 35mm | Director: Radley Metzger | Writer: Screenplay by Jesse Vogel based on the novel by Violette Leduc | Starring: Essy Persson, Anna Gaël, Barbara Laage, Anne Vernon | Year: 1968 | Country: France/Netherlands/USA/West Germany | Format: 35mm<br/>
Durata: 118 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://thenewbev.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/02/Lickerish-Quartet-featured.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sat March 21 - 6:00 pm / 8:00 pm]]></description><guid>https://thenewbev.com/program/march-21-the-lickerish-quartet-therese-and-isabelle</guid></item><item><title>The Hot Box       / Terminal Island</title><link>https://thenewbev.com/program/march-28-the-hot-box-terminal-island</link><description><![CDATA[Award-winning filmmaker Jonathan Demme ( The Silence of the Lambs ) produces and co-writes The Hot Box , an action-thriller straight from the grimiest corner of the grindhouse. Four nurses working in the tropical Republic of San Rosario enter a hellish nightmare when they are kidnapped and delivered to a rebel army fighting a guerilla war against oppressive government forces. Tormented by every man that crosses their path, the four women must band together in the dense jungle in pursuit of a solitary goal: survival. (Shout! Factory)

A cult movie slayer from acclaimed filmmaker Stephanie Rothman ( The Velvet Vampire ), Terminal Island blends violent action with commentary on the American justice system. Carmen Simms has just been sentenced to life imprisonment on Terminal Island – an island created to house vicious criminals in the wake of prison overcrowding. With no guards, no cells, and no laws, Terminal Island has morphed into a defacto society with the tyrannical Bobby ruling over all. As tension and violence mount, Carmen finds her place as the unlikely leader of the island’s underground resistance, which is planning to overthrow Bobby’s reign of terror. Starring Phyllis Davis ( Sweet Sugar ) and Emmy winner Tom Selleck (Magnum P.I.) in one of his earliest roles. (American Genre Film Archive)<br/>
Cast: Director: Joe Viola | Writer: Joe Viola and Jonathan Demme | Starring: Andrea Cagan, Margaret Markov, Rickey Richardson, Laurie Rose, Carmen Argenziano, Charles Dierkop | Year: 1972 | Country: Philippines/USA | Format: 35mm | Director: Stephanie Rothman | Writer: Written by Jim Barnett and Charles S. Swartz & Stephanie Rothman | Starring: Phyllis Davis, Don Marshall, Ena Hartman, Marta Kristen, Barbara Leigh, Tom Selleck, Roger E. Mosley | Year: 1973 | Country: USA | Format: 35mm<br/>
Durata: 88 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://thenewbev.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/02/Hot-Box-featured.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sat March 28 - 6:30 pm / 8:30 pm]]></description><guid>https://thenewbev.com/program/march-28-the-hot-box-terminal-island</guid></item><item><title>Venus in Furs       / Succubus</title><link>https://thenewbev.com/program/march-16-venus-in-furs-succubus</link><description><![CDATA[Of all the twisted hits from cult director Jess Franco, this is the one that fans and critics alike call his masterpiece! James Darren stars as a traumatized trumpeter sucked into a world of psycho-sexual horror along with his sultry girlfriend (singer Barbara McNair), a kinky lesbian (Margaret Lee of The Bloody Judge ) and the mysterious, insatiable beauty (luscious Maria Rohm of Justine ) who may lead them all straight to hell. Dennis Price ( Vampyros Lesbos ) co-stars in this infamous erotic shocker that also features an outstanding jazz score by British rockers Manfred Mann. (Blue Underground)

At a chic nightclub for jaded jetsetters, a simulated snuff performance is the main attraction, and Lorna, its leading lady, is the obsession of men and women alike. Little do they realize that Lorna’s Mephistophelian manager has transformed her into “the essence of evil… a devil on earth!” Soon, the sensuous starlet’s stage persona possesses her entirely, thrusting Lorna into a hallucinatory world of sadomasochistic excess and drawing everyone she touches into her debaucherous delirium. Can anyone stop Lorna before her perverse stage show becomes a murderous reality? Starring the beautiful Janine Reynaud, Jack Taylor and Howard Vernon, Jess Franco’s Faustian fever dream provides the blue-print for the erotic horror that has become the infamous director’s enduring legacy. (Blue Underground)<br/>
Cast: Director: Jess Franco | Writer: Screenplay by Jess Franco and Malvin Wald | Starring: James Darren, Barbara McNair, Maria Rohm, Klaus Kinski, Dennis Price, Margaret Lee, Aldo Lastretti | Year: 1969 | Country: UK/Italy/West Germany | Format: 35mm | Director: Jess Franco | Writer: Screenplay by Pier A. Caminnecci | Starring: Janine Reynaud, Jack Taylor, Adrian Hoven, Howard Vernon | Year: 1968 | Country: West Germany | Format: 35mm<br/>
Durata: 80 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://thenewbev.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Venus-in-Furs-featured.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Mon March 16 - 7:30 pm / 9:25 pm]]></description><guid>https://thenewbev.com/program/march-16-venus-in-furs-succubus</guid></item><item><title>Showgirls</title><link>https://thenewbev.com/program/march-12-showgirls</link><description><![CDATA[Leave your inhibitions at the door, the show is about to begin. Director Paul Verhoeven and screenwriter Joe Eszterhas go beyond your wildest dreams and beyond your wildest fantasies in their outrageously titillating, NC-17 rated tale of sex, seduction, betrayal, and backstage melodrama that follows a young drifter reaching, pulling, and clawing her way toward the dream of becoming a top Las Vegas showgirl. Elizabeth Berkley, Gina Gershon, and Kyle MacLachlan star.<br/>
Cast: Director: Paul Verhoeven | Writer: Joe Eszterhas | Starring: Elizabeth Berkley, Kyle MacLachlan, Gina Gershon, Glenn Plummer, Robert Davi, Rena Riffel | Year: 1995 | Country: USA/France | Format: 35mm<br/>
Durata: 131 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://thenewbev.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Showgirls-featured.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Thu March 12 - 7:30 pm]]></description><guid>https://thenewbev.com/program/march-12-showgirls</guid></item><item><title>Expose Me, Lovely (Adults Only)</title><link>https://thenewbev.com/program/march-14-expose-me-lovely-midnight-show</link><description><![CDATA[It takes a hard cop to solve a hard case! New York City private dick Frosty Knight is on the hunt for the missing heir to a political candidate. But as he probes deeper into his investigation, he’ll soon find himself enmeshed in a larger mystery. Writer-director Armand Weston helms a hardcore & hardboiled pornographic neo-noir inspired by Robert Montgomery’s Lady in the Lake .<br/>
Cast: Director: Armand Weston | Writer: Armand Weston | Starring: Jennifer Welles, Jody Maxwell, Cary Lacy, Ras Kean, Eve Iminu | Year: 1976 | Country: USA | Format: 35mm<br/>
Durata: 90 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://thenewbev.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/02/Expose-Me-Lovely-featured.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sat March 14 - 11:59 pm]]></description><guid>https://thenewbev.com/program/march-14-expose-me-lovely-midnight-show</guid></item><item><title>Lolita (1997)</title><link>https://thenewbev.com/program/march-5-lolita</link><description><![CDATA[Director Adrian Lyne ( Fatal Attraction ) took everyone by surprise with this faithful adaptation of Vladimir Nabokov’s controversial literary classic Lolita . Lyne takes a decidedly more serious approach than Kubrick’s version but still retains some of the subtle satiric humor. Visiting professor Humbert Humbert (Jeremy Irons) becomes instantly infatuated, in love with the underage daughter (Dominique Swain) of his new landlady (Melanie Griffith), a lonely, brassy woman whom Humbert will eventually wed to be close to his girlish idyll. The film features a beautiful, haunting score by Ennio Morricone. After post-production was complete, Lolita ran into unexpected hurdles due to its taboo subject matter, with virtually every major distributor turning it down before it premiered on the Showtime network, then subsequently enjoyed limited theatrical runs in Los Angeles and New York.

“The film’s master stroke is its understanding that this is Humbert’s story, told in his own lyrical voice… Jeremy Irons creates one of the great, fearless screen performances… He is calculating, romantic, eventually soul-sick with his own love… Melanie Griffith is ideally cast as the annoying, widowed Charlotte. Dominique Swain is extraordinary as Lolita…Rich beyond what anyone could have expected, the film repays repeated viewings.” – Caryn James, The New York Times<br/>
Cast: Director: Adrian Lyne | Writer: Screenplay by Stephen Schiff based on the novel by Vladimir Nabokov | Starring: Jeremy Irons, Melanie Griffith, Frank Langella, Dominique Swain | Year: 1997 | Country: USA/France | Format: 35mm<br/>
Durata: 138 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://thenewbev.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/01/Lolita-1997-featured.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Thu March 05 - 7:30 pm]]></description><guid>https://thenewbev.com/program/march-5-lolita</guid></item><item><title>The Decameron</title><link>https://thenewbev.com/program/march-13-the-decameron</link><description><![CDATA[Legendary Italian director Pier Paolo Pasolini delivers nine exuberant tales in this “earthy, genuinely ribald and spicy” (Variety) film. Based on Boccaccio’s timeless classic – and the first in Pasolini’s Trilogy of Life series – The Decameron is an uproariously “irreverent romp” (Films and Filming)! Lusty nuns who perform sexual “miracles,” a cheating wife with a head for business, a dying con artist attempting a heavenly swindle, young lovers caught with their pants down, a servant who loses his head for love and a gullible farmer who tries to turn his wife into a mare. These are just some of the stories Pasolini vividly brings to life! (MGM)<br/>
Cast: Director: Pier Paolo Pasolini | Writer: Written by Pier Paolo Pasolini based on 'The Decameron' by Boccaccio | Starring: Franco Citti, Ninetto Davoli, M. Gabriella Frankel, Gerhard Exel, Wolfgang Hillinger, Vincenzo Amato, Jovan Jovanovic, Giuseppe Zigaina | Year: 1971 | Country: Italy/France/West Germany | Format: English subtitled 35mm<br/>
Durata: 111 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://thenewbev.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/02/Decameron-featured.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Fri March 13 - 7:30 pm]]></description><guid>https://thenewbev.com/program/march-13-the-decameron</guid></item><item><title>Lolita (1997)</title><link>https://thenewbev.com/program/march-4-lolita</link><description><![CDATA[Director Adrian Lyne ( Fatal Attraction ) took everyone by surprise with this faithful adaptation of Vladimir Nabokov’s controversial literary classic Lolita . Lyne takes a decidedly more serious approach than Kubrick’s version but still retains some of the subtle satiric humor. Visiting professor Humbert Humbert (Jeremy Irons) becomes instantly infatuated, in love with the underage daughter (Dominique Swain) of his new landlady (Melanie Griffith), a lonely, brassy woman whom Humbert will eventually wed to be close to his girlish idyll. The film features a beautiful, haunting score by Ennio Morricone. After post-production was complete, Lolita ran into unexpected hurdles due to its taboo subject matter, with virtually every major distributor turning it down before it premiered on the Showtime network, then subsequently enjoyed limited theatrical runs in Los Angeles and New York.

“The film’s master stroke is its understanding that this is Humbert’s story, told in his own lyrical voice… Jeremy Irons creates one of the great, fearless screen performances… He is calculating, romantic, eventually soul-sick with his own love… Melanie Griffith is ideally cast as the annoying, widowed Charlotte. Dominique Swain is extraordinary as Lolita…Rich beyond what anyone could have expected, the film repays repeated viewings.” – Caryn James, The New York Times<br/>
Cast: Director: Adrian Lyne | Writer: Screenplay by Stephen Schiff based on the novel by Vladimir Nabokov | Starring: Jeremy Irons, Melanie Griffith, Frank Langella, Dominique Swain | Year: 1997 | Country: USA/France | Format: 35mm<br/>
Durata: 138 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://thenewbev.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/01/Lolita-1997-featured.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Wed March 04 - 7:30 pm]]></description><guid>https://thenewbev.com/program/march-4-lolita</guid></item><item><title>Last Tango in Paris</title><link>https://thenewbev.com/program/march-31-last-tango-in-paris</link><description><![CDATA[Paul, a middle-aged American living in emotional exile, comes to Paris when his estranged wife commits suicide. Chancing to meet young Frenchwoman named Jeanne, Paul enters into a sadomasochistic, carnal relationship with her, indirectly attacking the hypocrisy all around him and his own feelings of guilt through his raw, outrageous sexual behaviour. (Park Circus)<br/>
Cast: Director: Bernardo Bertolucci | Starring: Marlon Brando, Maria Schneider, Maria Michi, Giovanna Galletti, Jean-Pierre Léaud, Massimo Girotti | Year: 1972 | Country: Italy/France | Format: 35mm<br/>
Durata: 129 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://thenewbev.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/02/Last-Tango-featured.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Tue March 31 - 7:30 pm]]></description><guid>https://thenewbev.com/program/march-31-last-tango-in-paris</guid></item><item><title>Henry &amp; June</title><link>https://thenewbev.com/program/march-24-henry-june</link><description><![CDATA[A searing erotic drama – the first film rated NC-17 by the MPAA – from The Unbearable Lightness of Being director Philip Kaufman.

Philip Kaufman’s brilliant film explores the erotic life of two individuals who became 20th Century literary giants. Upon meeting American author Henry Miller (Fred Ward) in Paris, 1931, a young writer named Anaïs Nin (Maria de Medeiros) embarks on a voyage of self-discovery, and faithfully records every experience in her diary. In their search for new truths, Anais and Henry are tantalized by Henry’s hauntingly sensual wife, June (Uma Thurman). Henry & June is an unforgettable journey into the uncharted territory of human relationships, based on the suppressed sections of Anaïs Nin’s diaries. (Universal)<br/>
Cast: Director: Philip Kaufman | Writer: screenplay by Philip Kaufman & Rose Kaufman based on the book by Anaïs Nin | Starring: Fred Ward, Uma Thurman, Maria de Medeiros, Richard E. Grant, Kevin Spacey | Year: 1990 | Country: USA/France | Format: 35mm<br/>
Durata: 136 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://thenewbev.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/12/Henry-June-featured.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Tue March 24 - 7:30 pm]]></description><guid>https://thenewbev.com/program/march-24-henry-june</guid></item><item><title>A Woman in Flames       / Belle de Jour</title><link>https://thenewbev.com/program/march-17-a-woman-in-flames-belle-de-jour</link><description><![CDATA[A housewife yearning for more abandons her arrogant husband and their upper-class life. While exploring her newfound sexual freedom, she soon discovers that sex can be a very profitable commodity. And as her new life as a dominatrix intensifies, she forms a complicated romantic relationship with a gigolo.

Catherine Deneuve’s porcelain perfection hides a cracked interior in one of the actress’s most iconic roles: Séverine, a Paris housewife who begins secretly spending her after­noon hours working in a bordello. This surreal and erotic late-sixties daydream from provocateur for the ages Luis Buñuel is an examination of desire and fetishistic pleasure (its characters’ and its viewers’), as well as a gently absurdist take on contemporary social mores and class divisions. Fantasy and reality commingle in this burst of cinematic transgression, which was one of Buñuel’s biggest hits. (Janus Films)<br/>
Cast: Director: Robert van Ackeren | Writer: Screenplay by Robert van Ackeren and Catharina Zwerenz | Starring: Gudrun Landgrebe, Mathieu Carriere, Hanns Zischler | Year: 1983 | Country: West Germany | Format: 16mm | Director: Luis Buñuel | Starring: Catherine Deneuve, Jean Sorel, Michel Piccoli | Year: 1967 | Country: France | Format: English subtitled 35mm<br/>
Durata: 100 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://thenewbev.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/02/Woman-in-Flames-featured.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Tue March 17 - 7:30 pm / 9:45 pm]]></description><guid>https://thenewbev.com/program/march-17-a-woman-in-flames-belle-de-jour</guid></item><item><title>True Romance</title><link>https://thenewbev.com/program/march-6-true-romance-midnight-show</link><description><![CDATA[A rock ‘n roll adventure following two unlikely lovers who accidentally double cross the mob and hit the road towards Los Angeles. Featuring an all-star cast, slick direction from Tony Scott and an endlessly-quotable script by Quentin Tarantino, True Romance will have you saying “you’re so cool” all month long.

“This is the kind of movie that creates its own universe, and glories in it. Made with such energy, such high spirits, such an enchanting goofiness, that it’s impossible to resist.” – Roger Ebert

“It’s Tarantino’s gutter poetry that detonates True Romance . This movie is dynamite.” – Peter Travers, Rolling Stone<br/>
Cast: Director: Tony Scott | Writer: Quentin Tarantino | Starring: Christian Slater, Patricia Arquette, Dennis Hopper, Val Kilmer, Gary Oldman, Brad Pitt, Christopher Walken, Bronson Pinchot, Samuel L. Jackson, Michael Rapaport, Saul Rubinek, Conchata Ferrell and James Gandolfini | Year: 1993 | Country: USA/France | Format: 35mm<br/>
Durata: 119 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://thenewbev.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/True-Romance-featured.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Fri March 06 - 11:59 pm]]></description><guid>https://thenewbev.com/program/march-6-true-romance-midnight-show</guid></item><item><title>Faster, Pussycat! Kill! Kill!       / Motorpsycho</title><link>https://thenewbev.com/program/march-7-faster-pussycat-kill-kill-motorpsycho</link><description><![CDATA[Ladies and gentlemen – welcome to violence! Celebrate the greatest girl-power grindhouse explosion to ever ignite the screen as well as pay tribute to the legendary sexploitation maestro and breastman extraordinaire behind it all, the King of the Nudies himself, Russ Meyer! Go-Go for a wild ride with three buxom, larger-than-life superwomen, Tura Satana, Haji & Lori Williams, as they Watusi across the Mojave Desert destroying every man who dares stand in their way. These outlaw hellcats drive fast, kick ass and look great while pushing the boundaries of being bad. Full of pop imagery, exuberant action and kinetic excitement, Faster, Pussycat! Kill! Kill! is one of the most iconic cult films EVER! Don’t miss it!

“ Faster, Pussycat! Kill! Kill! is, beyond a doubt, the best movie ever made. It is possibly better than any film that will be made in the future.” – John Waters

A gang of murder-cycle maniacs led by a sadistic Vietnam Vet are out for kicks and their voracious appetite for sex & violence will never be quenched! MOTORPSYCHO! But when the local sheriff proves ineffectual to stop them, a veterinarian (Alex Rocco) teams with a widow (Haji) to take the law into their own hands in a roaring rampage of revenge. Bursting with white-hot energy, Russ Meyer’s immediate precursor to his masterpiece Faster Pussycat! shows the exploitation icon shifting into entertainment overdrive in the trial run for his greatest picture.<br/>
Cast: Director: Russ Meyer | Starring: Tura Satana, Haji, Lori Williams, Susan Bernard,  Stuart Lancaster, Paul Trinka, Dennis Busch, Ray Barlow, Mickey Foxx | Year: 1965 | Country: USA | Format: 35mm | Director: Russ Meyer | Writer: Screenplay by W.E. Sprague and Russ Meyer from an original story by Russ Meyer and James Griffith and Hal Hopper | Starring: Stephen Oliver, Haji, Alex Rocco, Holle K. Winters, Joesph Cellini | Year: 1965 | Country: USA | Format: 35mm<br/>
Durata: 74 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://thenewbev.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/06/Faster-Pussycat-featured.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sat March 07 - 6:30 pm / 8:25 pm]]></description><guid>https://thenewbev.com/program/march-7-faster-pussycat-kill-kill-motorpsycho</guid></item><item><title>Faster, Pussycat! Kill! Kill!       / Motorpsycho</title><link>https://thenewbev.com/program/march-8-faster-pussycat-kill-kill-motorpsycho</link><description><![CDATA[Ladies and gentlemen – welcome to violence! Celebrate the greatest girl-power grindhouse explosion to ever ignite the screen as well as pay tribute to the legendary sexploitation maestro and breastman extraordinaire behind it all, the King of the Nudies himself, Russ Meyer! Go-Go for a wild ride with three buxom, larger-than-life superwomen, Tura Satana, Haji & Lori Williams, as they Watusi across the Mojave Desert destroying every man who dares stand in their way. These outlaw hellcats drive fast, kick ass and look great while pushing the boundaries of being bad. Full of pop imagery, exuberant action and kinetic excitement, Faster, Pussycat! Kill! Kill! is one of the most iconic cult films EVER! Don’t miss it!

“ Faster, Pussycat! Kill! Kill! is, beyond a doubt, the best movie ever made. It is possibly better than any film that will be made in the future.” – John Waters

A gang of murder-cycle maniacs led by a sadistic Vietnam Vet are out for kicks and their voracious appetite for sex & violence will never be quenched! MOTORPSYCHO! But when the local sheriff proves ineffectual to stop them, a veterinarian (Alex Rocco) teams with a widow (Haji) to take the law into their own hands in a roaring rampage of revenge. Bursting with white-hot energy, Russ Meyer’s immediate precursor to his masterpiece Faster Pussycat! shows the exploitation icon shifting into entertainment overdrive in the trial run for his greatest picture.<br/>
Cast: Director: Russ Meyer | Starring: Tura Satana, Haji, Lori Williams, Susan Bernard,  Stuart Lancaster, Paul Trinka, Dennis Busch, Ray Barlow, Mickey Foxx | Year: 1965 | Country: USA | Format: 35mm | Director: Russ Meyer | Writer: Screenplay by W.E. Sprague and Russ Meyer from an original story by Russ Meyer and James Griffith and Hal Hopper | Starring: Stephen Oliver, Haji, Alex Rocco, Holle K. Winters, Joesph Cellini | Year: 1965 | Country: USA | Format: 35mm<br/>
Durata: 74 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://thenewbev.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/06/Faster-Pussycat-featured.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sun March 08 - 6:30 pm / 8:25 pm]]></description><guid>https://thenewbev.com/program/march-8-faster-pussycat-kill-kill-motorpsycho</guid></item><item><title>Deep Throat (Adults Only)       / Hot Summer in the City (Adults Only)</title><link>https://thenewbev.com/program/march-1-deep-throat-hot-summer-in-the-city</link><description><![CDATA[How far does a girl have to go to untangle her tingle? A sexually frustrated woman finally uncovers an unconventional solution to help her climax. One of the key films that launched porno chic, Deep Throat helped ignite a cinematic revolution, garnering major box office success and enduring controversies (behind the scenes and beyond), while fighting a multitude of obscenity battles and bans along the way.

The first XXX film lensed in Michigan! Set during the long, hot summer of 1967 and its impending real-life confrontations in Detroit, Hot Summer in the City pushes the boundaries of pornographic entertainment, injecting roughie violence and exploitation themes into its hardcore sex storyline. With genuine Top 40 hits playing in the background, a group of Black Militants kidnap a young white virgin in a plan to set off race riots throughout the suburbs. ADULTS ONLY – All attendees must be 18+ w/ ID for admission<br/>
Cast: Director: Gerard Damiano | Starring: Linda Lovelace, Harry Reems, Dolly Sharp, Carol Connors | Year: 1972 | Country: USA | Format: 35mm | Director: Gail Palmer | Starring: Lisa Baker, Duke Johnson, Shorty Roberts, Stitch Umbas, Coke Chain, Black Orchid | Year: 1976 | Country: USA | Format: 35mm<br/>
Durata: 55 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://thenewbev.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Deep-Throat-featured.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sun March 01 - 6:30 pm / 8:00 pm]]></description><guid>https://thenewbev.com/program/march-1-deep-throat-hot-summer-in-the-city</guid></item><item><title>True Romance</title><link>https://thenewbev.com/program/march-20-true-romance-midnight-show</link><description><![CDATA[A rock ‘n roll adventure following two unlikely lovers who accidentally double cross the mob and hit the road towards Los Angeles. Featuring an all-star cast, slick direction from Tony Scott and an endlessly-quotable script by Quentin Tarantino, True Romance will have you saying “you’re so cool” all month long.

“This is the kind of movie that creates its own universe, and glories in it. Made with such energy, such high spirits, such an enchanting goofiness, that it’s impossible to resist.” – Roger Ebert

“It’s Tarantino’s gutter poetry that detonates True Romance . This movie is dynamite.” – Peter Travers, Rolling Stone<br/>
Cast: Director: Tony Scott | Writer: Quentin Tarantino | Starring: Christian Slater, Patricia Arquette, Dennis Hopper, Val Kilmer, Gary Oldman, Brad Pitt, Christopher Walken, Bronson Pinchot, Samuel L. Jackson, Michael Rapaport, Saul Rubinek, Conchata Ferrell and James Gandolfini | Year: 1993 | Country: USA/France | Format: 35mm<br/>
Durata: 119 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://thenewbev.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/True-Romance-featured.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Fri March 20 - 11:59 pm]]></description><guid>https://thenewbev.com/program/march-20-true-romance-midnight-show</guid></item><item><title>Amuck!       / Slaughter Hotel</title><link>https://thenewbev.com/program/march-26-amuck-slaughter-hotel</link><description><![CDATA[He kidnapped beautiful women, forcing them to do what he wanted… AND HE WANTED EVERYTHING! A secretary hunts for her missing friend but uncovers more than she bargained for in Amuck! , a stylish & sex-crazed Italian giallo from writer-director Silvio Amadio. International beauties Barbara Bouchet & Rosalba Neri star.

Cult icons Klaus Kinski, Margaret Lee, and Rosalba Neri in a sex-filled thriller from director Fernando Di Leo!

Fernando Di Leo, best known for a series of crime films, tried his hand at horror with this extremely sick little item loaded with nudity and violence. Set at a remote mental institution (inexplicably located in a castle), the film features Klaus Kinski as a doctor whose mostly female patients are being brutally dispatched by a psychopath. Margaret Lee and Rosalba Neri are among the frequently unclothed cast. (Kino Lorber)<br/>
Cast: Director: Silvio Amadio | Starring: Farley Granger, Barbara Bouchet, Rosalba Neri, Nino Segurini | Year: 1972 | Director: Fernando Di Leo | Writer: Screenplay & Story by Fernando Di Leo & Nino Latino | Starring: Klaus Kinski, Margaret Lee, Rosalba Neri, Jane Garret | Year: 1971 | Country: Italy | Format: 35mm<br/>
Durata: 91 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://thenewbev.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/02/Amuck-featured.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Thu March 26 - 7:30 pm / 9:25 pm]]></description><guid>https://thenewbev.com/program/march-26-amuck-slaughter-hotel</guid></item><item><title>Behind the Green Door (Adults Only)</title><link>https://thenewbev.com/program/march-28-behind-the-green-door-midnight-show</link><description><![CDATA[As part of a strange club’s elaborate sexual performance, anonymous lovers emerge through a mysterious green door to fulfill a woman’s deepest longings and hidden desires. A low budget, but highly ambitious effort which would become one of the biggest X-rated hits of the 1970s, the Mitchell Brothers’ landmark Behind the Green Door made an international sensation and bonafide star out of its leading lady Marilyn Chambers, while also becoming one of the first hardcore features to win mainstream acclaim for both its technical innovation and artistic merits.<br/>
Cast: Director: Jim and Artie Mitchell | Starring: Marilyn Chambers, Johnny Keyes, George McDonald, Ben Davidson | Year: 1972 | Country: USA | Format: 35mm<br/>
Durata: 72 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://thenewbev.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/02/Behind-the-Green-Door-featured.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sat March 28 - 11:59 pm]]></description><guid>https://thenewbev.com/program/march-28-behind-the-green-door-midnight-show</guid></item><item><title>Showgirls</title><link>https://thenewbev.com/program/march-11-showgirls</link><description><![CDATA[Leave your inhibitions at the door, the show is about to begin. Director Paul Verhoeven and screenwriter Joe Eszterhas go beyond your wildest dreams and beyond your wildest fantasies in their outrageously titillating, NC-17 rated tale of sex, seduction, betrayal, and backstage melodrama that follows a young drifter reaching, pulling, and clawing her way toward the dream of becoming a top Las Vegas showgirl. Elizabeth Berkley, Gina Gershon, and Kyle MacLachlan star.<br/>
Cast: Director: Paul Verhoeven | Writer: Joe Eszterhas | Starring: Elizabeth Berkley, Kyle MacLachlan, Gina Gershon, Glenn Plummer, Robert Davi, Rena Riffel | Year: 1995 | Country: USA/France | Format: 35mm<br/>
Durata: 131 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://thenewbev.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/04/Showgirls-featured.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Wed March 11 - 7:30 pm]]></description><guid>https://thenewbev.com/program/march-11-showgirls</guid></item><item><title>True Romance</title><link>https://thenewbev.com/program/march-27-true-romance-midnight-show</link><description><![CDATA[A rock ‘n roll adventure following two unlikely lovers who accidentally double cross the mob and hit the road towards Los Angeles. Featuring an all-star cast, slick direction from Tony Scott and an endlessly-quotable script by Quentin Tarantino, True Romance will have you saying “you’re so cool” all month long.

“This is the kind of movie that creates its own universe, and glories in it. Made with such energy, such high spirits, such an enchanting goofiness, that it’s impossible to resist.” – Roger Ebert

“It’s Tarantino’s gutter poetry that detonates True Romance . This movie is dynamite.” – Peter Travers, Rolling Stone<br/>
Cast: Director: Tony Scott | Writer: Quentin Tarantino | Starring: Christian Slater, Patricia Arquette, Dennis Hopper, Val Kilmer, Gary Oldman, Brad Pitt, Christopher Walken, Bronson Pinchot, Samuel L. Jackson, Michael Rapaport, Saul Rubinek, Conchata Ferrell and James Gandolfini | Year: 1993 | Country: USA/France | Format: 35mm<br/>
Durata: 119 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://thenewbev.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/True-Romance-featured.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Fri March 27 - 11:59 pm]]></description><guid>https://thenewbev.com/program/march-27-true-romance-midnight-show</guid></item><item><title>Henry &amp; June</title><link>https://thenewbev.com/program/march-25-henry-june</link><description><![CDATA[A searing erotic drama – the first film rated NC-17 by the MPAA – from The Unbearable Lightness of Being director Philip Kaufman.

Philip Kaufman’s brilliant film explores the erotic life of two individuals who became 20th Century literary giants. Upon meeting American author Henry Miller (Fred Ward) in Paris, 1931, a young writer named Anaïs Nin (Maria de Medeiros) embarks on a voyage of self-discovery, and faithfully records every experience in her diary. In their search for new truths, Anais and Henry are tantalized by Henry’s hauntingly sensual wife, June (Uma Thurman). Henry & June is an unforgettable journey into the uncharted territory of human relationships, based on the suppressed sections of Anaïs Nin’s diaries. (Universal)<br/>
Cast: Director: Philip Kaufman | Writer: screenplay by Philip Kaufman & Rose Kaufman based on the book by Anaïs Nin | Starring: Fred Ward, Uma Thurman, Maria de Medeiros, Richard E. Grant, Kevin Spacey | Year: 1990 | Country: USA/France | Format: 35mm<br/>
Durata: 136 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://thenewbev.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/12/Henry-June-featured.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Wed March 25 - 7:30 pm]]></description><guid>https://thenewbev.com/program/march-25-henry-june</guid></item><item><title>Last Tango in Paris</title><link>https://thenewbev.com/program/march-30-last-tango-in-paris</link><description><![CDATA[Paul, a middle-aged American living in emotional exile, comes to Paris when his estranged wife commits suicide. Chancing to meet young Frenchwoman named Jeanne, Paul enters into a sadomasochistic, carnal relationship with her, indirectly attacking the hypocrisy all around him and his own feelings of guilt through his raw, outrageous sexual behaviour. (Park Circus)<br/>
Cast: Director: Bernardo Bertolucci | Starring: Marlon Brando, Maria Schneider, Maria Michi, Giovanna Galletti, Jean-Pierre Léaud, Massimo Girotti | Year: 1972 | Country: Italy/France | Format: 35mm<br/>
Durata: 129 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://thenewbev.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/02/Last-Tango-featured.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Mon March 30 - 7:30 pm]]></description><guid>https://thenewbev.com/program/march-30-last-tango-in-paris</guid></item><item><title>A Woman in Flames       / Belle de Jour</title><link>https://thenewbev.com/program/march-18-a-woman-in-flames-belle-de-jour</link><description><![CDATA[A housewife yearning for more abandons her arrogant husband and their upper-class life. While exploring her newfound sexual freedom, she soon discovers that sex can be a very profitable commodity. And as her new life as a dominatrix intensifies, she forms a complicated romantic relationship with a gigolo.

Catherine Deneuve’s porcelain perfection hides a cracked interior in one of the actress’s most iconic roles: Séverine, a Paris housewife who begins secretly spending her after­noon hours working in a bordello. This surreal and erotic late-sixties daydream from provocateur for the ages Luis Buñuel is an examination of desire and fetishistic pleasure (its characters’ and its viewers’), as well as a gently absurdist take on contemporary social mores and class divisions. Fantasy and reality commingle in this burst of cinematic transgression, which was one of Buñuel’s biggest hits. (Janus Films)<br/>
Cast: Director: Robert van Ackeren | Writer: Screenplay by Robert van Ackeren and Catharina Zwerenz | Starring: Gudrun Landgrebe, Mathieu Carriere, Hanns Zischler | Year: 1983 | Country: West Germany | Format: 16mm | Director: Luis Buñuel | Starring: Catherine Deneuve, Jean Sorel, Michel Piccoli | Year: 1967 | Country: France | Format: English subtitled 35mm<br/>
Durata: 100 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://thenewbev.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/02/Woman-in-Flames-featured.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Wed March 18 - 7:30 pm / 9:45 pm]]></description><guid>https://thenewbev.com/program/march-18-a-woman-in-flames-belle-de-jour</guid></item><item><title>The Decameron</title><link>https://thenewbev.com/program/march-14-the-decameron</link><description><![CDATA[Legendary Italian director Pier Paolo Pasolini delivers nine exuberant tales in this “earthy, genuinely ribald and spicy” (Variety) film. Based on Boccaccio’s timeless classic – and the first in Pasolini’s Trilogy of Life series – The Decameron is an uproariously “irreverent romp” (Films and Filming)! Lusty nuns who perform sexual “miracles,” a cheating wife with a head for business, a dying con artist attempting a heavenly swindle, young lovers caught with their pants down, a servant who loses his head for love and a gullible farmer who tries to turn his wife into a mare. These are just some of the stories Pasolini vividly brings to life! (MGM)<br/>
Cast: Director: Pier Paolo Pasolini | Writer: Written by Pier Paolo Pasolini based on 'The Decameron' by Boccaccio | Starring: Franco Citti, Ninetto Davoli, M. Gabriella Frankel, Gerhard Exel, Wolfgang Hillinger, Vincenzo Amato, Jovan Jovanovic, Giuseppe Zigaina | Year: 1971 | Country: Italy/France/West Germany | Format: English subtitled 35mm<br/>
Durata: 111 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://thenewbev.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/02/Decameron-featured.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sat March 14 - 7:30 pm]]></description><guid>https://thenewbev.com/program/march-14-the-decameron</guid></item><item><title>True Romance</title><link>https://thenewbev.com/program/march-13-true-romance-midnight-show</link><description><![CDATA[A rock ‘n roll adventure following two unlikely lovers who accidentally double cross the mob and hit the road towards Los Angeles. Featuring an all-star cast, slick direction from Tony Scott and an endlessly-quotable script by Quentin Tarantino, True Romance will have you saying “you’re so cool” all month long.

“This is the kind of movie that creates its own universe, and glories in it. Made with such energy, such high spirits, such an enchanting goofiness, that it’s impossible to resist.” – Roger Ebert

“It’s Tarantino’s gutter poetry that detonates True Romance . This movie is dynamite.” – Peter Travers, Rolling Stone<br/>
Cast: Director: Tony Scott | Writer: Quentin Tarantino | Starring: Christian Slater, Patricia Arquette, Dennis Hopper, Val Kilmer, Gary Oldman, Brad Pitt, Christopher Walken, Bronson Pinchot, Samuel L. Jackson, Michael Rapaport, Saul Rubinek, Conchata Ferrell and James Gandolfini | Year: 1993 | Country: USA/France | Format: 35mm<br/>
Durata: 119 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://thenewbev.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/12/True-Romance-featured.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Fri March 13 - 11:59 pm]]></description><guid>https://thenewbev.com/program/march-13-true-romance-midnight-show</guid></item><item><title>Nights in Black Leather (Adults Only)</title><link>https://thenewbev.com/program/march-21-nights-in-black-leather-midnight-show</link><description><![CDATA[Eternal self-made gay sex symbol Peter Berlin makes his screen debut as a German immigrant who gets into all sorts of adventures on a trip to San Francisco in this classic from one-and-done filmmaker Ignatio Rutkowski. The closest a gay adult film ever got to the style of Paul Morrissey and Andy Warhol, Nights in Black Leather is both a slyly comedic look at San Francisco’s gay scene and a tribute to the singular commanding presence of Peter Berlin. (Muscle Distribution)<br/>
Cast: Director: Richard Abel (as Ignatio Rotkowski) | Starring: Peter Berlin | Year: 1973 | Country: USA | Format: 16mm<br/>
Durata: 99 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://thenewbev.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/02/Nights-in-Black-Leather-featured-850x850.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sat March 21 - 11:59 pm]]></description><guid>https://thenewbev.com/program/march-21-nights-in-black-leather-midnight-show</guid></item></channel></rss>