<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The New Beverly Cinema</title><link>https://thenewbev.com/schedule/</link><description>Schedule and program for The New Beverly Cinema (Quentin Tarantino&apos;s revival theater in Los Angeles).</description><item><title>Caligula: The Ultimate Cut (Special Guest)</title><link>https://thenewbev.com/program/february-26-caligula-the-ultimate-cut</link><description><![CDATA[Just added! Aaron Shaps, editor of The Ultimate Cut and author of Caligula: The Official Story of the Film from Titan Books, will join us IN PERSON, schedule permitting, to discuss the film at our Thursday 2/26 show.

While our allotment of advance tickets has sold out online, some additional tickets will be available to purchase at the door on a first come, first served basis on the night of the show. Box office & doors open approximately 1 hour before showtime. For shows that have sold out online, in-person ticket purchases are limited to 2 tickets per person. ADULTS ONLY! Must be 18+ with ID for admission.

Absolute power corrupts in Caligula: The Ultimate Cut , an extensive reconstruction of the notorious 1980 spectacle. Shadowed by the murder of his family, Caligula (Malcolm McDowell) eliminates his devious adoptive grandfather (Peter O’Toole) and seizes control of the Roman Empire alongside his wife Caesonia (Helen Mirren) before descending into a spiral of depravity, destruction, and madness.<br/>
Cast: Director: Principal photography by Tino Brass; Ultimate Cut produced by Thomas Negovan | Writer: Adapted from an original screenplay by Gore Vidal | Starring: Malcolm McDowell, Helen Mirren, Teresa Ann Savoy, Peter O'Toole, John Steiner, Guido Mannari, Paolo Bonacelli, Leopoldo Trieste, Giancarlo Badessi, Mirella D'Angelo, Anneka Di Lorenzo, Lori Wagner, Adriana Asti, John Gielgud | Year: 1979/2023 | Country: Italy/USA | Format: 35mm<br/>
Durata: 178 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://thenewbev.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Caligula-featured.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Thu February 26 - 7:30 pm]]></description><guid>https://thenewbev.com/program/february-26-caligula-the-ultimate-cut</guid></item><item><title>Blonde Ambition (Adults Only)</title><link>https://thenewbev.com/program/february-28-blonde-ambition-midnight-show</link><description><![CDATA[Whisked away to the big city, Candy and her ditsy sister Sugar Kane will finally get their shot at Broadway success. One of the funniest and most opulent X-rated films ever produced, The Amero Brothers’ love letter to the golden age of Hollywood musicals is a tour de force of burlesque humor, uproarious sight gags, and madcap set pieces, all culminating in one of the most outrageous finales in hardcore film history<br/>
Cast: Director: John and Lem Amero | Starring: Suzy Mandel, Dory Devon, Eric Edwards, R.Bolla, Wade Nichols, Molly Malone, Kurt Mann, Erica Eaton, David Morris, Pat Finnegan | Year: 1981 | Country: USA | Format: 35mm<br/>
Durata: 83 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://thenewbev.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Blonde-Ambition-featured-2.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sat February 28 - 11:59 pm]]></description><guid>https://thenewbev.com/program/february-28-blonde-ambition-midnight-show</guid></item><item><title>Deep Throat (Adults Only)       / Hot Summer in the City (Adults Only)</title><link>https://thenewbev.com/program/march-1-deep-throat-hot-summer-in-the-city</link><description><![CDATA[How far does a girl have to go to untangle her tingle? A sexually frustrated woman finally uncovers an unconventional solution to help her climax. One of the key films that launched porno chic, Deep Throat helped ignite a cinematic revolution, garnering major box office success and enduring controversies (behind the scenes and beyond), while fighting a multitude of obscenity battles and bans along the way.

The first XXX film lensed in Michigan! Set during the long, hot summer of 1967 and its impending real-life confrontations in Detroit, Hot Summer in the City pushes the boundaries of pornographic entertainment, injecting roughie violence and exploitation themes into its hardcore sex storyline. With genuine Top 40 hits playing in the background, a group of Black Militants kidnap a young white virgin in a plan to set off race riots throughout the suburbs. ADULTS ONLY – All attendees must be 18+ w/ ID for admission<br/>
Cast: Director: Gerard Damiano | Starring: Linda Lovelace, Harry Reems, Dolly Sharp, Carol Connors | Year: 1972 | Country: USA | Format: 35mm | Director: Gail Palmer | Starring: Lisa Baker, Duke Johnson, Shorty Roberts, Stitch Umbas, Coke Chain, Black Orchid | Year: 1976 | Country: USA | Format: 35mm<br/>
Durata: 55 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://thenewbev.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Deep-Throat-featured.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sun March 01 - 6:30 pm / 8:00 pm]]></description><guid>https://thenewbev.com/program/march-1-deep-throat-hot-summer-in-the-city</guid></item><item><title>Caligula: The Ultimate Cut</title><link>https://thenewbev.com/program/february-27-caligula-the-ultimate-cut</link><description><![CDATA[An extensive reconstruction of the notorious spectacle presented in 35mm! ADULTS ONLY! Must be 18+ with ID for admission.

Absolute power corrupts in Caligula: The Ultimate Cut , an extensive reconstruction of the notorious 1980 spectacle. Shadowed by the murder of his family, Caligula (Malcolm McDowell) eliminates his devious adoptive grandfather (Peter O’Toole) and seizes control of the Roman Empire alongside his wife Caesonia (Helen Mirren) before descending into a spiral of depravity, destruction, and madness.<br/>
Cast: Director: Principal photography by Tino Brass; Ultimate Cut produced by Thomas Negovan | Writer: Adapted from an original screenplay by Gore Vidal | Starring: Malcolm McDowell, Helen Mirren, Teresa Ann Savoy, Peter O'Toole, John Steiner, Guido Mannari, Paolo Bonacelli, Leopoldo Trieste, Giancarlo Badessi, Mirella D'Angelo, Anneka Di Lorenzo, Lori Wagner, Adriana Asti, John Gielgud | Year: 1979/2023 | Country: Italy/USA | Format: 35mm<br/>
Durata: 178 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://thenewbev.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Caligula-featured.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Fri February 27 - 6:30 pm]]></description><guid>https://thenewbev.com/program/february-27-caligula-the-ultimate-cut</guid></item><item><title>Deep Throat (Adults Only)       / Hot Summer in the City (Adults Only)</title><link>https://thenewbev.com/program/february-28-deep-throat-hot-summer-in-the-city</link><description><![CDATA[How far does a girl have to go to untangle her tingle? A sexually frustrated woman finally uncovers an unconventional solution to help her climax. One of the key films that launched porno chic, Deep Throat helped ignite a cinematic revolution, garnering major box office success and enduring controversies (behind the scenes and beyond), while fighting a multitude of obscenity battles and bans along the way.

The first XXX film lensed in Michigan! Set during the long, hot summer of 1967 and its impending real-life confrontations in Detroit, Hot Summer in the City pushes the boundaries of pornographic entertainment, injecting roughie violence and exploitation themes into its hardcore sex storyline. With genuine Top 40 hits playing in the background, a group of Black Militants kidnap a young white virgin in a plan to set off race riots throughout the suburbs. ADULTS ONLY – All attendees must be 18+ w/ ID for admission<br/>
Cast: Director: Gerard Damiano | Starring: Linda Lovelace, Harry Reems, Dolly Sharp, Carol Connors | Year: 1972 | Country: USA | Format: 35mm | Director: Gail Palmer | Starring: Lisa Baker, Duke Johnson, Shorty Roberts, Stitch Umbas, Coke Chain, Black Orchid | Year: 1976 | Country: USA | Format: 35mm<br/>
Durata: 55 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://thenewbev.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Deep-Throat-featured.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sat February 28 - 7:00 pm / 8:30 pm]]></description><guid>https://thenewbev.com/program/february-28-deep-throat-hot-summer-in-the-city</guid></item><item><title>Once Upon A Time In… Hollywood</title><link>https://thenewbev.com/program/february-27-once-upon-a-time-in-hollywood-midnight</link><description><![CDATA[Quentin Tarantino’s Once Upon a Time in… Hollywood visits 1969 Los Angeles, where everything is changing, as TV star Rick Dalton (Leonardo DiCaprio) and his longtime stunt double Cliff Booth (Brad Pitt) make their way around an industry they hardly recognize anymore. The ninth film from the writer-director features a large ensemble cast and multiple storylines in a tribute to the final moments of Hollywood’s golden age.

“The film is Quentin Tarantino’s magnum opus – a sweeping statement on an entire generation of American popular culture and an almost expressionistic rendering of the counterculture forming at its margins, gradually growing in influence.” – Sam C. Mac, Slant Magazine

“As a film about making films, and the agony and ecstasy of everything we love about movies, Tarantino knocks it out of the park.” – Hannah Woodhead, Little White Lies

“It’s a heady, engrossing, kaleidoscopic, spectacularly detailed nostalgic splatter collage of a film, an epic tale of backlot Hollywood in 1969” – Owen Gleiberman, Variety

“An absolute blast, a pure, giddy rush of thrillingly confident, expansive filmmaking that showcases the most resonant and satisfying storytelling Tarantino has given us” – Jessica Kiang, Sight & Sound<br/>
Cast: Director: Quentin Tarantino | Writer: Quentin Tarantino | Starring: Leonardo DiCaprio, Brad Pitt, Margot Robbie, Emile Hirsch, Margaret Qualley, Timothy Olyphant, Austin Butler, Dakota Fanning, Bruce Dern, Al Pacino | Year: 2019 | Country: USA | Format: 35mm<br/>
Durata: 161 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://thenewbev.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/06/Once-Hollywood-featured.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Fri February 27 - 11:59 pm]]></description><guid>https://thenewbev.com/program/february-27-once-upon-a-time-in-hollywood-midnight</guid></item></channel></rss>