<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The New Beverly Cinema</title><link>https://thenewbev.com/schedule/</link><description>Schedule and program for The New Beverly Cinema (Quentin Tarantino&apos;s revival theater in Los Angeles).</description><item><title>Paranoia       / The Sweet Body of Deborah (IB Tech Print)</title><link>https://thenewbev.com/program/february-25-paranoia-the-sweet-body-of-deborah</link><description><![CDATA[“Love is the tool that strips a jet-set widow bare of her morals and her millions!”  This was the first of four giallo collaborations Carroll Baker did with Italian director Umberto Lenzi ( Almost Human ) and it remains the most popular. Lonely widow Baker flies to Italy with her lawyer, who is settling her wealthy husband’s estate, and takes up residence in a secluded villa. Soon after arriving, a penniless playboy (Lou Castel) suffers a car breakdown outside her gates. She allows him to repair it in her driveway. One thing leads to another, they end up in bed, and he insinuates himself into her life. Out of the blue, Castel’s bisexual “sister” (Colette Descombes) shows up, and Baker feels a growing uneasiness. Mind games escalate: debauched threesomes, playing a pop single repeatedly to annoy Baker, and finally drugging her and tying her to her bed. A mix of real suspense and Valley of the Dolls -style dramatics, elevated by Baker’s uninhibited performance (including a generous helping of gratuitous nudity) delivers, as do two – yes, two – wild twist endings.

Riddle, riddle, Debbie in the middle. Surprise, surprise, guess who dies? Newlywed bliss turns to terror when the happy husband learns his former fiancé is dead. As mysterious threats roll in holding him responsible, a voyeuristic neighbor begins fixating on the new bride. An early jet set giallo pulsing with sensuality and packed with psychological thrills, stunning locations, and a glamorous cast. Genre faves Carroll Baker, Jean Sorel, Evelyn Stewart, Luigi Pistilli, and George Hilton star, with a twist-filled screenplay by Torso ’s Ernesto Gastaldi.<br/>
Cast: Director: Umberto Lenzi | Writer: Umberto Lenzi | Starring: Carroll Baker, Lou Castel, Colette Descombes, Tino Carraro | Year: 1969 | Country: Italy/France | Format: 35mm | Director: Romolo Guerrieri | Writer: Screenplay by Ernesto Gastaldi, Story by Ernesto Gastaldi and Luciano Martino | Starring: Carroll Baker, Jean Sorel, Evelyn Stewart, Luigi Pistilli | Year: 1968 | Country: Italy/France | Format: I.B. Technicolor 35mm<br/>
Durata: 96 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://thenewbev.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Paranoia-featured.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Wed February 25 - 7:30 pm / 9:30 pm]]></description><guid>https://thenewbev.com/program/february-25-paranoia-the-sweet-body-of-deborah</guid></item><item><title>Caligula: The Ultimate Cut</title><link>https://thenewbev.com/program/february-27-caligula-the-ultimate-cut</link><description><![CDATA[An extensive reconstruction of the notorious spectacle presented in 35mm!

Absolute power corrupts in Caligula: The Ultimate Cut , an extensive reconstruction of the notorious 1980 spectacle. Shadowed by the murder of his family, Caligula (Malcolm McDowell) eliminates his devious adoptive grandfather (Peter O’Toole) and seizes control of the Roman Empire alongside his wife Caesonia (Helen Mirren) before descending into a spiral of depravity, destruction, and madness.<br/>
Cast: Director: Principal photography by Tino Brass; Ultimate Cut produced by Thomas Negovan | Writer: Adapted from an original screenplay by Gore Vidal | Starring: Malcolm McDowell, Helen Mirren, Teresa Ann Savoy, Peter O'Toole, John Steiner, Guido Mannari, Paolo Bonacelli, Leopoldo Trieste, Giancarlo Badessi, Mirella D'Angelo, Anneka Di Lorenzo, Lori Wagner, Adriana Asti, John Gielgud | Year: 1979/2023 | Country: Italy/USA | Format: 35mm<br/>
Durata: 178 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://thenewbev.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Caligula-featured.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Fri February 27 - 6:30 pm]]></description><guid>https://thenewbev.com/program/february-27-caligula-the-ultimate-cut</guid></item><item><title>Blonde Ambition (Adults Only)</title><link>https://thenewbev.com/program/february-28-blonde-ambition-midnight-show</link><description><![CDATA[Whisked away to the big city, Candy and her ditsy sister Sugar Kane will finally get their shot at Broadway success. One of the funniest and most opulent X-rated films ever produced, The Amero Brothers’ love letter to the golden age of Hollywood musicals is a tour de force of burlesque humor, uproarious sight gags, and madcap set pieces, all culminating in one of the most outrageous finales in hardcore film history<br/>
Cast: Director: John and Lem Amero | Starring: Suzy Mandel, Dory Devon, Eric Edwards, R.Bolla, Wade Nichols, Molly Malone, Kurt Mann, Erica Eaton, David Morris, Pat Finnegan | Year: 1981 | Country: USA | Format: 35mm<br/>
Durata: 83 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://thenewbev.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Blonde-Ambition-featured.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sat February 28 - 11:59 pm]]></description><guid>https://thenewbev.com/program/february-28-blonde-ambition-midnight-show</guid></item><item><title>Paranoia       / The Sweet Body of Deborah (IB Tech Print)</title><link>https://thenewbev.com/program/february-24-paranoia-the-sweet-body-of-deborah</link><description><![CDATA[“Love is the tool that strips a jet-set widow bare of her morals and her millions!”  This was the first of four giallo collaborations Carroll Baker did with Italian director Umberto Lenzi ( Almost Human ) and it remains the most popular. Lonely widow Baker flies to Italy with her lawyer, who is settling her wealthy husband’s estate, and takes up residence in a secluded villa. Soon after arriving, a penniless playboy (Lou Castel) suffers a car breakdown outside her gates. She allows him to repair it in her driveway. One thing leads to another, they end up in bed, and he insinuates himself into her life. Out of the blue, Castel’s bisexual “sister” (Colette Descombes) shows up, and Baker feels a growing uneasiness. Mind games escalate: debauched threesomes, playing a pop single repeatedly to annoy Baker, and finally drugging her and tying her to her bed. A mix of real suspense and Valley of the Dolls -style dramatics, elevated by Baker’s uninhibited performance (including a generous helping of gratuitous nudity) delivers, as do two – yes, two – wild twist endings.

Riddle, riddle, Debbie in the middle. Surprise, surprise, guess who dies? Newlywed bliss turns to terror when the happy husband learns his former fiancé is dead. As mysterious threats roll in holding him responsible, a voyeuristic neighbor begins fixating on the new bride. An early jet set giallo pulsing with sensuality and packed with psychological thrills, stunning locations, and a glamorous cast. Genre faves Carroll Baker, Jean Sorel, Evelyn Stewart, Luigi Pistilli, and George Hilton star, with a twist-filled screenplay by Torso ’s Ernesto Gastaldi.<br/>
Cast: Director: Umberto Lenzi | Writer: Umberto Lenzi | Starring: Carroll Baker, Lou Castel, Colette Descombes, Tino Carraro | Year: 1969 | Country: Italy/France | Format: 35mm | Director: Romolo Guerrieri | Writer: Screenplay by Ernesto Gastaldi, Story by Ernesto Gastaldi and Luciano Martino | Starring: Carroll Baker, Jean Sorel, Evelyn Stewart, Luigi Pistilli | Year: 1968 | Country: Italy/France | Format: I.B. Technicolor 35mm<br/>
Durata: 96 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://thenewbev.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Paranoia-featured.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Tue February 24 - 7:30 pm / 9:30 pm]]></description><guid>https://thenewbev.com/program/february-24-paranoia-the-sweet-body-of-deborah</guid></item><item><title>Vixen!       / Up!</title><link>https://thenewbev.com/program/february-15-vixen-up</link><description><![CDATA[Amid the cultural chaos of 1968 and armed with a budget of only $70,000, producer / director / cinematographer Russ Meyer transcended sexploitation by crafting this “bosomacious melodrama” (Time Magazine) about racism, communism, bush pilots, draft dodgers and a ferociously free-spirited wife named Vixen (the incredible Erica Gavin of Beyond the Valley of the Dolls and Caged Heat .) Despite attempts at censorship that included prosecutions for obscenity and one of the first-ever X ratings, Vixen became one of the year’s top-grossing movies, forever transformed independent film and remains the creative template for Meyer’s unapologetic vision of American cinema. (Severin Films)

No fairy tale…this! In 1976 producer / director/ cinematographer / editor Russ Meyer delivered his penultimate feature, one that went as far out as even Russ could think to go. Welcome to a sex-blasted NorCal burg where kinky Führers, ravenous piranha, sapphic ecstasy, murder mystery, Shakespearean appropriation and the remarkable Raven De La Croix collide, with Kitten Natividad (in her debut with Russ) as The Greek Chorus of it all. Co-written by movie critic icon Roger Ebert (who also lent his pen to Beyond the Valley of the Dolls ), this uniquely perverse comedic detonation is Meyer at his most outrageous, and is definitely *not* to be confused with the Pixar cartoon. (Severin Films)<br/>
Cast: Director: Russ Meyer | Writer: Screenplay by Robert Rudelson, original story by Russ Meyer and Anthony James Ryan | Starring: Erica Gavin, Harrison Page, Garth Pillsbury, Jon Evans | Year: 1968 | Country: USA | Format: 35mm | Director: Russ Meyer | Writer: Screenplay by B. Callum [Russ Meyer], original story by Russ Meyer & Jim Ryan and Reinhold Timme [Roger Ebert] | Starring: Raven De La Croix, Robert McLane, Kitten Natividad, Monty Bane | Year: 1976 | Country: USA | Format: 35mm<br/>
Durata: 80 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://thenewbev.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Vixen-featured.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sun February 15 - 6:30 pm / 8:10 pm]]></description><guid>https://thenewbev.com/program/february-15-vixen-up</guid></item><item><title>Arabian Nights</title><link>https://thenewbev.com/program/february-20-arabian-nights</link><description><![CDATA[Pier Paolo Pasolini presents a strikingly sensual and visually dazzling take on One Thousand and One Nights. Lusciously lensed across Yemen, Iran, and Nepal, the film flows with the exotic, erotic, and dreamlike, following a young man searching for the slave girl he loves, while other travelers recount their own tragic and romantic lives along the way.<br/>
Cast: Director: Pier Paolo Pasolini | Writer: Pier Paolo Pasolini | Starring: Ninetto Davoli, Franco Citti, Ines Pellegrini, Tessa Bouche | Year: 1974 | Country: Italy/France | Format: English subtitled 35mm<br/>
Durata: 130 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://thenewbev.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Arabian-Nights-featured.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Fri February 20 - 7:30 pm]]></description><guid>https://thenewbev.com/program/february-20-arabian-nights</guid></item><item><title>Deep Throat (Adults Only)       / Hot Summer in the City (Adults Only)</title><link>https://thenewbev.com/program/march-1-deep-throat-hot-summer-in-the-city</link><description><![CDATA[How far does a girl have to go to untangle her tingle? A sexually frustrated woman finally uncovers an unconventional solution to help her climax. One of the key films that launched porno chic, Deep Throat helped ignite a cinematic revolution, garnering major box office success and enduring controversies (behind the scenes and beyond), while fighting a multitude of obscenity battles and bans along the way.

The first XXX film lensed in Michigan! Set during the long, hot summer of 1967 and its impending real-life confrontations in Detroit, Hot Summer in the City pushes the boundaries of pornographic entertainment, injecting roughie violence and exploitation themes into its hardcore sex storyline. With genuine Top 40 hits playing in the background, a group of Black Militants kidnap a young white virgin in a plan to set off race riots throughout the suburbs. ADULTS ONLY – All attendees must be 18+ w/ ID for admission<br/>
Cast: Director: Gerard Damiano | Starring: Linda Lovelace, Harry Reems, Dolly Sharp, Carol Connors | Year: 1972 | Country: USA | Format: 35mm | Director: Gail Palmer | Starring: Lisa Baker, Duke Johnson, Shorty Roberts, Stitch Umbas, Coke Chain, Black Orchid | Year: 1976 | Country: USA | Format: 35mm<br/>
Durata: 55 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://thenewbev.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Deep-Throat-featured.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sun March 01 - 6:30 pm / 8:00 pm]]></description><guid>https://thenewbev.com/program/march-1-deep-throat-hot-summer-in-the-city</guid></item><item><title>Deep Throat (Adults Only)       / Hot Summer in the City (Adults Only)</title><link>https://thenewbev.com/program/february-28-deep-throat-hot-summer-in-the-city</link><description><![CDATA[How far does a girl have to go to untangle her tingle? A sexually frustrated woman finally uncovers an unconventional solution to help her climax. One of the key films that launched porno chic, Deep Throat helped ignite a cinematic revolution, garnering major box office success and enduring controversies (behind the scenes and beyond), while fighting a multitude of obscenity battles and bans along the way.

The first XXX film lensed in Michigan! Set during the long, hot summer of 1967 and its impending real-life confrontations in Detroit, Hot Summer in the City pushes the boundaries of pornographic entertainment, injecting roughie violence and exploitation themes into its hardcore sex storyline. With genuine Top 40 hits playing in the background, a group of Black Militants kidnap a young white virgin in a plan to set off race riots throughout the suburbs. ADULTS ONLY – All attendees must be 18+ w/ ID for admission<br/>
Cast: Director: Gerard Damiano | Starring: Linda Lovelace, Harry Reems, Dolly Sharp, Carol Connors | Year: 1972 | Country: USA | Format: 35mm | Director: Gail Palmer | Starring: Lisa Baker, Duke Johnson, Shorty Roberts, Stitch Umbas, Coke Chain, Black Orchid | Year: 1976 | Country: USA | Format: 35mm<br/>
Durata: 55 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://thenewbev.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Deep-Throat-featured.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sat February 28 - 7:00 pm / 8:30 pm]]></description><guid>https://thenewbev.com/program/february-28-deep-throat-hot-summer-in-the-city</guid></item><item><title>Caligula: The Ultimate Cut (Special Guest)</title><link>https://thenewbev.com/program/february-26-caligula-the-ultimate-cut</link><description><![CDATA[Just added! Aaron Shaps, editor of The Ultimate Cut and author of Caligula: The Official Story of the Film from Titan Books, will join us IN PERSON, schedule permitting, to discuss the film at our Thursday 2/26 show.

An extensive reconstruction of the notorious spectacle presented in 35mm!

Absolute power corrupts in Caligula: The Ultimate Cut , an extensive reconstruction of the notorious 1980 spectacle. Shadowed by the murder of his family, Caligula (Malcolm McDowell) eliminates his devious adoptive grandfather (Peter O’Toole) and seizes control of the Roman Empire alongside his wife Caesonia (Helen Mirren) before descending into a spiral of depravity, destruction, and madness.<br/>
Cast: Director: Principal photography by Tino Brass; Ultimate Cut produced by Thomas Negovan | Writer: Adapted from an original screenplay by Gore Vidal | Starring: Malcolm McDowell, Helen Mirren, Teresa Ann Savoy, Peter O'Toole, John Steiner, Guido Mannari, Paolo Bonacelli, Leopoldo Trieste, Giancarlo Badessi, Mirella D'Angelo, Anneka Di Lorenzo, Lori Wagner, Adriana Asti, John Gielgud | Year: 1979/2023 | Country: Italy/USA | Format: 35mm<br/>
Durata: 178 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://thenewbev.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Caligula-featured.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Thu February 26 - 7:30 pm]]></description><guid>https://thenewbev.com/program/february-26-caligula-the-ultimate-cut</guid></item><item><title>Arabian Nights</title><link>https://thenewbev.com/program/february-19-arabian-nights</link><description><![CDATA[Pier Paolo Pasolini presents a strikingly sensual and visually dazzling take on One Thousand and One Nights. Lusciously lensed across Yemen, Iran, and Nepal, the film flows with the exotic, erotic, and dreamlike, following a young man searching for the slave girl he loves, while other travelers recount their own tragic and romantic lives along the way.<br/>
Cast: Director: Pier Paolo Pasolini | Writer: Pier Paolo Pasolini | Starring: Ninetto Davoli, Franco Citti, Ines Pellegrini, Tessa Bouche | Year: 1974 | Country: Italy/France | Format: English subtitled 35mm<br/>
Durata: 130 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://thenewbev.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Arabian-Nights-featured.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Thu February 19 - 7:30 pm]]></description><guid>https://thenewbev.com/program/february-19-arabian-nights</guid></item><item><title>Through the Looking Glass (Adults Only)       / Bacchanale (Adults Only)       / Bonus SECRET Third Movie (Adults Only)</title><link>https://thenewbev.com/program/february-22-through-the-looking-glass-bacchanale-secret-third-movie</link><description><![CDATA[Catherine’s life is one of luxury. But since the death of her beloved father, her stately family home, luxurious car, and refined sensibilities have not brought her happiness. Aloof and disinterested in her husband and daughter, Catherine prefers to spend her evenings engaged in sensual fantasies while sitting amongst the items from her childhood bedroom, now stored in a dark attic. But one stormy night, while seated in front of a large mirror, her father – or a demon in his shape – appears in the reflection, promising her untold pleasures and happiness if she simply comes through the glass. Frightened at first, Catherine eventually gives in and begins to visit the steadily more sinister world inside the mirror. But with each dream-like trip, the dark truths of her past, which she has tried so long to forget, start becoming more and more clear, all as the sinister power of temptation becomes wholly irresistible…  An unsettling supernatural thriller which explores the terror of long buried trauma, director Jonas Middleton ( Just Before Dawn ) and screenwriter Ron Wertheim’s ( Memories Within Miss Aggie ) genre defying masterpiece, Through the Looking Glass , ranks as one of the finest examples of hardcore filmmaking ever produced. Assembling a outstanding cast headed by Catherine Burgess ( Cinderella 2000 , Expose Me Lovely ), Jamie Gillis ( Dracula Sucks ), Teri Hall ( The Story of Joanna ), Kim Pope ( The Intrusion ), and Roger Caine ( Martin ) and featuring an acclaimed original score composed by Arlon Ober ( Eating Raoul ) and Harry Manfredini ( Friday the 13th ). (Mélusine)

The Amero Brothers helm a crossover of arthouse and hardcore, mixing the strange & surreal, erotic & artistic, to craft a truly one-of-a-kind NYC underground classic. A tormented woman goes through Dante’s Inferno, processing her own feelings through a series of haunting sexual fantasies and stark dreamscapes.

A previously-thought-lost XXX ultra-rarity uncovered by the Vinegar Syndrome archivists! Be the first audience in nearly 50 years to experience this must-see rediscovery, with the title remaining top secret until the film unspools on screen.<br/>
Cast: Director: Jonas Middleton | Starring: Jamie Gillis, Catherine Burgess, Kim Pope, Terri Hall, Roger Caine | Year: 1976 | Country: USA | Format: 35mm | Director: John and Lem Amero | Starring: Uta Erickson | Year: 1970 | Country: USA | Format: 35mm<br/>
Durata: 75 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://thenewbev.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Through-the-Looking-Glass-featured.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sun February 22 - 6:30 pm / 8:30 pm / 10:05 pm]]></description><guid>https://thenewbev.com/program/february-22-through-the-looking-glass-bacchanale-secret-third-movie</guid></item><item><title>The Girl From Starship Venus       / Flesh Gordon</title><link>https://thenewbev.com/program/february-23-the-girl-from-starship-venus-flesh-gordon</link><description><![CDATA[2069… A Space Sexploration! In the softcore sci-fi satire The Girl From Starship Venus , a Venusian spacecraft lands in London and its alien visitor transforms into a beautifully buxom human female, resulting in a swinging string of hilariously sexy encounters in porn shops, massage parlors and strip joints in a campy quest to investigate the inhabitants of our strange planet. German cheesecake model Monika Ringwald stars, drawing big laughs from deadpan comedy in a film that Quentin Tarantino calls one of the top 20 grindhouse classics!

“Even as a kid I knew I would get things from The Girl From Starship Venus that I wouldn’t get from the Hollywood films” – Quentin Tarantino

Porn pioneers Bill Osco, Howard Ziehm and Michael Benveniste conjured this soft sexploitation spoof, with Flesh (Jason Williams) and Dale Ardor (Suzanne Fields) the only survivors of a plane incapacitated by sex rays from space. Encountering Dr. Jerkoff (Joseph Hudgins), who has already built a phallic spaceship to travel to the planet Porno to investigate, the three blast off to the domain of galactic emperor, Wang the Perverted (William Hunt). Despite tortures and encounters with odd monsters such as Penisauruses, Flesh escapes, aided by libidinous Queen Amora. Wang shoots down their ship, but Flesh survives to reunite with Dr. Jerkoff. Wang’s intentions of marrying Dale are foiled when Nellie (Candy Samples), chief of the Amazonian lesbians kidnaps her. Flesh and Jerkoff rescue Dale, aided by gay Prince Precious and his forest tribe. When Jerkoff confronts Wang with a new weapon, Wang brings to life the giant idol, the Great God Porno to prevent his prey from escaping.

“A goofy, corny, sexually outrageous tribute… complete with up-to-date special effects, kitschy costumes, and godawful acting… a huge amount of fun” – Mondo Digital<br/>
Cast: Director: Derek Ford | Starring: Monika Ringwald, Mark Jones, Andrew Grant, Tony Kenyon, David Rayner, Beatrice Shaw | Year: 1975 | Country: UK | Format: 35mm | Director: Howard Ziehm and Michael Benveniste | Starring: Jason Williams, Suzanne Fields, Joseph Hudgins,  William Dennis Hurt, Candy Samples | Year: 1974 | Country: USA | Format: 35mm<br/>
Durata: 67 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://thenewbev.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Starship-Venus-featured.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Mon February 23 - 7:30 pm / 9:20 pm]]></description><guid>https://thenewbev.com/program/february-23-the-girl-from-starship-venus-flesh-gordon</guid></item><item><title>Once Upon A Time In… Hollywood</title><link>https://thenewbev.com/program/february-27-once-upon-a-time-in-hollywood-midnight</link><description><![CDATA[Quentin Tarantino’s Once Upon a Time in… Hollywood visits 1969 Los Angeles, where everything is changing, as TV star Rick Dalton (Leonardo DiCaprio) and his longtime stunt double Cliff Booth (Brad Pitt) make their way around an industry they hardly recognize anymore. The ninth film from the writer-director features a large ensemble cast and multiple storylines in a tribute to the final moments of Hollywood’s golden age.

“The film is Quentin Tarantino’s magnum opus – a sweeping statement on an entire generation of American popular culture and an almost expressionistic rendering of the counterculture forming at its margins, gradually growing in influence.” – Sam C. Mac, Slant Magazine

“As a film about making films, and the agony and ecstasy of everything we love about movies, Tarantino knocks it out of the park.” – Hannah Woodhead, Little White Lies

“It’s a heady, engrossing, kaleidoscopic, spectacularly detailed nostalgic splatter collage of a film, an epic tale of backlot Hollywood in 1969” – Owen Gleiberman, Variety

“An absolute blast, a pure, giddy rush of thrillingly confident, expansive filmmaking that showcases the most resonant and satisfying storytelling Tarantino has given us” – Jessica Kiang, Sight & Sound<br/>
Cast: Director: Quentin Tarantino | Writer: Quentin Tarantino | Starring: Leonardo DiCaprio, Brad Pitt, Margot Robbie, Emile Hirsch, Margaret Qualley, Timothy Olyphant, Austin Butler, Dakota Fanning, Bruce Dern, Al Pacino | Year: 2019 | Country: USA | Format: 35mm<br/>
Durata: 161 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://thenewbev.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/06/Once-Hollywood-featured.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Fri February 27 - 11:59 pm]]></description><guid>https://thenewbev.com/program/february-27-once-upon-a-time-in-hollywood-midnight</guid></item><item><title>The Fireworks Woman (Adults Only)</title><link>https://thenewbev.com/program/february-21-the-fireworks-woman-midnight-show</link><description><![CDATA[What happens when a brother and sister break the ultimate taboo? When a pair of siblings cross a forbidden line, brother Peter withdraws to become a priest, while sister Angela is abandoned to a series of strange and mysterious encounters. Filmmaker Wes Craven’s sole foray into hardcore, made between The Last House on the Left and The Hills Have Eyes , ranks as his most controversial film, brimming with dreamlike imagery and dark religious commentary.<br/>
Cast: Director: Wes Craven (as Abe Snake) | Starring: Eric Edwards, Jennifer Jordan, Jamie Gillis, Erica Eaton, Marc Stevens | Year: 1975 | Country: USA | Format: 35mm<br/>
Durata: 78 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://thenewbev.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Fireworks-Woman-featured.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sat February 21 - 11:59 pm]]></description><guid>https://thenewbev.com/program/february-21-the-fireworks-woman-midnight-show</guid></item><item><title>The Opening of Misty Beethoven (Adults Only)</title><link>https://thenewbev.com/program/february-14-the-opening-of-misty-beethoven-midnight-show</link><description><![CDATA[In his erotic retelling of Pygmalion, master director Radley Metzger transplants the action to 1970’s New York, Rome, and Paris, following sexologist Dr. Seymour Love (Jamie Gillis) as he sets about transforming Misty Beethoven (Constance Money) into the world’s greatest lover. Featuring many of the most famous golden-age actors, plus a witty & intelligent screenplay, Misty Beethoven is the benchmark by which all other adult films have been measured.

Print courtesy of the Nicolas Winding Refn Collection.<br/>
Cast: Director: Radley Metzger (as Henry Paris) | Starring: Casey Donovan, Constance Money, Gloria Leonard, Jamie Gillis, Jaqueline Beudant, Jenny Baxter, Marlene Willoughby, Mary Stuart, Peter Andrews, Ras Kean, Terri Hall | Year: 1976 | Country: USA | Format: 35mm<br/>
Durata: 85 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://thenewbev.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Misty-Beethoven-featured.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sat February 14 - 11:59 pm]]></description><guid>https://thenewbev.com/program/february-14-the-opening-of-misty-beethoven-midnight-show</guid></item><item><title>Once Upon A Time In… Hollywood</title><link>https://thenewbev.com/program/february-20-once-upon-a-time-in-hollywood-midnight</link><description><![CDATA[Quentin Tarantino’s Once Upon a Time in… Hollywood visits 1969 Los Angeles, where everything is changing, as TV star Rick Dalton (Leonardo DiCaprio) and his longtime stunt double Cliff Booth (Brad Pitt) make their way around an industry they hardly recognize anymore. The ninth film from the writer-director features a large ensemble cast and multiple storylines in a tribute to the final moments of Hollywood’s golden age.

“The film is Quentin Tarantino’s magnum opus – a sweeping statement on an entire generation of American popular culture and an almost expressionistic rendering of the counterculture forming at its margins, gradually growing in influence.” – Sam C. Mac, Slant Magazine

“As a film about making films, and the agony and ecstasy of everything we love about movies, Tarantino knocks it out of the park.” – Hannah Woodhead, Little White Lies

“It’s a heady, engrossing, kaleidoscopic, spectacularly detailed nostalgic splatter collage of a film, an epic tale of backlot Hollywood in 1969” – Owen Gleiberman, Variety

“An absolute blast, a pure, giddy rush of thrillingly confident, expansive filmmaking that showcases the most resonant and satisfying storytelling Tarantino has given us” – Jessica Kiang, Sight & Sound<br/>
Cast: Director: Quentin Tarantino | Writer: Quentin Tarantino | Starring: Leonardo DiCaprio, Brad Pitt, Margot Robbie, Emile Hirsch, Margaret Qualley, Timothy Olyphant, Austin Butler, Dakota Fanning, Bruce Dern, Al Pacino | Year: 2019 | Country: USA | Format: 35mm<br/>
Durata: 161 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://thenewbev.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/06/Once-Hollywood-featured.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Fri February 20 - 11:59 pm]]></description><guid>https://thenewbev.com/program/february-20-once-upon-a-time-in-hollywood-midnight</guid></item><item><title>Vixen! (Erica Gavin In Person)       / Up!</title><link>https://thenewbev.com/program/february-14-vixen-up</link><description><![CDATA[While our allotment of advance tickets has sold out online, some additional tickets will be available to purchase at the door on a first come, first served basis on the night of the show. Box office & doors open approximately 1 hour before showtime. For shows that have sold out online, in-person ticket purchases are limited to 2 tickets per person.

Just added! Vixen star Erica Gavin will join us IN PERSON, schedule permitting, to introduce the show.

Amid the cultural chaos of 1968 and armed with a budget of only $70,000, producer / director / cinematographer Russ Meyer transcended sexploitation by crafting this “bosomacious melodrama” (Time Magazine) about racism, communism, bush pilots, draft dodgers and a ferociously free-spirited wife named Vixen (the incredible Erica Gavin of Beyond the Valley of the Dolls and Caged Heat .) Despite attempts at censorship that included prosecutions for obscenity and one of the first-ever X ratings, Vixen became one of the year’s top-grossing movies, forever transformed independent film and remains the creative template for Meyer’s unapologetic vision of American cinema. (Severin Films)

No fairy tale…this! In 1976 producer / director/ cinematographer / editor Russ Meyer delivered his penultimate feature, one that went as far out as even Russ could think to go. Welcome to a sex-blasted NorCal burg where kinky Führers, ravenous piranha, sapphic ecstasy, murder mystery, Shakespearean appropriation and the remarkable Raven De La Croix collide, with Kitten Natividad (in her debut with Russ) as The Greek Chorus of it all. Co-written by movie critic icon Roger Ebert (who also lent his pen to Beyond the Valley of the Dolls ), this uniquely perverse comedic detonation is Meyer at his most outrageous, and is definitely *not* to be confused with the Pixar cartoon. (Severin Films)<br/>
Cast: Director: Russ Meyer | Writer: Screenplay by Robert Rudelson, original story by Russ Meyer and Anthony James Ryan | Starring: Erica Gavin, Harrison Page, Garth Pillsbury, Jon Evans | Year: 1968 | Country: USA | Format: 35mm | Director: Russ Meyer | Writer: Screenplay by B. Callum [Russ Meyer], original story by Russ Meyer & Jim Ryan and Reinhold Timme [Roger Ebert] | Starring: Raven De La Croix, Robert McLane, Kitten Natividad, Monty Bane | Year: 1976 | Country: USA | Format: 35mm<br/>
Durata: 80 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://thenewbev.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Vixen-featured.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sat February 14 - 7:00 pm / 8:40 pm]]></description><guid>https://thenewbev.com/program/february-14-vixen-up</guid></item><item><title>The Defilers       / A Smell of Honey, a Swallow of Brine</title><link>https://thenewbev.com/program/february-16-the-defilers-a-smell-of-honey-a-swallow-of-brine</link><description><![CDATA[Everything they touch is stained! The Defilers are Carl (future filmmaker Byron Mabe) and Jameison (Jerome Eden), a pair of sadistic beatniks who spice up their boring lives by imprisoning an innocent young woman (the “mouth-watering 20-year-old Scandinavian screen find” Mai Jansson) in the basement of an abandoned building. A quintessential “roughie,” The Defilers is a stylishly squirm-inducing shocker from exploitation film legends David F. Friedman ( She-Freak ) and R. Lee Frost ( House on Bare Mountain ). (American Genre Film Archive)

She turned men on, turned them off, and turned them inside out . . . she’s A Smell of Honey, A Swallow of Brine ! Stacey Walker ( The Notorious Daughter of Fanny Hill ) stars as Sharon Winters, the ultimate tease who gets her kicks by picking guys up and then screaming for help. As she leaves a trail of broken men in her wake, will she ever meet her match? Written and produced by David F. Friedman and directed by The Defilers star Byron Mabe, this is, as Friedman’s original ad campaign proclaimed, “an adult experience!” (American Genre Film Archive)<br/>
Cast: Director: R.L. Frost | Writer: David F. Friedman | Starring: Byron Mabe, Jerome Eden, Mai Jansson | Year: 1965 | Country: USA | Format: 35mm | Director: Byron Mabe | Writer: David F. Friedman | Starring: Stacey Walker, Neville Coward, Bob Todd, Sharon Carr | Year: 1966 | Country: USA | Format: 35mm<br/>
Durata: 69 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://thenewbev.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Defilers-featured.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Mon February 16 - 7:30 pm / 9:10 pm]]></description><guid>https://thenewbev.com/program/february-16-the-defilers-a-smell-of-honey-a-swallow-of-brine</guid></item><item><title>Summer with Monika       / Inga</title><link>https://thenewbev.com/program/february-17-summer-with-monika-inga</link><description><![CDATA[Inspired by the earthy eroticism of Harriet Andersson, in the first of her many roles for him, Ingmar Bergman had a major international breakthrough with this sensual and ultimately ravaging tale of young love. A girl (Andersson) and boy (Lars Ekborg) from working-class families in Stockholm run away from home to spend a secluded, romantic summer at the beach, far from parents and responsibilities. Inevitably, it is not long before the pair are forced to return to reality. The version initially released in the U.S. was reedited by its distributor into something more salacious, but the original Summer with Monika ( Sommaren med Monika ), presented here, is a work of stunning maturity and one of Bergman’s most important films. (Janus Films)

Director Joe Sarno’s 1968 breakout hit Inga catapulted its young Swedish star Marie Liljedahl to international fame and established Sarno’s reputation as one of the 20th century’s leading auteurs of sexploitation cinema. A beautiful and naïve young woman becomes a pawn in a game of sexual manipulation and deceit after moving into her aunt’s home. To escape, she must choose between a sophisticated much-older man and her aunt’s younger lover. (Film Movement)<br/>
Cast: Director: Ingmar Bergman | Writer: Screenplay by Per Anders Fogelström | Starring: Harriet Andersson, Lars Ekborg, Dagmar Ebbeson, Åke Fridell, Naemi Briese | Year: 1953 | Country: Sweden | Format: English subtitled 35mm | Director: Joseph W. Sarno | Writer: Joseph W. Sarno | Starring: Marie Liljedahl, Monica Strömmerstedt, Thomas Ungewitter, Anne-Lise Myhrvold | Year: 1968 | Country: Sweden | Format: 35mm<br/>
Durata: 81 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://thenewbev.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Summer-with-Monika-featured.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Tue February 17 - 7:30 pm / 9:35 pm]]></description><guid>https://thenewbev.com/program/february-17-summer-with-monika-inga</guid></item><item><title>Summer with Monika       / Inga</title><link>https://thenewbev.com/program/february-18-summer-with-monika-inga</link><description><![CDATA[Inspired by the earthy eroticism of Harriet Andersson, in the first of her many roles for him, Ingmar Bergman had a major international breakthrough with this sensual and ultimately ravaging tale of young love. A girl (Andersson) and boy (Lars Ekborg) from working-class families in Stockholm run away from home to spend a secluded, romantic summer at the beach, far from parents and responsibilities. Inevitably, it is not long before the pair are forced to return to reality. The version initially released in the U.S. was reedited by its distributor into something more salacious, but the original Summer with Monika ( Sommaren med Monika ), presented here, is a work of stunning maturity and one of Bergman’s most important films. (Janus Films)

Director Joe Sarno’s 1968 breakout hit Inga catapulted its young Swedish star Marie Liljedahl to international fame and established Sarno’s reputation as one of the 20th century’s leading auteurs of sexploitation cinema. A beautiful and naïve young woman becomes a pawn in a game of sexual manipulation and deceit after moving into her aunt’s home. To escape, she must choose between a sophisticated much-older man and her aunt’s younger lover. (Film Movement)<br/>
Cast: Director: Ingmar Bergman | Writer: Screenplay by Per Anders Fogelström | Starring: Harriet Andersson, Lars Ekborg, Dagmar Ebbeson, Åke Fridell, Naemi Briese | Year: 1953 | Country: Sweden | Format: English subtitled 35mm | Director: Joseph W. Sarno | Writer: Joseph W. Sarno | Starring: Marie Liljedahl, Monica Strömmerstedt, Thomas Ungewitter, Anne-Lise Myhrvold | Year: 1968 | Country: Sweden | Format: 35mm<br/>
Durata: 81 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://thenewbev.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Summer-with-Monika-featured.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Wed February 18 - 7:30 pm / 9:35 pm]]></description><guid>https://thenewbev.com/program/february-18-summer-with-monika-inga</guid></item><item><title>Sodom and Gomorrah: The Last Seven Days (Adults Only)       / The Autobiography of a Flea (Adults Only)</title><link>https://thenewbev.com/program/february-21-sodom-and-gomorrah-the-last-seven-days-the-autobiography-of-a-flea</link><description><![CDATA[The Mitchell Brothers, the entrepreneurial siblings behind the smash hit Behind the Green Door , unleash a riotously ambitious porno comedy mash-up of wild midnight movie madness, (very loose) biblical adaptation, oddball humor, and hardcore sex. When Lot and his family move to Sodom, they run up against their new city’s laws against sexual activities…. while a talking extraterrestrial monkey (voiced by a John Wayne imitator???) watches everything from space.

From the ribald erotic novel of the 19 th century that made damsels quiver with desire and full-blooded laddies hot with fleshy lust! In the early 1800s, a flea narrates the tale of its host, a naïve woman whose burgeoning sexuality gets corrupted by lascivious clergy and unscrupulous family. One of the first female directors during the golden age of porn, Sharon McKnight helms an adult classic produced by the legendary Mitchell Brothers.<br/>
Cast: Director: James and Artie Mitchell | Starring: Sean Brancato, Gina Fornelli, George McDonald, Jacquie Brody, Deborah Brast, Thom Glardon, Tyler Reynolds, Johnny Keyes | Year: 1975 | Country: USA | Format: 35mm | Director: Sharon McKnight | Starring: Annette Haven, Jean Jennings, Joanna Helden, John Holmes, John Leslie, Paul Thomas | Year: 1973 | Country: USA | Format: 35mm<br/>
Durata: 92 minuti<br/>
<img src="https://thenewbev.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Sodom-Gomorrah-featured.jpg" alt="Poster" /><br/>
Orari: Sat February 21 - 6:30 pm / 8:40 pm]]></description><guid>https://thenewbev.com/program/february-21-sodom-and-gomorrah-the-last-seven-days-the-autobiography-of-a-flea</guid></item></channel></rss>